masters8: heck yee
gaocaandra: yooo
efiggs: Hey bro
egb3: Yeeeaaaaaah
Mieer: Sup
gaocaandra: yea
logi6000: yooo
egb3: hello
Mieer: Supp
gaocaandra: git it
gaocaandra: boi
Mieer: HEEE BECCCCCC
rrobomonk: fuck yeeesss
mehdi_tw: YOOO
logi6000: 2k channel points
DecayingSkullz: Hi George
danbokhari98: yer
myaocat: PogCamp HACKING STREAM PogChamp
Mieer: LEGGOOOOO SONNNN
simping4geohot: OH SHIT
zeroalligator: Hey George
simping4geohot: WE IN HERE
allbrakesnogas: booooy
GabeDoesNotTalk: I was just watching Bill Gates’ interview
fotisalgr_01: Greece
aliman_21: how much progress have we made
fotisalgr_01: Hello
lordbottaro: Hi Man
Mieer: HeyGuys
rrobomonk: cheeeeersss
efiggs: You are doing a good service by bio hacking this virus
doctorgenus: GEORGEEEEEEEEEE
mehdi_tw: we are doing good shit today ?
doctorgenus: i miss you
the_benju: letsss goooooo
alextodoroki: alright boys i'm gay, lubed and ready to go
Mieer: George whatsuppp
mehdi_tw: there's no haters
joeleonard212: hi man finally I can follow you
doctorgenus: it's been too long, since 11p.m. last night
ssmuls69: yooooo
ad5k: Sugar free bulls >
simping4geohot: PUBLICLY SHAME THEM
dawaeSHW: thanks for anotehr day, cheers from spain
sony193: hellllllloooooooo corohotz virusss
Damislav: our favorite twitcher
microx0ft: @geohot do you think that the electrification of the world has an impact on pandemics? Is 5G impacted coronavirus?
dorkmo: haters guna hate
thecoder15: oh shit hes on
logi6000: not a hypocrite a asshole
simping4geohot: BOO THAT MAN
mehdi_tw: that's dumb to be honnest
l0v3xxx: why does he use light mode I dont get it
simping4geohot: the mongol series was the shit
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you come from gettign laid??
ahahahaitslit: did you check out eric weinstein's podcast as well
jax05_: @l0v3xxx george is a unique species
slimpimp007: hold up, what's the link?
dorkmo: double edge scam
logi6000: @dorkmo I like that
Ayyyy420Lmao: hehehe talking about flipping burgers when u get home
mehdi_tw: that's what we call a hater
gaocaandra: actualky yews
knilecrack: it's jsut chit chat ?
knilecrack: just*
simping4geohot: tbh i like hearing geohots hot takes
l0v3xxx: @jax05_ lol facts, must be
NascoB: OMG HE COUGHED
geekPanther: Yeah,
mattdougherty22: I am listening bc of your social views
squiggly_nibba: Studying corona gave him the corona
simping4geohot: geohot we were going to make an augur v2 PM on whether or not you would stream today
Ayyyy420Lmao: you can get better to some extent, u can get good info from those streams
Mieer: This Stream is for -->> TRASH TALKING / AND DOING STUFFFF
33333333333333: good morning lad
gaocaandra: i watch it to have company while coding
Ozonemaster: was worth waiting. here he comes
rrobomonk: lmao
simping4geohot: ME!
squiggly_nibba: me
knilecrack: Putin
doctorgenus: then why are we watching it?!!!!!!!
aar0npham: lol
lordbottaro: Classic bot
Mieer: LOL
Ayyyy420Lmao: i dont think
aar0npham: LOL
ghostcomrade: That's soo dumb
abk467: im brain washed
v0lko: my brain is wiped clean
mehdi_tw: big homie obviously
mattdougherty22: steams are good for learning how to learn
claudethefraud: ive waited my whole life to watch you omfg
doctorgenus: gay crush on george?
rrobomonk: sheeeeep
aar0npham: yes
the_benju: i wash my own brain
knilecrack: :D
sebastianh_777: brainwash me more4
logi6000: but what if he is and we just are brainwashed to think not to
doctorgenus: nope
microx0ft: nobody
Mieer: My Brain needs a wash though..
33333333333333: george new dictator
nozpheratu: You didn't program me to answer that question, George.
doctorgenus: you're awesome
forkdb: You are not
mikhailangelo: me :)
efiggs: Me
tokumei64: tbh your takes are so hot, i can't even tell if they're good or not, they're just interesting
sureom: WHATS UP MY LIGGA
unnamedtroll: our brains are dirty please wash them for us
Ozonemaster: i feel my brain way cleaner after i watch ur streams. maybe hes right
ankitc: hotarmy
jax05_: @the_benju LUL
Damislav: geo army
alextodoroki: georgehotz when are u going to make my fatnasies come true and bed me
eyesonlyug: The revolution will not be *streamed*
fotisalgr_01: Geo hello from Greece
ad5k: I’m washed
Ozonemaster: !time
roystang: is this live
efiggs: What revolutionary ?
devm0d: Commabroarmy.com
geekPanther: You said this earlier George, "If you take anything I say in the stream serious, You are dilutional and stupid" @georgehotz
zeroalligator: You are showing critical thinking, those who don’t understand turn toward ignorant hate.
microx0ft: @geohot do you think that the electrification of the world has an impact on pandemics? Is 5G impacted coronavirus?
simping4geohot: please respond to @alextodoroki inquiry geohot
caslecasle: You should buby 2020m.com instead
sliceserve: want to play a game of chess?
caslecasle: buy
logi6000: anyone elses stream just die
toxicsicle: toxicsicle subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Yung_Johnn: Howdy :)
champ900: George I love you
awesomeo113: scammazed
Mieer: It's 3:47 AM, I have been sitting here writing a scientific report for 12 hours now.
Bloodswordz88: Hail Brethren
simping4geohot: george glen rock will be the first to fall
Ayyyy420Lmao: as a NEET living on gob welfare i can relate
thecoder15: @georgehotz there are also sides to every trade
simping4geohot: to corona
thecoder15: lol you can apply that to anything
ghostcomrade: I watch these to see how programmers think
theonlymonkas: hi
sliceserve: i can't decide if he is hot or not, what does chat say?
caslecasle: jupyter notebooks KEK
simping4geohot: im a programmer and i dont think
AbsydeAuberon: primeagenAJasm
ghostcomrade: No like their thinking processes and shit
myaocat: what you think? https://github.com/wenmin-wu/jupyter-tabnine/
v0lko: you don't use venvs of pyenv?
v0lko: *or
sliceserve: is he working with a k e y b o a r d or a soviet era tank?
lordbottaro: If u are not a programmer run away
caslecasle: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7jiPeIFXb6U
mashafique: What's up George
gregzanchelli: @georgehotz got more groceries
simping4geohot: pog
aliman_21: switches
ghostcomrade: Who else quarantined asf rn
jax05_: soon the whole floor will be groceries
awesomeo113: george is actually Karen stocking up on groceries
lordbottaro: I’m italian
aliman_21: why is k. e. y. board blocked by automod
simping4geohot: geohot my grandma told me python is for brainlets is that true?
RekLite: @ghostcomrade HeyGuys
mashafique: At some point the whole background will be Whole Foods. Need to get a sponsorship
see_you198: Hello
ankitc: the BBC world family is back
joeleonard212: can you do a quick recap of the previous 5 videos ? this is the first one Im watching
awesomeo113: fuck amazon
lordbottaro: Anyone is from Italy?
oMYTHRA: georgy boi whats good
joeleonard212: @lordbottaro here
ghostcomrade: USA worse than Italy and Spain now
taxad0: love u man
myaocat: @georgehotz Tip: instead of clicking add cell aka on clicking mouse you can click escape(go to command mode like vim) and click a to insert cell before or b to insert cell after
lordbottaro: Bella!!
Ayyyy420Lmao: un cazzo
caslecasle: @aliman_21 dont know why he doesnt add a !***board command lol
caslecasle: everyone knows he is using a HHKB
joeleonard212: ti ho mandato una richiesta di amicizia ;)
thecoder15: We rae number one now baby
ghostcomrade: If you're not speaking english stfu
Ayyyy420Lmao: io no voglio ser il teu amico
lordbottaro: Dopo ti aggiungo
joeleonard212: I know
alextodoroki: jajajaja
simping4geohot: NO FOREIGNERS ALLOWED
PiroFloydian: hello
Ayyyy420Lmao: huehuehue
knilecrack: нјет мај френд
joeleonard212: can you do a quick recap man ?
ankitc: pasta
gaasedelen: where is the Yerba Mate
champ900: George I think you are a net positive good for the planet
Ne0Zer0: LULK
Cheezrguy: жажажажа
Ne0Zer0: LUL
caslecasle: PUT UP THE WALL
Mieer: XD
xmalware60: baguette
mashafique: LUL
simping4geohot: lmao
sockpuppet_user: balls
masters8: @georgehotz Reverse engineer human?
ImpalerV: KEKW
knilecrack: џаџаџаџа
fuseteaseftali: ĞĞĞĞ
5bumbum: jajaja
ghostcomrade: man said "jajaja' guys
Mieer: Age of Empires.. Good Times
gaocaandra: kkkkkk
awesomeo113: gagagaga
eeXecute: jajaja
oMYTHRA: KEKW
fotisalgr_01: Καλημερα
Bloodswordz88: Hail Brethren. Praise be to you HahaSnowhal
logi6000: says the guy who listens to Russian rap
ankitc: who touch my sphageet
lanyxqt2: JAJAJAJ
Yung_Johnn: Is there a list of applications i can open to follow along independantly?
caslecasle: jajajajaaja guys xdDDD
efiggs: Jajahahja
ahahahaitslit: jajjajaja
taxad0: jajajaja
eric_hansen: HeyGuys
lordbottaro: Jajajaja is spanish
kazehaia: mudaram a interface do site plague
oMYTHRA: George we need some BTTV emotes in here
ghostcomrade: who else from Canada?
myaocat: xaxa is russian
forkdb: Yellow boy!!
devm0d: Chupa mi verga
Bloodswordz88: lol
zeroalligator: Ahhh AOE
wask4: preparate pelotudo
Hawklite: @Yung_Johnn yeah, chrome and google.com
ahahahaitslit: @ghostcomrade i am
efiggs: Pe pe poo Pool
caslecasle: jajajjaja is spanish for I eat ass
lordbottaro: Cinga t madre
mashafique: @Yung_Johnn https://github.com/geohot/corona
caslecasle: :)
simping4geohot: @georgehotz can you do a stream working with K framework
ghostcomrade: @ahahahaitslit my guy
simping4geohot: i need you to do some formal verification
devm0d: Jaja binks
gregzanchelli: agreed
Julianhgg: Hi from Dominican Republic ! spanish
ghostcomrade: Nobody: jajjaja guys: jajajaja
fotisalgr_01: Γιώργο ✅☄️
lordbottaro: Jajaja
guinness84: Hi from America ! English
LocoLuka: would you recommend studying bioinformatics in uni?
MrStereoX: Why a mac and not a windows computer ? @georgehotz
myaocat: Hi From Israel עברית
ghostcomrade: don't go to uni
nozpheratu: Hi from Canada ! Canadian
lordbottaro: Uni is shit
zeroalligator: EH
ghostcomrade: Oooohhh Canadaaa
mauiw0wii: mauiw0wii subscribed at Tier 1.
MrStereoX: @myaocat Boker :)
logi6000: @mrstereox better for development. many tools built in. same could be said about Linux tho...
myaocat: @MrStereoX jajaja
LocoLuka: @ghostcomrade wouldnt bioinformatics be hard to learn on ur own
ghostcomrade: Uni is scam, I repeat, Uni is scam
simping4geohot: uni is worth if you git gud at programming in highschool
simping4geohot: then you just skip to the good CS classes
caslecasle: Who knew GeoHot would go on to use the biggest BETA environment aka jupyter notebooks...
simping4geohot: noobs
senpagax: corona buffer overflow let's gooooo
ghostcomrade: @LocoLuka tbh idk anything about it
kingzooc: whats the k e y b o a r d
joeleonard212: is there a github to this project ??
gaocaandra: yea
gregzanchelli: yes check his page
mashafique: @joeleonard212 https://github.com/geohot/corona
logi6000: @senpagax nah zinc overflow
shr1ftyy: >>> So What's the goal of this? <<<
simping4geohot: yeah to get it open terminal and do sudo pm-suspend
MrStereoX: @myaocat why are you awake so early
Ayyyy420Lmao: i dont think people do sequence alignment on their pcs they always use the blast server
eric_hansen: @georgehotz take a look at http://virusite.org/ it's a database of viruses with a sequence search tool
kingzooc: someone link me geos k e y b o a r d on amazon plezzzzzzzzzz
logi6000: @shr1ftyy it's not about the goal it's about the journey
joeleonard212: @mashafique thank you very much
fotisalgr_01: Γιώργο in Greek 🇬🇷
myaocat: @MrStereoX Learning Programming :D
kingzooc: ?
caslecasle: SO WHAT IS THE POINT OF THIS @georgehotz Kappa Kappa
MrStereoX: @myaocat Me too!
simping4geohot: i can teach you to code
mashafique: @joeleonard212 no prob
simping4geohot: you can trust me i am in geohot stream
logi6000: @kingzooc hhkb pro 2. it's expensive af
myaocat: no you can trust me :)
kingzooc: @logi6000 how much homie
doctorgenus: @georgehotz !! what's in the grocery bags?!! it's been there since day 2 of the stream!
gregzanchelli: @kingzooc no k e y b o a r d talk
logi6000: @kingzooc like 200 something
toxicsicle: is this relevant to what you are working on? https://jvi.asm.org/content/82/4/1899 and does anyone know what the HIV aspect of the paper means?
Vepicfishal: Did you come across this link : https://nextstrain.org/ncov?dmin=2020-02-15 ?
ankitc: i should not be watching this
doctorgenus: @logi6000 , do you know what mouse he uses?
maxf18qc: they said on the news to not put your fingers on or in your mouth
jagger_rsw: Guten Abend from Switzerland!
Mint2bSpiced: yeah this is the problem with most bioinformatics programs which are free, you have to setup the link to a repository, to increase workflow
claudethefraud: me neither, i wish i knew what he was doing
ghostcomrade: @ankitc same
simping4geohot: if you want to do an epic hack open a nodejs repl and paste this: (f => f(f))(async f => f(f) && f(f));
IchibanWarui: !uptime
logi6000: @doctorgenus no clue. I'd imagine magic mouse by the noise
ankitc: i am just here for bio talk
NameListFull: hey man, u could stream earlier
myaocat: @simping4geohot what is this does?
kingzooc: 200
Cazaa_: i wish understand what is he doing
kingzooc: lmao
jax05_: @IchibanWarui stream just started a few minutes ago
risky_banana: have we cured it yet guys?
kingzooc: wtf
thecoder15: lol fuck your pipe bomb @simping4geohot
KaleSC: im here to be brainwashed
guinness84: bioinformatics is for pussies Gang gang
froakeyft: @simping4geohot I love your username
Ayyyy420Lmao: @myaocat i think its an infinite loop
simping4geohot: BAD UX
DiosDIO: There will be no cure till next year tbh
IchibanWarui: thanks @jax05_
gregzanchelli: @Ayyyy420Lmao ot os
simping4geohot: @froakeyft thank u
jax05_: @KaleSC you've come to the right place :)
ghostcomrade: @simping4geohot simppp
ankitc: It does not even have dark mode lol
mashafique: movie time PogChamp
Srule: Did you finish your bag of potatoes yet?
champ900: ok do some hackery
ghostcomrade: who know a good hacking stream?
Level_002: !uptime
bleepan: Do you still use HHKB?
logi6000: @bleepan ight no more keyboarda
jax05_: @bleepan he doesn't like to talk about that lol
lordbottaro: That’s comment are serious? Learn programming
guy_ross: @bleepan no kb talk
824ever: Hello Mr.5head
bleepan: It’s memery
bleepan: Chillax
lordbottaro: Chill.py
Mieer: I have been sitting for 20 finishing my science report. I am so tired. But I cannot go to sleep yet. It's 03:58 am. here WutFace
simping4geohot: the fuck is a .gb
824ever: @guy_ross how big is the timeout for the thing
jax05_: @bleepan wow hilarious
simping4geohot: @georgehotz can you explain what a gibi file is?
Srule: are 60% keyboards good for watching pornhub?
simping4geohot: never heard of it
myaocat: Why don't you use autocomplete for Jupyter? https://github.com/wenmin-wu/jupyter-tabnine
Blackwhitelife: did he crack the code?
Yung_Johnn: @mieer whats it about?
Vepicfishal: You can see all the mutation over here : https://nextstrain.org/ncov?dmin=2020-02-15
doctorgenus: not yet
Mieer: @Blackwhitelife yes, he cured Cancer
doctorgenus: he will though
doctorgenus: geohot should start a cult lol
Mieer: @Yung_Johnn Elderly Disease Intervention
uhmas00: @georgehotz what's ur work schedule like ?
mauiw0wii: the geobotz?
logi6000: @doctorgenus nah a church... of Scientology
fotisalgr_01: Γιώργο in Greek 🇬🇷
AlexEDM: AlexEDM subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Srule: Is this destiny 2.0?
bleepan: @uhmas00 what’s your work schedule like?
AlexEDM: B)
AlexEDM: ayy I'm a sub now
AlexEDM: love you, George
Bloodswordz88: HahaThisisfine
AlexEDM: nein homo
ahahahaitslit: 1k people in my city have corona
Srule: @bleepan what’s your work schedule like?
gregzanchelli: @ahahahaitslit gtfo
uhmas00: @Srule what’s your work schedule like?
bleepan: @srule what’s your work schedule like?
simping4geohot: YES
gaocaandra: yeaa
LocoLuka: @georgehotz best book that you would recommend
araeasmes: nah
joeleonard212: are you going to use some NNs somewhere in this project ??
doctorgenus: we came here for codeeeeee
sk84uhlivin: You said we're done with it, I dunnooooo
t00big2fl4il: what
chetdonovan: :)
ankitc: hecker time
Ayyyy420Lmao: write a short story
gaocaandra: bring the clicks
gaocaandra: jajajjaajaaaja
Srule: Write a song
amuzinc: love reinventing the wheel
mashafique: This chat is so memey LUL
Mieer: ~ HE IS WRITING THA CODE ~ PogChamp
DiosDIO: 530,00´ confirmed cases, imagine the new cases in 5 days
ahahahaitslit: @gregzanchelli could be worse
doctorgenus: so jupyter is just a notebook/terminal with a bunch of python commands that run?
Ayyyy420Lmao: a long way to 7bil cases
bleepan: What’s the coronavirus
Mieer: UPPERCASE
Dewzyy_: yo!
EkSing: @georgehotz you look like you’re just glancing when you read, or are you just a fast reader
simping4geohot: UPPER
gaocaandra: uppercase
LocoLuka: UPPER
yungtoad1: Middle case
theonlymonkas: upper
bleepan: Upper
gregzanchelli: @georgehotz use command option d to toggle dock
fotisalgr_01: Γιώργο in Greek 🇬🇷
ClintBushton: 420
mashafique: Why read 30 words when 10 will do the job
doctorgenus: wow redbull?!
doctorgenus: did you guys see that?
Srule: SaRzxx gaming tag case
doctorgenus: he means busienss today
AlexEDM: redbull at 8pm
bleepan: Like listening to this stream
AlexEDM: sheesh
kazehaia: LUL , RedBull 2.0
Dewzyy_: Are you still working on the Coronavirus test?
theonlymonkas: is that redbull or tea
ahahahaitslit: rip sleep
williamjennings1: HeyGuys
myaocat: a video comparing two RNA-seq dataset, not sure if it helps https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YeoHJFHnCrw :)
gaocaandra: because the papers need to stand out
pelegogrosso: Hi Geo, can you say what's the best way to learn programming? or how do you started?
Blackwhitelife: guys how to join the start up? i have programming skills in python, HTML and CSS
williamjennings1: Is it weird to take walks at night
Srule: They guy who names monitors names these too
doctorgenus: @Blackwhitelife start with craigslist
Landowner555: this is some big brain stream
smtlaissezfaire: How do human coronaviruses differ from non-human ones?
Blackwhitelife: @doctorgenus craig?
SOmedude456: holy fuck george is fast on vim
simping4geohot: bruh he not that sick on vim
Yung_Johnn: @doctorgenus where does craig keep his list
11plus4thinking: @georgehotz you should do a gameplay stream where you play half-life alyx :D
ankitc: i could do so many other things but watching someone else is fun
ankitc: so fuck it
twinprimes71: meow cat
doctorgenus: @Blackwhitelife Maybe it's only in US, a site you can find jobs
bleepan: He’s not that fast you just hear clicking
simping4geohot: challenge mode: genome comparison using linux pipes
claudethefraud: oof
anonymous__________: hey geohotz be careful with hands on mouth ~.~
C0deCane: yall remember when the NBA shut down back in the day for something similar I sure hope Michael Jordan can beat those aliens this time LUL Kappa
benchai18: @c0decane You again.
pelegogrosso: what ge's trying o do?
claudethefraud: OptimizePrime OptimizePrime OptimizePrime OptimizePrime OptimizePrime OptimizePrime
joeleonard212: will you use some NNs in this project ?
benchai18: @c0decane 😘
amuzinc: @pelegogrosso comparing the genome seq of sars 1 and the new one
uhmas00: how many hours do u work day?
DiosDIO: I wonder what Michael Jordan would've thought about all this
claudethefraud: where did yu learn all this bro
toxicsicle: have you looked at this article yet? https://jvi.asm.org/content/82/4/1899 feel like it might be related. i might be behind missed the last stream
simping4geohot: lmao
gaocaandra: comopressive transformer
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Mieer: Back Propagation
Ne0Zer0: lmfao
ahahahaitslit: no thats kobe
C0deCane: @benchai18 sup my guy
braininavatt: LUL
gaocaandra: from scratch
prakyath_kantharaju: regex ?
Yung_Johnn: Where we setting up the campus?
DiosDIO: LUL shit my bad
joeleonard212: ok, this is the first video Im watching I basically dont know what are you goint to do
Mieer: Michael is Alive
simping4geohot: too soon geohot
benchai18: @georgehotz u get my email about Xbox hacker ??
theonlymonkas: LUL
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz what is your IQ?
C0deCane: @DiosDIO LUL ahahahaha
davedavidsonfromdavis: deep fry your bat in gutter oil
ahahahaitslit: michael I jordan
davedavidsonfromdavis: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zrv78nG9R04
bleepan: Lol
claudethefraud: HANDS OUT OFF MOUTH
ankitc: wow that focus is sexy
gaocaandra: you can use CNNs
ankitc: if it was me i would have started watching micahel jordan videos
DiosDIO: It's hard not to touch your face sometimes
gaocaandra: google had a paper
C0deCane: Put your hands in your mouth to keep them off your face @georgehotz
alextodoroki: dyanmic programming is ab itch
gaocaandra: transforming dna seq into iages
Blackwhitelife: guys this is the pinnacle of the internet
l0v3xxx: I wonder what Bill Nye would have thought about all this
gaocaandra: and training a classsiffier
williamjennings1: if your gonna touch your face use your hooddie
braininavatt: cute Kappa
pwgenest: pwgenest subscribed with Twitch Prime.
queencitydisco: science guy
thecoder15: what you can run C in a jupiter notebook???
Ayyyy420Lmao: bill nye the cia shill guy
gaocaandra: yea
Rizomni: too afraid to put the groceries away
logi6000: this dude really got all the extension that are in the for browser.
Blackwhitelife: one man's persistence and perseverance, THIS IS THE POWER OF THE INTERNET, GO DO SOME STUFF GUYS
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz sponsored by redbull? Pog
benchai18: @georgehotz Did you get my email about the Xbox / AMD hacker ransom???
williamjennings1: is he drinking a redbull
TheArc_TV: What is the goal currently
C0deCane: @Major_Spicy he's own 40% of red bulls stocks pretty sure he's more than just sponsered
Srule: No sports, no goals
C0deCane: sponsored*
C0deCane: Kappa
simping4geohot: w
williamjennings1: gonna take an caffiene pill
11plus4thinking: yu
zombiedigital: when you print out your reverse engineered coronavirus you might get it. just sayin ok LULW
guinness84: just take a genomics class at ucsd 4Head
simping4geohot: what do you mean by alignment? Are you trying to find arbitrary length sequences that match between two genomes?
bleepan: I am NOT on mushrooms
bleepan: @simping4geohot yes
almonte550: 6 days in a row learning from these stream saga, thank you so much @georgehotz
TactileDactyl: NM score is _the_ standard metric for alignment
ankitc: go to university this is the kind of shit phd make
bleepan: @ankitc no it’s not
Bloodswordz88: google is my university
gill_bates_macrosoft: geo right now is only using 0.69% of his brain
Yung_Johnn: Any word about a possible campus George?
Jehhred: I feel like we've just gone down a gigantic biology rabbit hole here
braininavatt: PogChamp Clap
mashafique: @Jehhred we've been in the rabbit for a few days now
imrooty: EZ
thecoder15: yup the rabbitwhole is deep
myaocat: @thecoder15 yes you can
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp
Ayyyy420Lmao: noooooooooo u cant name in wuhan virus its racys
braininavatt: ^
bleepan: Spanish flu
ankitc: its chinese virus
DiosDIO: LUL racys
isalhi: what’s the move tnght on this stream
javalava96: crazy that we're all here because someone ate a bat
Jehhred: Not sure if we're getting closer to a solution or developing bigger problems
GingerPowder: PogChamp cvHazmat
braininavatt: !whatsthemovetonight
ankitc: that is bat soup crazy
nozpheratu: Did he just search for a virus using a sequence?
Bowlgirlblergh: Kung flu 4Head
thecoder15: Im looking for a robotics project to start what problem should i try to solve?
Yung_Johnn: entomophagy
uhmas00: bat soup
dingus74: LOL
Ayyyy420Lmao: that's the cnn version
gregzanchelli: bat aids
gaocaandra: the bat was aspie
bleepan: Dood really bunched a wierd lookin bird
Waywoah: I heard it was just from being around the animals
robonhansonem: We are all hear because we jelly of Hotz brain,
JesseSkinner: i heard it was some kind of armadillo endangered species thing
simping4geohot: i don't think that's clear
braininavatt: like, how could you resist bat soup Kappa
DiosDIO: They eat something like a serpent or a bat
toxicsicle: @georgehotz is HIV relevant to corono or anything you are working on? https://jvi.asm.org/content/82/4/1899
Srule: I tried ecstasy for the first time while in quarantine at my mother in laws house. I ended up rubbing a balloon in my head until I cummed in my pants. Now I’m stuck and shit is awkward.
jax05_: but that's my favorite part
uhmas00: they drank BAT SOUP
almonte550: No no no, there was a intermediate animal
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
anxova: Kappa sure
fizeh: 90% of the entertainment from the stream comes from distractions
AresRai: chat adhd fit your adhd its ok
zelkh9: are there pdb models of all 4 major envelope proteins?
theonlymonkas: LUL
almonte550: between bat and us
braininavatt: yes, blame the cats
DiosDIO: a snake
Mieer: A stewpot was made from: Bat / Snake / Rat ?
Mint2bSpiced: no humans where infected by a pangolin which was infected by a bat...
TactileDactyl: there is a "wet market" where 40 wild animals were sold, there was blood and feces everywhere according to a worker
ankitc: this is bat soup crazu amirite ?
TactileDactyl: spread by contact
pelegogrosso: George, what's the best way to learn programming? books.. foruns.., I think i'm too old to star 20 yo.
braininavatt: no need to go into a rabbit hole, just watch the last scene of contagion SeemsGood
zeroalligator: Rabbit hole
simping4geohot: @pelegogrosso that's not too late
TactileDactyl: they dry the bats for "medicine"
atzehji: this stream is kinda relaxing. watching before going to sleep lol
doctorgenus: did you eat dinner yet? can we see you cook? lol
Bowlgirlblergh: if it's great is it really crap?
thecoder15: @georgehotz you get that sequencer i linked a few streams ago yet?
simping4geohot: You just need to get curious and break shit
Clevermacia: Bro - George Hotz is such an inspiration . Thank you for all you do man. You've changed my life for the good
simping4geohot: and eventually it works
Mieer: Great CRAP StinkyCheese
Waywoah: Apparently pagolins are possible carriers https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-2169-0?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_content=organic&utm_campaign=NGMT_USG_JC01_GL_Nature
Clevermacia: You should create a cure with a quantum computer, like IBMs quiskit -- https://quantum-computing.ibm.com/
almonte550: Is it a bad moment to eat bat soup?
braininavatt: huh
Ayyyy420Lmao: @almonte550 nope, its the best moment, no one buys bats anymore theyre cheap now
bleepan: @clevermacia bruh shh
DiosDIO: Have you guys seen what Wuhan was selling in the wet markets? Crazy shit
Srule: What’s the best way to start programming? I’m 11 and scared it’s to late. Should I watch YouTube videos or buy books? Thank you
almonte550: @Ayyyy420Lmao sweet!
zelkh9: all this is just homology modeling @georgehotz
braininavatt: if i ever go to Indonesia, i am having some of that bat soup
TheArc_TV: Fold some proteins, will only take a full research computing cluster:D
kenzo_94: Hi George, what did you do the last streams? I lost them
Ayyyy420Lmao: i want to eat dogs and cats but dont have money to travel to china
robonhansonem: Srule. Find a problem you want to solve, figure out how to do it with a computer.
TheArc_TV: 4Head
simping4geohot: @Srule meditation and gfuel bro
Clevermacia: Ive been using openpilot on my rav4 2019 for over a year, I'll never drive another car without openpilot
Yung_Johnn: @Srule dont look at the world like that. listen to bach and other classical music, find an interest that fits you
echobrother: what language is he programming in
pelegogrosso: do you think that books are good way to start learn?
almonte550: @echobrother python
benchai18: @kenzo_94 They’re on the comma AI Yourube channel
OGDonNinja: here's some real info if you want to check it out https://patents.google.com/patent/US10130701B2/en
simping4geohot: he's programming in fortran
jax05_: @pelegogrosso it depends on your learning style
echobrother: @almonte550 Is that the best hacking language?
DiosDIO: AIDS was also transmitted from an ape or monkey to a human, humans really need to stop eating or fucking exotic animals
mr_stochastic: @pelegogrosso Best to just start coding something. You'll get stuck, then google or reference a book, then try code. And you repeat
simping4geohot: @echobrother there is no best hacking language lol
ankitc: i want to hit close on this tab and start working
oMYTHRA: the language that shares a name with a snake
almonte550: @echobrother the best hacking language could be any language to be honest
almonte550: If you are good enought
mr_stochastic: @echobrother Not best necessarily. Lots of good libraries for that kind of thing in Ruby too
braininavatt: yep, that's how it works Kappa
microx0ft: does anyone think that 5G is related to corona virus?
echobrother: @almonte550 what do you recommend
Clevermacia: for reals though go down the quantum loophole, I feel like you could legit solve this crisis with your intelligence, a little artificial intelligence and some quantum computing
simping4geohot: python is rly ergonomic
almonte550: @echobrother python
simping4geohot: but dynamic typed languages are for brainlets
Clevermacia: *quantum rabithole haha
simping4geohot: that's what my grandma said at least
OGDonNinja: https://patents.google.com/patent/US10130701B2/en
joeleonard212: @DiosDIO I agree, the planet is rising up. Its very interesting to see how now air is more clean and parks in general, less peolple around
robonhansonem: @yung_johnn If you are going to find and interest, it may as well be the ruminative. Programming is the closest thing we have to magic. Worth cultivating an interest in.
thecoder15: quantum computing is such early stage rn you cant solve shit with it
Mint2bSpiced: See Fold.it
Ayyyy420Lmao: FAH mining cryptos
joeleonard212: means more peace for the nature
Srule: I’m have a brother that knows how to hack. He is friends with bill gates. He said this is all just a big branding campaign by a beer company.
C0deCane: @microx0ft LUL nice troll
echobrother: @almonte550 ok how do you recommend learning to hack
gregzanchelli: SCAM
Waldoqq: hey guys excited for another night of conspiracy theories :)
Abnico: lmao
minami_lol: HeyGuys
tarunaditya: @srule 😂😂
braininavatt: wow how dare them
alextodoroki: geohotz when u gonna fulfill my fantasies and come to bed with me
Mint2bSpiced: see their coronavirus specific page at fold.it
AlexEDM: get this man's stars up
almonte550: @echobrother I'm not a hacker I can't recommend anything related to that
gill_bates_macrosoft: sup boyz, nice to see another episode of the geohot experience
risky_banana: F@H been around a longass time tho
braininavatt: let me star you, what's the link?
logi6000: legal crypto botnet
imAidenr: whastup everyone @georgehotz hobbHi hobbHi
AlexEDM: google geohot github @braininavatt
echobrother: @almonte550 ok thanks for your help
Nudethedder: imagine cryptomining at 470 petaflops.
braininavatt: wooooooow
simping4geohot: pog
mashafique: @braininavatt https://github.com/geohot/corona
Ayyyy420Lmao: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
almonte550: @echobrother no pro
zelkh9: openmm is amazing
benchai18: @georgehotz Did you get my email about the Xbox / AMD hacker ransom? ❓
TheArc_TV: Think one of my professors has an open source MD version
braininavatt: BloodTrail @AlexEDM @mashafique
logi6000: @nudethedder the network wouldn't be able to handle it
TheArc_TV: Molecular dynamics
Clevermacia: https://quantum-computing.ibm.com/
Joshh185: Does this guy have an OnlyFans page?
simping4geohot: probably still not that worthwhile considering btc runs on asics and eth is i/o bound
lordbottaro: Amazing job
bleepan: comma ai == scam
robonhansonem: Gwern was not impressed with F@H: https://www.gwern.net/Charity-is-not-about-helping
Clevermacia: nah but he's live on chatturbate from 8-4 central
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Joshh185 yeah there were lewd pics on the leak
simping4geohot: you'd definitely notice if you were mining eth on your machine
fizeh: LUL
klarmacher: OhMyDog
lordbottaro: Wtf that’s is amazing
oMYTHRA: PogU
doctorgenus: don't worry george, i'll give u starssssss
Srule: The human body is just a node for the virus
ankitc: any CTO on the chat
almonte550: fake lab again?
Ayyyy420Lmao: the requests needs to be approved or u can fill garbage and get the link anyway?
zelkh9: charmm doesn’t use openmm wtf
Srule: I’m cto of IMVU.
zelkh9: you can use openmm for gpu acceleration of free to use charmm
simping4geohot: why are so many bioinformatics tools in interpreted languages? do the benefits of the ergonomicity of interpreted languages outweigh the performance losses in most cases?
Nudethedder: @logi6000 point taken - maybe selling hash cracking power instead then
zelkh9: or just buy commercial charmm and use their gpu accelerated code
simping4geohot: or like data tools more generally
Ayyyy420Lmao: you probably write shit in python but important calculus stuff is writen in c
zelkh9: openmm is in some conda forge channel
zelkh9: ez to install
thecoder15: yeah most computational frameworks use python bound to c /c
simping4geohot: ah so the actual processing has like a C backend?
zelkh9: http://docs.openmm.org/latest/userguide/application.html#installing-openmm
Mint2bSpiced: @simping4geohot they are meant to be ran by supercomputers and nice GUI take up computing power
Ayyyy420Lmao: yea
thecoder15: and GPGPU accelerated when possible
Nudethedder: @logi6000 well, their work scheduling servers wouldn't be able to handle that either, they fucking suck. NotLikeThis
TheArc_TV: Python has a FORTRAN backend I thought mostly
Srule: Hey Destiny, stop coding! Get back to debating or playing league of legends.
JdPaulBlart: !uptime
zelkh9: python is just a wrapper for the underlying c/cuda
raystriker98: @georgehotz you need to check out Gromacs
AresRai: @Srule nobody care about your gnome
zelkh9: you just need openmm take it from a phd in comp biophysics
Clevermacia: get on the quantum computing bagwagon
Clevermacia: https://quantum-computing.ibm.com/
11moon11: I found this: http://www.pyrosetta.org/ It's a Python library for molecular modeling
zelkh9: you do need a hefty system do anything though
jax05_: @JdPaulBlart stream has been up for ~1hr
echobrother: What is George Hotz trying to code
simping4geohot: CMAKE In 2020 pog
bleepan: @clevermacia yadunnonuttin
Ayyyy420Lmao: are quantum computers a thing? i mean a non scam thing
raystriker98: gromacs is a molecular dynamics package mainly designed for simulations of proteins, lipids, and nucleic acids.
TheArc_TV: Yes theyre a real thing
logi6000: @echobrother a vaccine for github
Waywoah: they're a thing, just in the early stages
benchai18: NEVER HEARD HIM SAY “I DONT GET IT” WTF
Clevermacia: @bleepan why you talking bro lol
echobrother: @logi6000 what is github
bleepan: @clevermacia cuzyoooaredummm
TheArc_TV: And good for simulating quantum mechanical systems and cryptography atm
Mieer: Boys.. it's prayer time FADJR. I am going to pray and then sleep. Everyone STAY STRONG THROUGH THESE DIFFICULT TIMES.. BloodTrail
raystriker98: @echobrother is a version control software
Nudethedder: @echobrother nothing specific, just learning, looking at research and probably trying to make some tools in the process
simping4geohot: @echobrother a porn site
zelkh9: doxygen is just for the docs
Clevermacia: @bleepan nuttin all over your face weeb lol
Andremm2: Ah.. cmake, what a nightmare
AlexEDM: i like it
joeleonard212: yes
simping4geohot: no
quinquanonagintilliard: oh yeah
fizeh: yes :)
jax05_: yes
happypuppppy: yes :)
alfyfav: HAHAHAHAHA
doctorgenus: we love it
Aenopixel: yes
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Yes :)
joeleonard212: so funny
mauiw0wii: !live
simping4geohot: but we are shitposting in the chat
alty1066: yes
mashafique: yes LUL
Nudethedder: @georgehotz it's too real
simping4geohot: so its bearable
Mint2bSpiced: yes
prakyath_kantharaju: That's life
AlexEDM: installing software is life, fam
360Plato: yes
joeleonard212: :d
entangledbeing: Can you train an ai antibody against COVID-19
Mieer: Stay Strong George
echobrother: @Nudethedder is he close to coding the vaccine?
Mint2bSpiced: im glad its not just me....
theonlymonkas: go go go!
zelkh9: you won’t be able to run shit on your mac, you need a real workstation/cluster
bleepan: @clevermacia *watches a YouTube video on quantum computing and thinks he’s a head of the curb and knows something*
logi6000: yes
logi6000: extremely
Mieer: @echobrother No not yet
joeleonard212: @entangledbeing no hes not going to use any ai
jax05_: i'm just here for the brainwashing tbh
joeleonard212: if im not wrong
prakyath_kantharaju: Isn't that part of programming life.. installing these fucking things
imrooty: struggling with build system is fun Kappa
raystriker98: @georgehotz just use gromacs already
firmstool: @georgehotz do you feel like you are getting closer to defining a precise problem/question?
echobrother: @Mieer How long will it take?
Srule: Can you clone corona from github and infect your computer? How would we cure it if our computers were getting sick too?
lordbottaro: Another lib George lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: install swag?
alfyfav: try brew install swig
filedescriptor: I use it :)
Clevermacia: @bleepan being a dick in a twitter stream because he can't get laid
Keyeh: swag?
entangledbeing: @joeleonard212 Why?
gregzanchelli: @Keyeh yes
lordbottaro: Damn
zelkh9: the ccmake install is easy bro, just install the dependencies
Clevermacia: @bleepan sorry your dry bro, social distancing you'll get over it
alfyfav: BREW INSTALL SWIG
Nudethedder: @echobrother he hasn't even approached anything resembling modifying, well.. anything - so no
adrijan1990: try sipping on some Nescafe for increased productivity. I, for one, become a genius after a dose ;)
alfyfav: YESSS SRR
joeleonard212: @entangledbeing I dunno I asked if he will use some NNs he said "no,no"
robonhansonem: Why can’t we synthesize antibodies? Can’t we build custom bacteria? Why can’t we use them to pump out antibodies?
bleepan: @clevermacia hahah I love twitter streams
Srule: Can you by some led lights for your stream please?
echobrother: @Nudethedder so what code is he writing?
toxicsicle: Difference in Receptor Usage between Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS) Coronavirus and SARS-Like Coronavirus of Bat Origin https://jvi.asm.org/content/82/4/1899
MrStereoX: Hey ! did you read Spiens ? @georgehotz
doctorgenus: can we cook?!!!
Ayyyy420Lmao: antibodies are produced on animal cells they dont fold propely en bacteria
almonte550: ASMR
doctorgenus: oh oh oh
entangledbeing: @joeleonard212 Lol he needs convincing
gregzanchelli: lex fridman
happenstancequery: pronhub premium
LocoLuka: USHER
Keyeh: ASMR
theonlymonkas: eminem
the_benju: cardi b corona virus remix
mauiw0wii: with darkmode.
jax05_: oh please no
doctorgenus: stephen curry interview fauci
benchai18: @georgehotz Did you get my email about the Xbox / AMD hacker ransom???
zibranja: what is george's gola ?
Ayyyy420Lmao: watch terry davis videos
filedescriptor: lol
Landowner555: LMFAOOOO
yungtoad1: i cum
mashafique: Don't do this to us
theonlymonkas: LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: ZZoomer
chucknorrisbeard12: LOL
simping4geohot: thanks george!
theonlymonkas: nooooooooooooooooooo
gregzanchelli: lex
bleepan: George why
slimpimp007: exurba1
robonhansonem: But they are just proteins, right?
Orennnn: lmfao
imrooty: lol
mashafique: lex fridman
almonte550: ASMR dud
Ayyyy420Lmao: watch terry davis videos.
happenstancequery: what the hell is a morgz
theonlymonkas: eminem
MrStereoX: DAILY DOSE OF INTERNET @georgehotz
chucknorrisbeard12: torture
quinquanonagintilliard: lofi
gregzanchelli: lex fridman
uther20: etika
doctorgenus: the cure
gregzanchelli: lex
almonte550: ASMR man
kyudra: daily dose of internet
thekalkulator: space x
mashafique: Lex pls
Shelledlizard4: daily does of internet
doctorgenus: from lady gaga, the cure
quinquanonagintilliard: plz lofi
theonlymonkas: eminem is nice
mauiw0wii: the office compilations
ankitc: sketchers
jax05_: jeez I got really scared for a moment lmao
eskibro83: urban exploration
nozpheratu: "George Hotz vim"
LocoLuka: lemmino
logi6000: fucking kill me plz
ankitc: lightup lightup sketchers
huntboom: !uptime
lordbottaro: Old shit dude
bleepan: 3blue1brown
doctorgenus: lolol
logi6000: sum41
TheArc_TV: Minutephysics
ImJ4Gu4R: what a classic lol
theonlymonkas: Kappa Kappa Kappa
Ayyyy420Lmao: postrock hipster shit uuufff
thekalkulator: 2blue1brown gives me headache
11plus4thinking: this is some end of the world music
almonte550: Wait what? the world is a beautiful place?
ImJ4Gu4R: ResidentSleeper
Srule: Fortnine motorcycle videos
almonte550: For coronavirus right?
Nudethedder: @echobrother he's mostly just trying to figure out what different parts of the virus do and get a grasp on everything related to it - I think he'd like to simulate a few things and maybe implement his own simulation solutions but it's not entirely clear
ImJ4Gu4R: All hail Covid-19
Srule: Reviews of keyboards please
simping4geohot: @georgehotz cargo has a really good bioinformatics crate
gaocaandra: this song makes me want to kill myself
almonte550: Time to mute this shit
Keyeh: not afraid of dying to corona FeelsGoodMan
simping4geohot: https://rust-bio.github.io/
ankitc: poop time
gaocaandra: tenage angst
ankitc: 💩
gaocaandra: soundtrack
quinquanonagintilliard: @simping4geohot 1
bleepan: Covid-19 is solving our moral obligation to kill ourselves
robonhansonem: Is something compiling?
mauiw0wii: is this hanson?
ImJ4Gu4R: in us pos case raise like never end and this soundtrack
the_goon: can't stand those angry teenager punk vocals
gaocaandra: whoo programs in rust
bleepan: @gaocaandra I have
simping4geohot: @quinquanonagintilliard we will show him again when he gets back
robonhansonem: Nah, just his Em. Bad copy. Lost many IQ points.
simping4geohot: @gaocaandra rust is god tier
gaocaandra: rlly
gaocaandra: ?
bleepan: Yes
gaocaandra: never trief
gaocaandra: whats different
simping4geohot: yeah
Ayyyy420Lmao: who programs in golang
logi6000: so what do we do if George dies on the toilet like elvis
simping4geohot: it's a memory safe version of C
simping4geohot: effectively
C0deCane: im telling you geohot acad is really a cult LUL
Clevermacia: @Ayyyy420Lmao yoo right here. golang
simping4geohot: pog
gaocaandra: we take over
senpagax: ahhhhh golang'
gaocaandra: and start the church
Musashhhi: let's get it
simping4geohot: @georgehotz use this! https://docs.rs/bio/0.30.0/bio/alignment/index.html
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Clevermacia how did u get into it?
robonhansonem: Who here programs in Perl?
benchai18: @georgehotz Did you get my email about the Xbox / AMD hacker ransom???
doctorgenus: george!!! why are you sooo coolll?
Clevermacia: @Ayyyy420Lmao started with react-native, then moved to flutter
ankitc: did you get his email
theonlymonkas: george is depressed
C0deCane: @benchai18 tell us about it
MrStereoX: @benchai18 hope you are doing well :)
yungtoad1: hey did you get his email
doctorgenus: george do you have maids come clean your kitchen?
robonhansonem: Nah. Robots.
benchai18: @mrstereox Hi ach sheli hope u are great
MrStereoX: <3
doctorgenus: someone needs to take care of the groceries
thecoder15: thanks for the new song
Keyeh: why people make it so hard to install their shit
williamjennings1: :D <3
simping4geohot: george couldve just used cargo but noooooooo
logi6000: @keyeh they're just too lazy to make it easy
simping4geohot: https://docs.rs/bio/0.30.0/bio/alignment/index.html
gregzanchelli: @Keyeh bEcAuSe HaRdEr iS cOoOlEr
not9k: lol
l0cky2013: LUL
raystriker98: gromacs, anyone?
benchai18: @c0decane Some dude stole source code for the upcoming Xbox Series X and the AMD APU inside it. Posted a snippet online, said he want 100 Million for it or he will sell it to a bidder. If no one pays, he will release the whole thing online.
MrStereoX: @georgehotz you are the best dude
theonlymonkas: sad george
ICAntF331MyFAce: WutFace
mashafique: Look at us. just vibing on a cool thursday night
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
simping4geohot: the disrespect!
MrStereoX: HOLY SHIT @benchai18
raystriker98: hahaha as soon as he saw rust
slimpimp007: neighbors writing up noise complaint emails rn
robonhansonem: We should infect people strategically to maximize economic growth and minimizing time in quarantine.
C0deCane: @benchai18 thats pretty fuckin nuts
bleepan: George don’t kys
C0deCane: @robonhansonem death row should be first to go
simping4geohot: HATER
gregzanchelli: why no rust
Nussinov: !uptime
benchai18: @c0decane if he has all of it, it would leave the next Xbox open to jailbreaks, mods, exploits to get peoples credit cards,
Keyeh: rust *vomits on the ground*
imrooty: rust LUL
theonlymonkas: i see the noise complaint coming
mashafique: nobody can hear you scream monkaS
AlexEDM: LOL
oMYTHRA: Rust doodoo
goldensoap_: LUL
quinquanonagintilliard: He's cool
slimpimp007: hahhahhaha
gaocaandra: an asshole
quinquanonagintilliard: Be that guy
doctorgenus: sorry george i'll kep it down
imrooty: lol
MrStereoX: @benchai18 imagine this guys is acually bluffing and he has nothing
benchai18: I emailed it to George but he doesn’t wanna answer my damn question
AlexEDM: G A I N S
C0deCane: @benchai18 yeah it would literally destroy all the work they have done over the last couple years or however long they have been dev'n this up
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz i have no idea what you are doing, its 5:40 where i live but i love it LUL
JdPaulBlart: dropping the thing is very loud i hear
Ayyyy420Lmao: san diego wow that's practically mexico
JesseSkinner: ~/fun/coronavirus
benchai18: @mrstereox I don’t think it’s fake cuz AMD issued takedown requests on the GitHub Repos he posted snippets on
hazrid93: is this guy making coronavirus
doctorgenus: give the guy at top a job as security at comma
logi6000: George gimme urbhome address
Jehhred: inb4 he gives the mac a virus
MrStereoX: oh shitt that's insane @benchai18 where did you read that
Keyeh: cool
C0deCane: @benchai18 we will see how the companies react to it but I don't think he will be getting any money
gregzanchelli: go for it
lordbottaro: .../fun/coronavirus/JesseSkinner
benchai18: https://www.gamesradar.com/amp/a-hacker-stole-and-leaked-the-graphics-source-code-for-xbox-series-x/
MrStereoX: TY
logi6000: George why haven't you switched to duckduckgo. you using ungoogled chromium why did you regoogle it
robonhansonem: He will kill us all in his mad hubris.
5_betbluff: @georgehotz have you seen this table from CDC that says 20% of hospitalizations are age 20-44? seems crazy high and different from everything else i've been reading https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/69/wr/mm6912e2.htm?s_cid=mm6912e2_w#T1_down
benchai18: You can read abt it anywhere. I haven’t checked that article I linked but it’s everywhere
lordbottaro: Np
Bloodswordz88: we beyond the games boy
lordbottaro: I’m italian here 800 deaths today, no fun guys.
gaocaandra: brave browser
gregzanchelli: yes brave
AgresticNA: how did you first learn to hack?
crisofilaxx: crisofilaxx subscribed at Tier 1.
jmv_chin: where ya get ur hoodes from
MrStereoX: He want it in bitcoin ? @georgehotz they will pay now ;)
mashafique: elaChug drink that water
Bloodswordz88: eating ass got me off the video games
robonhansonem: crypto shilling is banned.
benchai18: @c0decane I was thinking that too. Cuz if they pay him, they have zero assurance he won’t leak it anyway. BUT, he may get hella $ from underground bidder
logi6000: better results tho
Ayyyy420Lmao: @robonhansonem buy chainlink loljk
benchai18: @georgehotz damn dude. Complaining a lot today
benchai18: @georgehotz yesterday u liked DDG
dvdutch: We figure this shit out yet?
crisofilaxx: KEEP HACKING ELITE
gregzanchelli: lmao
logi6000: this website straight outta the 90s
Krlithus: all bio related sites seems to be made 20 years ago...
gregzanchelli: echo hello
C0deCane: @benchai18 id say if its 100% true they will push the release date back and start over where they can
kisspapa: so what is that git thing hes installing do? simulate the virus or something?
gaocaandra: use brave
NameListFull: duckduckgo is bad at search
Bowlgirlblergh: make your own search engine!
Ayyyy420Lmao: well people from bio dont know this basic stuff
Ayyyy420Lmao: just like u fail highschool bio tests
minami_lol: how to power on my pc
Keyeh: basic Hamiltonian Kappa
toxicsicle: https://jvi.asm.org/content/82/4/1899
edu4594: @gaocaandra brave is chromium based
AresRai: hacking the corona
zwisch: then may god help us all
gaocaandra: programmers
P0LY: evo19MindBlown
gaocaandra: in general
logi6000: so are you saying you juul now
dr_set: that will be cool
doctorgenus: isn't everyone a hacker?
AresRai: could be once everything is figured out and quantified in computerterms
quinquanonagintilliard: by kitchen pharma LUL
MrStereoX: @georgehotz SAVING THE WORLD PogChamp
entangledbeing: Training antibodies
gaocaandra: i cringe at the code written by data scientist
doctorgenus: we all break stuff as we learn
dvdutch: Who got the github repo?
mashafique: @Keyeh where do you see a Hamiltonian?
gazny: one of the companies has an algorithm to solve for vaccines haven't heard of it since.
crisofilaxx: Cheer100 KEEP HACKING ELITE
Keyeh: @mashafique it was written on the page
lordbottaro: Pls I need the password of my gf (retards)
C0deCane: @5_betbluff look at ICU admission and death rate on those stats tho its nothing to be worried about for that age group really
mashafique: @Keyeh I must have missed it LUL
dvdutch: jk found it
robonhansonem: RNA vaccines. Super easy to make new vaccines this way. Works in animals.
masters8: You spent all this time on genomic data, now you want to run MD? Oh noes...
senpagax: wow he's even more manic in livestream than vods, somehow
joeleonard212: @entangledbeing where are yu from ? let's discuss that next time
joeleonard212: im going to sleep now
5_betbluff: @C0deCane yea but 20% just seems crazy hgih to me
robonhansonem: Is he manic or just competent?
benchai18: @c0decane Here’s my thoughts on that though.. the AMD chip in it is new, epic, and not on the market currently. If he has hard coded source code from ROM, they can’t scrap it without making new chips. That chip is EXPENSIVE and ground breaking
Keyeh: gedit OMEGALUL
zwisch: not everyone is skilled in everything
masters8: alanine dipeptide is a meme
rickoftheroot: LUL
nozpheratu: As somebody who works a lot with researchers: most of them are technologically retarded.
logi6000: all these sites straight outta the 99s
logi6000: 90s
gazny: those docs should suggest vscode instead as a text editor since it is cross platform,
hkisthebest: @georgehotz whats up with the bunch of bags behind you?
dvdutch: Can you manipulate genetic mutations using bitboards at all? just a thought
MrStereoX: @benchai18 mmm... maybe they should hire a Serial killer
robonhansonem: Yes, but some people have better brains and are depressingly good at anything they put a modicum of effort into. Life is not fair. We were built by an uncaring Eldridge horror.
ankitc: vscode is kool
prakyath_kantharaju: Some need to tell them that JS exists
iambdp22: https://www.embopress.org/doi/10.1038/sj.emboj.7600640
logi6000: @hkisthebest just his 2 lb of black tar heroin
dvdutch: like a quarternary bitboard
C0deCane: @5_betbluff i don't im sure a lot of the younger people are more part of the transmission and not being heavily affected because are immune systems are faster to respond
benchai18: @mrstereox מוסד maybe?
MrStereoX: more like "black cube" yikesss
gregzanchelli: π=3
logi6000: @gregzanchelli nah 4
C0deCane: @benchai18 I still don't think i would want to be in that hackers position at this point lol
gregzanchelli: g=10
Ayyyy420Lmao: e=pi
gregzanchelli: π=e=sqrt(g)
arielccjunior: I love you Geo Sensei! HOW DARE YOU INSPIRE ME TO LEARN HOW TO CODE!
C0deCane: @benchai18 i am curious how he achieved this.
MrStereoX: @C0deCane its really depends where hes from
guacDev: george how often do you shower
mashafique: g = pi^2 @gregzanchelli
C0deCane: @MrStereoX trueeee
gregzanchelli: @mashafique good engineer
mashafique: @gregzanchelli never that LUL
dvdutch: I love how MT226610 just ends in 29 adenines
robonhansonem: What are these points about?
zelkh9: the openmm tutorial sucked
zelkh9: find a different tutorial online
gregzanchelli: @mashafique sin(x)=x
C0deCane: hes still got to sell it somehow and i don't think that part will be very easy to hide, I could be wrong tho
robonhansonem: I found a use for the points
twitchnozama: amber.xml is probably somewhere else where the forcefiled method has access to?
lolzmaster99: What is being simulated?
theonlymonkas: corona
TheZarkxs: usa is now the 1st in coronavirus cases, USA USA USA!
MrStereoX: Thats wierd
twitchnozama: probably check the forcefield method to find out where it lcd to
logi6000: use comma servers
zelkh9: they are serialized versions of force field parameters
lolzmaster99: More specifically though
mashafique: @TheZarkxs KKona
robonhansonem: Ha
zelkh9: just download the force fields directly
theonlymonkas: 85,594 cases BibleThump
Mint2bSpiced: the forcefields should be algorithms to extrapolate the shapes based on minimum energies...or probability that they exist
robonhansonem: Damn
zelkh9: that is not what a force field is at all
TheZarkxs: man i got lost when maths started to used letters, explain what you are doing or consequences
MrStereoX: Imagine George having kids and they open a lab to cure the world 4Head
ahahahaitslit: any fellow crips here?
mashafique: @Mint2bSpiced a force field is a vector field
nihonzera: the number of cases in Japan started to increase after the government postponed Olympics.
gregzanchelli: @ahahahaitslit i can cwalk
logi6000: @ahahahaitslit nah just Scientologist
robonhansonem: George should marry that German girl who one the maths Olympiad. Have mad smart brood.
robonhansonem: *won
zelkh9: a force field is a set of parameters that define intra and inter molecular interactions for a molecular dynamics simulation
zelkh9: vmd is a lot better
zelkh9: don’t bother with pymol
masters8: ^ for trajectories yes
zelkh9: vmd gives you a sexy tcl interface
masters8: But I like pymol better when I'm not visualizing a traj
lolzmaster99: Is he trying to simulate corno and sodium interactions?
mashafique: @zelkh9 I was giving it in a physics context rather than a chem one but you're right LUL
masters8: Just my preference
lolzmaster99: coronoa*
dvdutch: not gonna lie view
brunnoskyy: hey Junior, do you remember of Marcio Gama and Artur Bruno of Brazil?
Kodaly: haha I see why they call you hotz xD
brunnoskyy: BRHUE AQUI
Mint2bSpiced: @zelkh9 that makes sense, so they are Transferable Force Fields?
robonhansonem: @zelkh9 If we had quantum computers, how much better would are simulations get. Would it accelerate materials technology greatly or are approximations useful enough?
gregzanchelli: more like pytrash
braininavatt: traj it
C0deCane: I don' t believe china's numbers, I just don't think its possible that their numbers have slowed so much
TheZarkxs: felt cute might find coronavirus vaccine later idk
Kodaly: #winning
zelkh9: just use vmd bruh
zelkh9: trust
braininavatt: PogChamp atoms
Ghost_001: PogChamp
mashafique: PogChamp science
Penguino138: Oooh dis is cool
robonhansonem: CoolStoryBob
entangledbeing: Does anybody do all atom sims or visions?
braininavatt: we're winning chat VoHiYo
Ghost_001: future PogChamp
theonlymonkas: wow
simping4geohot: what is the benefit of jupyter notebooks as a python dev?
simping4geohot: like what does jupyter do
veeraman: https://covid-global-hackathon.devpost.com/
masters8: @entangledbeing I run MD sims, is that what you mean?
neuralmind: happy to be part of the culture feels nice
simping4geohot: that a regular text editor doesnt
crisofilaxx: you run 10000 insted of 1000!!
gregzanchelli: activity
Ghost_001: jupyter presents ur code better
raystriker98: @simping4geohot lets you run python code in small increments
gregzanchelli: monitor
logi6000: @simping4geohot been using python forever. still don't understand the use for it
almonte550: Use all comma ai GPUs to simulate faster!
crisofilaxx: you ran 10000 steps!!! insted of 1000
zelkh9: just use top bruh
lyte8: Activity monitor
gregzanchelli: you need discrete graphics card i think
Ghost_001: rewrite it in assembly
entangledbeing: @masters8 What’s an MD sim?
C0deCane: This whole "they went real lockdown on their asses " shit , " they can run their gov better" shit, their "societal structure is better " shit. Its all nothing but Chinese propaganda
efiggs: Have you found the cure yet?!?!
masters8: @entangledbeing Molecular dynamics simulation
TheZarkxs: we went from the coronavirus vaccine to improve cod warzone performance
raystriker98: your gpu ain't that great tho
almonte550: rewrite it in machine code and it will be more faster, believe me
masters8: lol
robonhansonem: I think what China got right was everyone wearing a mask.
Ayyyy420Lmao: the chinese propaganda is hilarious been wwatching a bit of CNC-world for the lulz
raystriker98: plus it might be using cuda and not amd libraries
zelkh9: you can’t run shit on that few cpus
TheZarkxs: move that ass protein babe
C0deCane: @robonhansonem They have to because without them they can't breath semi clean air
masters8: Yes, that's what it is
entangledbeing: @masters8 Very cool. What sort of things do you sim?
almonte550: Does it evaporate?
zelkh9: the output discarded the water away when it saved it to disk
masters8: @entangledbeing Proteins, sometimes with drug molecules. Like he's doing here. Specifically, I do research on the waters he's talking about now
Ayyyy420Lmao: it doesnt evaporate its a closed system
zelkh9: md can’t make atoms dissapear
ankitc: bye i think i am gonna close this tab
zelkh9: its either nve, npt, or nvt
masters8: GCMC MD can
entangledbeing: @masters8 Do people use MD sims to create new drugs and such?
almonte550: So now can we start optimizing covid-19?
zelkh9: never grand canonical
zelkh9: i said md @masters8
masters8: Yeah, just thought I'd add
TheZarkxs: if you are hacking the nasa, can you discover how astronauts poo? ty
C0deCane: @Ayyyy420Lmao whats even funnier is somehow they are the good guys for sending supplies to Italy and stuff.... LUL as if they're not the reason we're in this predicament in the first place
robonhansonem: Getting real Eric Drexler in this joint.
logi6000: did the m16 come yet
SparksCx: wtf
Ghost_001: LUL
braininavatt: Kreygasm keep em coming Kreygasm
lolzmaster99: gehot what molecule is that
TheZarkxs: well its not the cure but its entertaining
gregzanchelli: lol it nearly started at absolute zero
masters8: @entangledbeing In basic terms: To investigate target proteins in order to see how it can be inhibited/activated
SparksCx: wtf are you actually doing lol
Acceptus_Metalist: 16 raiders from Acceptus_Metalist have joined!
C0deCane: @TheZarkxs entertainment is the cure
Ghost_001: Ghost_001 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
robonhansonem: DxCat
aykevy: @SparksCx hes gonna cure corona
ImJ4Gu4R: this thing gets so intense
ImJ4Gu4R: hope got diy test kit soon
entangledbeing: https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/03/200324102720.htm
TheZarkxs: sounds like something taken from a star wars movie, not the newest ones that are bs
zelkh9: good ol jorgensen
jmv_chin: because steel is heavier than feathers Kappa
robonhansonem: FDA just banned DIY test kits.
zelkh9: force field parameters are mainly spring constants and equilibrium lengths
zelkh9: also lennard jones terms
C4TFive: @robonhansonem so you need to get a friend to test you instead? Kappa
Hawklite: yeah, would be cooler if it breathed fire
C0deCane: @georgehotz for your college or academy you should do some "Cicada " like thing on the internet to recruit smart people
logi6000: FDA just banned DIY test kits. fuck
braininavatt: comma.bio not yet Kappa
Ayyyy420Lmao: is cicada the cia or just a prank?
wrelt: both
mashafique: the good ole 6-12 potential
senpagax: @C0deCane 1 haha
C0deCane: LUL
C0deCane: anyone here even attempt to solve it ?
almonte550: Finally
goldensoap_: geothoot how are u so smart
pedrovictortech: BIOINFORMATICS!!!
jmv_chin: snappy google skills
C0deCane: @georgehotz if I contract the virus can i come to your lab for you to study me?
TheZarkxs: imagine if this guy really discovers the vaccine and we will appear on history books. hello grandson if you are reading this you are gay
zelkh9: it’ll take essentially forever
xinthegame: https://www.twitch.tv/xinthegame/
logi6000: @ayyyy420lmao it's a secret society. but if it's a troll with no solution I really feel bad bout those dudes who quit there jobs and dedicated there life to solving
alfyfav: friction coefficient?
alfyfav: seconds?
almonte550: Can we make an hour then?
smalldiickrick: clintNerd
alfyfav: It's a coefficient, should it have seconds?
Mint2bSpiced: how cpu power do you have?
zelkh9: you can’t just turn the crank on an all atom explicit sim and expect shit to fold like what
jax05_: @TheZarkxs I actually laughed
zelkh9: gamma is 1/ps guys
Mint2bSpiced: *much
simping4geohot: @zelkh9 what do you mean gamma?
porteus: @smalldiickrick clunk
jomkingal: Hey George good evening from NJ
almonte550: spikeeeeeee
zelkh9: the langevin friction coefficient
smalldiickrick: @porteus clintSuave
almonte550: spike protein!
pedrovictortech: Has anyone found the ORI of the coronovirus?
C0deCane: real question for chat if the gov came out with a cure that took them 2 weeks and if @georgehotz came up with a cure that took 6 months and all of it was done on stream whose cure would you take
gregzanchelli: @C0deCane gov
C0deCane: LUL
robonhansonem: Hotz. The Nobel prize speech would be epic.
almonte550: @C0deCane who said I want to get cured
esence: Half Life 3 (on Brain Computer platform) confirmed
WooraWoora: @C0deCane the government who has actual scientists
jmv_chin: he basically googled for the past days and surprised how far he's getting
C0deCane: @almonte550 assume you die without it
logi6000: @almonte550 ok so we found the suicidal msn
wombat993: Just joined. Can someone summarize what he's trying to do?
simping4geohot: geohot a google recruiter just called me, they said they liked what i had to say in your twitch chat and think i have what it takes to be a google software engineer! Thanks geohot!
gregzanchelli: @wombat993 hacking the simulation
zelkh9: @c0decane real answer this stream is fun and all but hotz is basically teaching himself an undergrad level of biochemistry right now, he is never going to figure out anything near a cure
MrTriharder: George u still haven’t found a cure admiralFeels
almonte550: @C0deCane gov, no doubt
iambdp22: May be useful for later: https://www.embopress.org/doi/10.1038/sj.emboj.7600640 | https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/19012724v2
mashafique: @simping4geohot your name is amazing LUL
wombat993: @gregzanchelli what simulation?
IbraMiharbi: SIMP
smalldiickrick: @simping4geohot LUL
logi6000: I'm not sure George would take his own cure
braininavatt: where's our cure, george? SwiftRage
gregzanchelli: @wombat993 we live in a simulation
braininavatt: PogChamp
smalldiickrick: PogChamp
braininavatt: progress VoHiYo
gregzanchelli: @wombat993 kidding hes just messing around with corona virus genome data
rickoftheroot: PogChamp
eeXecute: thingy PogChamp
Ayyyy420Lmao: is that the spike?
C0deCane: LUL i was trying to pick out the simps in chat but its not to hard in here
robonhansonem: George’s cure is self replicating. There is no option.
dvdutch: George do you know an estimated ELO rating for the chess engine you built
bfgz: a penis?
miiiiiiim: its a pp
gregzanchelli: pp
braininavatt: GO GO GO!
jmv_chin: what if he naturally buffs the corona and makes a small-corona to a big-corona
MrTriharder: U guys telling me u have rainbow color pp? DansGame
guinness84: LUL
mashafique: @C0deCane a blind person could spot the simps in here LUL elaBlind
simping4geohot: LOL
simping4geohot: good luck with that one geohot
Hoefler02: ^
guinness84: starwars my guy
Penguino138: force field should just be a physical field
dolorosa7: Reverse engineering a 1990s telephone cord?
braininavatt: the force george, pls
Penguino138: or a physical simulation
pedrovictortech: Is he reading comment today?
simping4geohot: that is a truly fucked error
almonte550: That error is so good
zelkh9: the input pdb is completely independent from what force field you use for the sim
gregzanchelli: @dolorosa7 rofl
jmv_chin: that error is so AI-ey
zelkh9: that error just says you gotta fix your input structure
zelkh9: nothing to do with force field
Mint2bSpiced: ^^
smalldiickrick: wow amazing work @georgehotz ! PogChamp (simple copy and paste this message into chat, dont forget to delete this part - CDC)
optimizely: https://rust-bio.github.io/
almonte550: Try fixing your input structure
xinthegame: https://www.twitch.tv/xinthegame/
simping4geohot: @optimizely we already tried to get him to use that
mashafique: @smalldiickrick elaWeird
pedrovictortech: cringe
simping4geohot: he made a vomiting sound and gave us the thumbs down
simping4geohot: geohot is too noob for rust
smalldiickrick: clintSoft
optimizely: haha ok
Fosade: what upppp
zelkh9: this is why you look at your shit in vmd first guys
zelkh9: you catch stuff like this
guinness84: check the names in the pdb files?
mashafique: Don't yell at him BabyRage
simping4geohot: terminal group is like an end triplet or something right?
element731: amber03 sounds like an AIM screenname
simping4geohot: a specific sequence?
simping4geohot: @zelkh9
gregzanchelli: NOT GLN
C0deCane: a terminal group is the lounge at a hospice place
zelkh9: it’s never going to work if just change the force field
almonte550: Stop stealing man!
TheZarkxs: water lifes matter
aj37z: reverse engineer the terminal group
zelkh9: you gotta make the residue names match the force field names
gaocaandra: terminal groups are the ones that occur at the end of carbon chains
mashafique: ^
gaocaandra: according to google
Hoefler02: ^
zelkh9: you need to read a tutorial on how to build a model outside of the openmm api
guinness84: >
Ayyyy420Lmao: >>
dingus74: <><>
zelkh9: like actually using amber/vmd/charmm/gromacs etc
mirceau: >>>
Ayyyy420Lmao: ▼▼▼
Hoefler02: Organic chem stuff
Hoefler02: Kinda
raystriker98: folding@home uses gromacs
zelkh9: openmm is hand holding you a bunch
Ayyyy420Lmao: ▲▲
robonhansonem: Wish I was not a simp.
guinness84: Perhaps you should right a better error message?
guinness84: write
EgoYebo: !uptime
zelkh9: http://www.ks.uiuc.edu/Training/Tutorials/namd/namd-tutorial-unix-html/index.html
zelkh9: do this
simping4geohot: when in doubt println
almonte550: yey
thekalkulator: if my kitty is loopy does that make her a loopy kitty?
zelkh9: the hand holding is not in code, it’s in understanding the basic workflow in setting up an md sim
allbrakesnogas: Fool me once, strike one. Fool me twice..... strike three
Pedroso: I can watch him for hours, but i can't study for 30 minutes...
braininavatt: Clap
Fosade: yep
Jehhred: Yum, looks like Spaghetti
esence: it worked
allbrakesnogas: mom spaghetti
almonte550: Let's simulated 1 hour of protein folding!
thekalkulator: @allbrakesnogas y(x) = round_down(1.5x) ?
zelkh9: http://www.ks.uiuc.edu/Training/Tutorials/namd/namd-tutorial-unix-html/index.html
simping4geohot: geohot can you do a k framework stream tomorrow
simping4geohot: or coq rather
zelkh9: if the residue names don’t match the force fields reside names it’ll never work
Clevermacia: Yo George have you taken openpilot for a spin in the rav4 yet?
simping4geohot: @zelkh9 is trying to show you the way but you won't let him
Clevermacia: 2019 specifically
lyte8: In the open docs there is something about missing residue templates
allbrakesnogas: @thekalkulator it was an office quote but sure why not
zelkh9: this’ll teach the underlying shit
imrooty: RTFM
guinness84: underlying shit is for pussies
Lizardan: what state in US does george live?
pedrovictortech: cali
simping4geohot: CA
braininavatt: LUL
smalldiickrick: @lyte8 PogChamp
mashafique: LUL
WaeHaKe: PogU
simping4geohot: 1337 shit geohot
westonwaldo: GEORGE! keep on streaming 4 life quit comma ai and do this forever
crisofilaxx: lol
esence: bioscriptkiddie? that's disgusting
braininavatt: copy-paste never fails SeemsGood
pedrovictortech: PogChamp
gazny: Learning bio is 5 days
antiratt: But can you hack the coronavirus?
allbrakesnogas: script kiddie is my rap name
thekalkulator: @allbrakesnogas what, are you, a downhill cart?
westonwaldo: westonwaldo subscribed with Twitch Prime.
treestompztv: script kiddies boot corona offline
pedrovictortech: Do people know the ori of covid-19?
zelkh9: you’re hiking up everest with a plastic hammer
westonwaldo: enjoy the sub sexi
hordead: it looks like you have no idea of what your doing
Clevermacia: hearing george say "everyone was a script kiddie once" man you've really humbled down lol
logi6000: headspace?
zelkh9: go through the namd manual
MrMcaustin1: Finally got on at the same time you were streaming <3
WaeHaKe: i have my ar15 ready to shoot corona out of the sky
esence: @Clevermacia , he was not talking about himself, though
Lizardan: Did George finish college?
MrMcaustin1: @Lizardan read his wikipedia page
InfiniteReddit: Hello fren
MrTriharder: @lizardan He was in Carnegie Mellon
Clevermacia: @esence I know, but I"m used to him talking sht on script kiddies or anyone with less intelligence than himself
westonwaldo: GEORGE! keep on streaming 4 life quit comma ai and do this forever
Lizardan: @MrMcaustin1 did he finish?
MrMcaustin1: I dont know
westonwaldo: what is George trying to do with all of this coding? what is the objective of all of this?
InfiniteReddit: Programming POGS
MrMcaustin1: Check his wikipedia page and thats probably as much info you'll get
robinbrinkler: according to github issues/2103 nucleotide being terminated differently in template might cause this error - if you open the xml file for the protein you're trying to load, it might show a phosphate or hydroxyl group at the end of <PDBx:name>. If that was a P or OH, then that should match the template - <Atom charge="0.4396" name="HO3'" type="DNA-HO"/>
TheArc_TV: Think he said he dropped out on AI podcast
zelkh9: if you read the namd tutorial you’ll get a lot farther
Luiserebii: Python is truly a gamer programming language
Clevermacia: yeah he has a degree, he worked for google and facebook while in college
braininavatt: ew, trying to understand stuff??? DansGame
aj37z: how much apartment cost
esence: anyways, this is a cool direction where programming might be headed. Even Gaben is investing resources into Brain Computing... :>
zelkh9: the fact that it uses vmd/namd and not openmm is irrelevant
smalldiickrick: NaM
robinbrinkler: -OH HO
ccb_ccb: what's the point of this
braininavatt: who read tutorials nowadays? Kappa
westonwaldo: keep on streaming 4 life quit comma ai and do this forever
ccb_ccb: ?
zelkh9: undergrads do it bruh
mashafique: Breaktime part 2 LUL ?
MrMcaustin1: @westonwaldo please dont spam the same message
eeXecute: LUL
simping4geohot: holy fuck
rstk1: LUL
simping4geohot: why is the tooling for all this shit so terrible
robonhansonem: Shit
zelkh9: they need you to register so they can get usage numbers to get their nih funding
simping4geohot: wheres my sudo apt-get
treestompztv: we have it so good in normal software
Lizardan: looks like he didn't finish college
mashafique: stream dowN?
Paw_4: wow the simulation is crashing right here
Eternallightning: hacking into system monkaS
mashafique: This is Golden Experience REquiem
TwitchahShadow: @georgehotz chrome 0day confirmed ?
Clevermacia: its your ram breh
Incurs0: LUL
FancyDawg_: back
braininavatt: DO SOMETHING! BibleThump
esence: isn't your JupyterLab running that model?
simping4geohot: lmfao
luigifrcruz: This livestream was seized by the FDA.
gazny: R<S a;ways told me google was malware
Penguino138: Use Brave browser instead of Chrome
dr_set: ditch chrome
Mint2bSpiced: what version of OBS do you have?
EgoYebo: Stop downloading Terrabytes of Pr0n Kappa
braininavatt: UPGRADE RAM!!! ffs
granti7: a hotkey?
MrStereoX: HACKED BABY
allbrakesnogas: network?
treestompztv: LUL
mashafique: NaM d
mrhdr: NaM ed
el_pirulote: its because of wam
simping4geohot: post link to namd page?
Penguino138: Are they making you mine Monero?
westonwaldo: wifi?
P0LY: NaM 7
porteus: NaM 7
11plus4thinking: NaM ez 5 dollars
zwisch: open firefox
MrMcaustin1: its the cdc, no more sars research
Mint2bSpiced: The older OBS version posted this error for mac
gaffo: again, obs does overlay rendering with chromium, could be a conflict there
Crypteemo: @georgehotz Chrome used to crash my whole comp, I switched to Opera and have been fine since
simping4geohot: POST LINK TO PAGE THAT WAS CRASHING PLS
2600: maybe you have an odd number of RAM sticks
Jehhred: Somebody at the other end of your ISP is flicking switches
westonwaldo: Nanoscale Molecular Dynamics is computer software for molecular dynamics simulation, written using the Charm++ parallel programming model. It is noted for its parallel efficiency and is often used to simulate large systems
MrStereoX: @gaffo <3
gaffo: :)
MrclearSky: OBS uses chromium for browserSource
dorkmo: firefox?
mrhdr: gaffo greekJim
granti7: twitch police, hide chat
shoji22: wkwkwk
MrStereoX: Dont fkriking smile at me. give me a heart @gaffo
sandmann00: Lol its a "Feature"
LordDankington: monkaS
westonwaldo: your welcome - https://www.ks.uiuc.edu/Research//namd/
brownyyyylocks: what jus happened
Clevermacia: some gjy earlier was being a dick because I suggested doing something on quantum computing lol
thickbordiga: quantum computing is a hoax
2600: you're a hoax
zelkh9: were you not able to register
brownyyyylocks: is that u god
gaffo: @MrStereoX I have no heart to give
simping4geohot: DONT GIVE UP GEOHOT
esence: not a hoax, according to Vitalik, but might be too expensive to maintain it's quantum state
Eternallightning: go off stream download and come back?
westonwaldo: George I am a medical school professor at Harvard, need access to any websites?
allbrakesnogas: Hi yeah could I please order some rice
simping4geohot: USE FIREFOX
zelkh9: theres a readme with install instructions
MrStereoX: i feel u @gaffo
11plus4thinking: NaM
Clevermacia: i'm pretty sure that's what kodak said about the pixel
zelkh9: for namd
mrhdr: NaM WTF
11plus4thinking: NaM wtf?
porteus: NaM wtf?
zelkh9: it’s pretty straightforward
Eternallightning: @westonwaldo no Kap PogChamp ?
t00big2fl4il: NAMD = Cross Site Script
LordDankington: no im a med school professor
allbrakesnogas: wait this isn't burger king
11plus4thinking: westonwaldo sure Kappa
westonwaldo: big fan of CommaAI
mrhdr: NaM
treestompztv: me too :)
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 subscribed at Tier 2. They've subscribed for 2 months! forgot to renew it
MrStereoX: @westonwaldo Dr. K.2
b0ngwizard420: George, what's in the grocery bags in the back?
Luiserebii: NAMD tutorial icon looks like something from my nightmares
JdPaulBlart: im doctor anthony fauci what questions can i answer about covid 19
11plus4thinking: NaM stop hating on me
mrhdr: dam, NaM spam
rimali: well known hacker known as the '80s'
thickbordiga: I can give you all the piss you need
aj37z: why views drop to 300
allbrakesnogas: I am a pissophile
Lizardan: back PogChamp
zelkh9: the part i wanted you to take away from the namd tutorial was not the namd stuff exactly, just that building stuff
jimmyadaro: Sups bois
esence: Click here to launch the Applet Demo
l1ght5p33d: this looks so old
imrooty: hacking the 80s
jcowley00: @westonwaldo any proof?
zelkh9: vmd is literally t
aj37z: NaM
rustduck: NaM why not
porteus: NaM
Eternallightning: 1.8 Angstrom PogChamp
zelkh9: literally the shit you fucking zoomer
Luiserebii: Is it possible to accomplish these tasks in Haskell
simping4geohot: lmfao
simping4geohot: @zelkh9 savage
garica111: HeyGuys
Clevermacia: why so many haters on quantum computing?
esence: "Search powered by Google"
allbrakesnogas: damn bastards keeping all the piss files for themselves
jimmyadaro: PDB LUL
mashafique: @zelkh9 don't be so triggered bro. drink some water elaChug
simping4geohot: @Luiserebii no, only bash
sockpuppet_user: pymol
cantstopever: Just started watching, what are you trying to accomplish with this project?
simping4geohot: @mashafique zelk is a god gtfo noob
entangledbeing: @cantstopever Everything
jimmyadaro: @cantstopever Hack coronavirus
t00big2fl4il: is Charm++ secure?
mashafique: @simping4geohot you're gonna have to change your name to simping4zelk soon LUL
l1ght5p33d: nicceee
Lizardan: WebGL Kreygasm
THX1342: They take the dinglebop and push it through the Grumbo, where the Fleeb is rubbed against it.
MrStereoX: @westonwaldo i think you will be the only one who understands what George do now
11plus4thinking: salmon15Hmm piss file
mashafique: Everyone drink water and relax elaChug elaFella
simping4geohot: @mashafique m-m-m-maybe you're right
esence: @Lizardan where the webgl at?
zelkh9: bruuuh
zelkh9: no psf no bond information
zelkh9: like what
11plus4thinking: NaM
braininavatt: H rockz!
porteus: NaM
Luiserebii: @cantstopever live gamer language memes
mrhdr: NaM
treestompztv: admHack
xinthegame: https://www.twitch.tv/xinthegame/
allbrakesnogas: Hydrogen is my legal name
11plus4thinking: damn NaM spam
mrhdr: damn NaM spam 💿
smalldiickrick: rip NaM D
sidthescikid: !uptime
sidthescikid: bruh
MrStereoX: Stream crashed like 5 mins ago so.. @sidthescikid
simping4geohot: my grandma told me healing crystals can cure coronavirus is that true?
THX1342: I love figuring out when businesses/projects are just wrappers around Unix programs
11plus4thinking: @xinthegame no one wants to watch you play minecraft i promise you
simping4geohot: ENTROPY
jomkingal: Good night George, good night everyone!
aj37z: becuz its winter
sidthescikid: @simping4geohot okay
vaskogomez87: because movemnt?
braininavatt: boooo tutorials booooo
sidthescikid: why COVID looking like a fruit rollup?
zelkh9: vmd lets you set colors just saying
FancyDawg_: George how are you pulling the Enterz sequences
FancyDawg_: from your repo it says from Bio import Enterz thing
alicyka: The colors is what made the bats so tasty
zelkh9: that was a vacuum sim hotz
FancyDawg_: but I dont see it in your repo
zelkh9: those are just crystal waters
zelkh9: only a few of them
Luiserebii: @sidthescikid bourgeoisie marketing tactic
zelkh9: not a box
westonwaldo: Anyone wants to understand what George is trying to do, here is a great article I was apart of that will help explain it. https://insidebigdata.com/2019/01/21/coding-the-cure-for-cancer/ and https://www.wired.com/insights/2013/06/from-code-to-cure-engineering-genomics/
LordDankington: @georgehotz just put covid-19 into ida pro, stop messing around with this sim stuff
Luiserebii: ^^^
westonwaldo: George if you want funding for what you are doing DM me. This is a really hot research topic for NIH and NSF. Would love to take this to the next level if you have any interest
MrStereoX: Thanx Wesonwaldo !
THX1342: put covid into ghidra it unlocks an easter egg: the cure
LordDankington: @THX1342 now we are getting somewhere
levelz31: what's a good online course to buy for learning javascript?
rimali: what do you have against the 80s man?
MrStereoX: Udemy colt steele @levelz31
rimali: stop this tirade
MurdocLIVE: @levelz31 youtube
TheArc_TV: I mean i think codecademy is free idk how good they are
Lizardan: @levelz31 youtube
Luiserebii: @levelz31 "The C++ Programming Language"
the_benju: @levelz31 the internet
esence: why have you set the temperature to 300*K?
Santiago_LHC: !uptime
zelkh9: that has no water
sidthescikid: @georgehotz Why not 273K?
simping4geohot: IF ONLY YOU USED RUST-BIO FROM THE START
schmxtzz: w3school
costcospizza: true
levelz31: @mrstereox cheers
simping4geohot: we would have the cure already
simping4geohot: if you used rust
costcospizza: theoretically it would work
C0deCane: @levelz31 idk thats a female language Kappa
MrStereoX: westonwaldo: George if you want funding for what you are doing DM mewestonwaldo. This is a really hot research topic for NIH and NSF. Would love to take this to the next level if you have any interest
T3chHS: @georgehotz If you get somewhere (assuming you are aiming at something) how will you know you got there?
Lizardan: rust is doodoo
Clevermacia: why is comma going to take 6-12 months longer than auto pilot to react to stop lights/signs? I got my grey panda brew
AThousandHours: why is rust doodoo Lizardan
imrooty: lol
MurdocLIVE: LOL
THX1342: LUL
TheArc_TV: Hahahahaha
TheArc_TV: LOL
levelz31: @c0decane learning python also 😉
Lizardan: @AThousandHours overhyped, slow copilation, unnecessary syntax complexity
treestompztv: LUL
esence: your kitchen needs more genders in there
chetta: lmao
THX1342: fundraising dinners
jimmyadaro: Eat garlic George
zelkh9: it might not be showing waters because it’s using a cartoon rep, water wont show up as cartoon
FancyDawg_: George can you post a requirements.txt
jimmyadaro: And onions
aj37z: NaM wtf
porteus: NaM wtf
LordDankington: used rust, loved it
westonwaldo: Lol I hear you. You have a gifted mind you should consider taking to this to the next level if you really want to make a difference
sidthescikid: why do we even need a simulation?
jimmyadaro: Eat onions
FancyDawg_: I dont know the library for Bio
Lizardan: Go > Rust
jimmyadaro: Remember to wash your hands
zelkh9: namd is literally state of the art bruhh
braininavatt: GHOTZ ASMR Kreygasm
MrStereoX: i tried @westonwaldo
Eternallightning: LUL
sidthescikid: LUL
kruzustv: social distancing guys pls
Penguino138: lets fold proteins while we stream
simping4geohot: @Lizardan rust is actually surprisingly ergonmic
THX1342: did you simulate the spike glycoprotein yet? that stuck to my head
benchai18: @jimmyadaro wHaTs hE wOrKinG oN?¿
simping4geohot: when you start working w it for a while
costcospizza: true
kruzustv: i love rust omg
esence: @georgehotz play with temperature, change 300*K to 280*K
Penguino138: @georgehotz I think protein folding is so intensive because it has to simulate all 3D spatial translations, rotations, and scales of the protein
zelkh9: it doesn’t work because statistical mechanics bruh
Luiserebii: @Penguino138 is that something from a skittles commercial
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 ChEcK HiS GiThUb hErE'S tHE lInK
jimmyadaro: LUL
jimmyadaro: Sup dude
samthedogg: @fancydawg_ sound like you you need to pip3 install the lib
Eternallightning: @georgehotz Look up the CASP13 competition
sidthescikid: @georgehotz @esence suggested messing with the temperature
crisofilaxx: hydrogen bullsh**
westonwaldo: George, I will fly you out to my lab and we can work on this together. There are a lot of variables you aren't considering and you lack a tremendous amount of resources to actually be successful to achieve what you are trying to do.
aj37z: U sound like Otacon from MGS
OnlyChliches: Might only be able to render known protiens with specific genetic sequences
benchai18: @jimmyadaro tHx broooo. HoW i HaK
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz https://covid-global-hackathon.devpost.com/
culpritgene: If you will first align it to an existing homologous structure and than start simulation - it will kinda work
benchai18: @jimmyadaro chillin man. How’s life
jimmyadaro: Have you seen the covid hackaton? @georgehotz https://covid-global-hackathon.devpost.com/
T3chHS: @georgehotz If you get somewhere (assuming you are aiming at something) how would you know you got there?
benchai18: No one has ever said “Ohhh that’s a nice protein”
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Same
esence: @benchai18 every day when I pile up my scoops
360Plato: @jimmyadaro another ctf...
THX1342: westonwaldo what IS he trying to do other than learn? LUL
THX1342: I don't know yet
zelkh9: ubq worked because the residue names matched the residue names in the force field
benchai18: @esence U lift?
esence: @benchai18 HOW COULD YOU TELL
jimmyadaro: @360Plato idk man, looks good to me
Luiserebii: is this legal
jimmyadaro: Have you seen the covid hackaton? @georgehotz https://covid-global-hackathon.devpost.com/
culpritgene: man, TER is just another (last) atom
MrMcaustin1: @jimmyadaro stop spamming the same link
culpritgene: it should have something in the 4th column
t00big2fl4il: I think you may have been missing the necessary enabled Java Applets for NAMD to work properly
MrStereoX: westonwaldo: George, I will fly you out to my lab and we can work on this together. There are a lot of variables you aren't considering and you lack a tremendous amount of resources to actually be successful to achieve what you are trying to do.
sidthescikid: Building blocks of proteins
culpritgene: yes, look at the original pbd file
emceeMC2: @georgehotz are you dedicating your computer to folding@home when you’re not streaming?
zelkh9: ubq worked because the residue names matched the residue names in the force field
efiggs: Have you found the cure yet?!?!
TheArc_TV: Actg right
simping4geohot: GROSS
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Aren't you helping people with this? lmao
pjayys77: disgusting
benchai18: Jesus you’re so negative
THX1342: this channel is about profiting off the human tragedy. it's disgusting, really
zelkh9: but yeah don’t read the tutorials LUL
benchai18: George is my fav Debbie Downer
jimmyadaro: Agreed
simping4geohot: NO YOU DO IT FOR THE CLOUT BABY
Lizardan: this channel is about profiting off the human tragedy. it's disgusting, really
T3chHS: Don't think that both can happen toghether
jimmyadaro: FOR THE LULZ LUL
esence: but that's what you are doing rn, IT'S DISGUSTING
sidthescikid: @jimmyadaro Nope. Just for honors and because he's bored and just wants to hack something
benchai18: Thanks Plato
jimmyadaro: @sidthescikid Sure lmao
murgmasallam: Whats the page link from where you downloaded the protein structure?
bassxzero: Sound logic
sidthescikid: @esence u have the whole copy pasta?
georgehotz: https://zhanglab.ccmb.med.umich.edu/C-I-TASSER/2019-nCov/
Eternallightning: usually the hydrogen on carbons are missing
MrStereoX: Have you ever worked with kaspersky ? @georgehotz
FancyDawg_: Can you post the Bio library for Entrez
culpritgene: the column which looks like C/C1/O is the column with atom types. You have a message saying that your atom type for TER is not specificed.
FancyDawg_: I cant seem to find the pip install
THX1342: I don't see it
Nussinov: do you think twitch chatters have a Jupiter notebook for copy pastas
BeeFigTree: protein look like long confetti
benchai18: Or cum
THX1342: does it link together to other envelop proteins?
jimmyadaro: @Nussinov We do!
o______________________k: squadR Hey DUD I want my coronara1n jailbreak DUD NOW DUD squadR squadR
THX1342: NotLikeThis
zelkh9: vmd has all those options and more
THX1342: can you show the spike glycoprotein george?
pedrovictortech: k-mersssss
22helper: whats George doing?
efiggs: Why don’t you talk about comma ai
THX1342: oooohh that's nice.. that visual makes more sense
jimmyadaro: Yeah George, show us your spike glycoprotein, you lil bastard LUL
esence: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
simping4geohot: omg!!! i just found this epic hack that gave me all the bitcorns!!!! just ran this in a node repl!!!! (f => f(f))(async f => f(f) && f(f));
sidthescikid: @efiggs he can but this is probably more important
Luiserebii: @georgehotz i think u should do this in scratch it always seems to work for me
sidthescikid: the world is in crisis and this guy pretends to "REVRSE ENGINEER CORONA VIRUS" and profit from it.. this is really disgusting
samthedogg: @fancydawg_ python3 -m pip install bio2bel_entrez
MrMcaustin1: @sidthescikid @esence stop
jimmyadaro: @sidthescikid Are you serious?
o______________________k: squadBrug squadBrug squadBrug squadBrug squadBrug squadBrug squadBrug
eeXecute: bitcorns PogChamp
samthedogg: took me 3 seconds to Google ffs
latenightbj: good morning
o______________________k: true DUD squadR
THX1342: are the colors supposed to mean anything?
Nussinov: in rainbow view I dont think the color means anything
stillgeting: LUL
Eternallightning: Its convention to gradient from N -> C terminus with the color @georgehotz
MrStereoX: NotLikeThis
T3chHS: @georgehotz If you get somewhere (assuming you are aiming at something) how will you know you got there?
Luiserebii: @simping4geohot that formatted my hard drive wtf
efiggs: I don’t understand what he is even doing
zennydmt: did you take operating systems at CMU?
MrStereoX: @T3chHS Good one
THX1342: like 5' and 3' ?
benchai18: Wtf ? Who’s talking shit about “profiting iTs dIsGuStInG”
THX1342: in RNA
o______________________k: squadPH
aj37z: yeah why didn you
emceeMC2: can u hak my frends facebook plz
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Dickheads, obviously
mikenachos: every vertex is a c
thickbordiga: all the lines are C
Eternallightning: C refers to carboxylic acid the COOH
t00big2fl4il: does it bond to C
sidthescikid: @jimmyadaro no there was a stream where someone said that and turned into an inside joke
prakyath_kantharaju: C is implied as vertex
simping4geohot: CHUG CHUG CHUG CHUG
jimmyadaro: @sidthescikid Oh okay
o______________________k: @jimmyadaro ay I'm a dick head too DUD squadR squadR
thickbordiga: DansGame moldy coffee
aj37z: didnt you just drink redbull?
efiggs: What’s a vertex?
eeXecute: Geo grabbing the OXY
prakyath_kantharaju: jeez Redbull and coffee
ahahahaitslit: nothing like some coffee and redbull late at night
mikenachos: efiggs where two edges meet
MrStereoX: @MrMcaustin1 did you ban the harvrad dr ?
benchai18: Lol
aj37z: rip heart
dprophecyguy: Hi does any body know what ice tea @georgehotz keeps drinking ?
MrMcaustin1: i didn't ban anyone
Taygetea: get on voice with someone who knows what they're doing and slow your ass down, for fuck's sake man
efiggs: @mikenachos Thank you
benchai18: Peace out Westeros Waldo
MrStereoX: Oh lol
MrMcaustin1: just a simple timeout
adorablejaay: @dprophecyguy Bofa
benchai18: BofA deez nuts?
sidthescikid: @westonwaldo What org do you work for?
adorablejaay: nathanPepe
ClintBushton: 13 second hand wash
simping4geohot: nice hardwood floors
Taygetea: george didn't see the flight offer
THX1342: damn... I was getting into this DNA/biotech world a few months back and dropped it to focus on becoming a 1337 h4x0r.. now geo comes out of the woods with this shit and I am questioning my life choices...
dprophecyguy: @adorablejaay Thanks a lot
jimmyadaro: Did you wash your hands @georgehotz ? LUL
gaocaandra: where is the corona.ipynb file in the repo
MrStereoX: kafeeeWave kafeeeWave kafeeeWave kafeeeWave
theonlymonkas: LUL
aj37z: instant coffee
thickbordiga: urine is sterile you don't need to wash your hands after you piss
jimmyadaro: Have you ate some garlic already? mf
gaocaandra: i dont use jupyter
thecoder15: "yeah were rich, lets make new coffee" ~ George Hotz
ahahahaitslit: adderall shot
TheArc_TV: “Urine is sterile” LUL
efiggs: I wish I could truly understand what he’s doing
pjayys77: !uptime
jimmyadaro: LUL
C0deCane: wash hands before piss dont get your dick dirty chat
jimmyadaro: @efiggs Making coffee
adorablejaay: @o______________________k Intro done yet?
o______________________k: oh wow hey chat dont mind me. just going to lay Down here mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper
Luiserebii: does this channel also do javascript tutorials
esence: it's a bit too late for a coffee
thickbordiga: george did you wash the inside of your dick out after you pissed?
aj37z: @Luiserebii yes
efiggs: No I mean like with the bioinformatics stuff
o______________________k: @adorablejaay not yet. DUD mizkifSit
sidthescikid: @Luiserebii python
jimmyadaro: Did you wash your hands @georgehotz ? LUL
TheArc_TV: I bleach my insides after I breath
Taygetea: george didn't see the flight offer, also he neds to slow down
aj37z: i shorted amazon
mohammed1996mizab: yo do you have gf?
jimmyadaro: I love ya
simping4geohot: lmfao
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
braininavatt: LUL
sidthescikid: DansGame
thickbordiga: java yes javascript no
Incurs0: LUL
o______________________k: LUL
birkett0011: LUL
MrStereoX: lul
Clevermacia: ooo there's the cocky george I know lol
ImJ4Gu4R: lol
braininavatt: permaban pls Kappa
K177: i can't wait for the helloworld tutorial
Waldoqq: we only do Python 2 here
zennydmt: did u take 15-400 at CMU?
THX1342: No, but he does do HTML programming tutorials
benchai18: For 6 nights straight now I was sure we were reverse engineering Mexican beer.
K177: woahhh
ImJ4Gu4R: do it lol
l1ght5p33d: hard to even tell these days
fancyslimshady: just watched a Nerf gun ad to get to your stream
sidthescikid: PogChamp OMG
jimmyadaro: LUL
rasenjon: is javascript the scripted version of java? :o
pjayys77: * how .d..o. you like ..C+....... nvm
K177: can you teach me about pythons memory management? :)
Santiago_LHC: MAGIC
FusRoDead: today we're going to show you how to set up your jupyter environment.
aj37z: java POGGERS
Incurs0: im learning PogChamp
Lizardan: Python rules the world
o______________________k: mizkifGun2 stop it NOW coder @georgehotz mizkifGun mizkifGun2 mizkifGun mizkifGun2 mizkifGun mizkifGun2
MrStereoX: poggggggggggersssssw we learning
sidthescikid: PogChamp Look at the efficiency!
braininavatt: wow PogChamp
crisofilaxx: lmfao
Musashhhi: space force making moves today
cantstopever: Where can I learn some JavaScript? I heard it’s a rly rly gud language
jimmyadaro: @Lizardan C does lmao
thecoder15: lol
K177: HYPERS
Eternallightning: Pythonic PogChamp
esence: BUT MUH SPEED
11plus4thinking: :)
Lizardan: C sucks .. TRUE
ImJ4Gu4R: ai ai chip
22helper: lol
K177: an array :)
Santiago_LHC: EDUCATIONAL
braininavatt: this is what I was looking for PogChamp
L0ader: UNSUBSCRIBE
MrMcaustin1: Kappa
thickbordiga: FeelsGoodMan // BUBBY SORT
L0ader: lul
Clevermacia: reminds me of the time someone suggested using a raspberry pi with openpilot. George lost his shit lol
jimmyadaro: ResidentSleeper
esence: RADIX SORT PLS
benchai18: Joey Diaz: “if 1=1: FUCK YOUR MOTHER “
K177: :) woah
OnlyChliches: The patronizing tone is nice.
adotout1: tfw you have a c program open on a second monitor....i feel attacked
o______________________k: mizkifV mizkifV mizkifV mizkifV
Taygetea: @Clevermacia why is that a bad idea
MrStereoX: im actually dieing
latenightbj: does bubble sort work with bubble tea ?
K177: yeah college is a scam :)
sidthescikid: LUL
Santiago_LHC: TUTORIAL TIME
K177: thanks for confirming that george :)
aar0npham: oh my good
jimmyadaro: ' OR 1=1
simping4geohot: AND THAT'S WHY WE USE RUST GEOHOT CUZ ITS EVEN BETTER
aj37z: :)
simping4geohot: (1..5).filter(|x| x % 2 == 0).map(|x| x*3).collect()
K177: D:
efiggs: See he’s making a joke rn but I can’t understand a thing...
luigifrcruz: lmfao
THX1342: :)
zwisch: LUL
K177: too far D:
K177: i like to count from 1 :(
rstk1: LUL
pjayys77: this will teach you to raise your hand in class to ask questions .. rip
braininavatt: 84! PogChamp
o______________________k: mizkifCry this beautiful mizkifCry mizkifCry mizkifCry mizkifCry
Waldoqq: IM LEARNING SO MUCH PogChamp
thickbordiga: mizkifSat
MurdocLIVE: 'stooopid' LUL
davidnzl: LUL
keith282: Woah george you're a really good teacher
jimmyadaro: @efiggs Are you mentally challenged?
K177: cmonBruh
K177: cmonBruh stop
dr_set: LUL
Clevermacia: yeah sometimes I wonder if George is a high functioning autistic
Lizardan: O^2 :)
360Plato: stopit
slimpimp007: 1001
adotout1: O OF N SQUARED
Santiago_LHC: He is like the Mr Rodgers of programming
Eternallightning: true ? !false : !true
imrooty: hahahah
zennydmt: O of n squared
T3chHS: O of N squared!
birkett0011: ON^2
keith282: O of N squared!
braininavatt: CoolStoryBob
sidthescikid: "O of n^2"
zennydmt: thanks daddy
ICAntF331MyFAce: 📝 cirISee
alwayxtoxic: O(n(log(n))
braininavatt: im learning so much rn
dingus74: LOL
K177: wait rly?
o______________________k: mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper mizkifSleeper
aar0npham: im hurting
simping4geohot: o of n squareddddddddd
MrStereoX: "HOW I GOT INTO GOOGLE"
bcrscahh198987: O of up george's butt
Lizardan: D:
Taygetea: @Clevermacia adhd is closer
Incurs0: LUL
THX1342: LUL
aar0npham: how to google
MrMcaustin1: fuckl
pjayys77: Oh.. so you thought you had a good question.. LUL LUL
aj37z: D:
simping4geohot: O OF N SQUARED!!!!!!!!!!!
yrpsa: This is great
culpritgene: now all together: 'R is stupid!'
esence: HEY BRO, DO YOU WANT A JOB AT GOOGLE?
equipollent_z: widdSmart
L0ader: Too real
braininavatt: CAN I???? PogChamp
thickbordiga: even the N word?
K177: computers really only had i and j's? :( oh nyo
Penguino138: This is the greatest tutorial on the world wide web
dingus74: jackoo1Weird
efiggs: No
PusiaPaker: this is amazing
zennydmt: dadda
l1ght5p33d: no
kruzustv: George this is the best intro for ur udemy course @georgehotz
guinness84: im learning so much
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
o______________________k: mizkifPout
jimmyadaro: epan aiken ook wenn ich spielen aufhoren hocchievehn!!!!!
optimizely: omg
eeXecute: 101 class PogChamp
Clevermacia: @Taygetea yeah or like asbergers
360Plato: WutFace
l1ght5p33d: pleas stop
l1ght5p33d: stahpp
pjayys77: bury all the fledgling programmers , I love it
aar0npham: please stop
braininavatt: CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob
aar0npham: ffs
aj37z: too much learning
mohammed1996mizab: i kind like it
ICAntF331MyFAce: 📝 cirISee you getting all this chat?
dingus74: Bruh
optimizely: george your awesome man
fancyslimshady: @georgehotz Your coffee machine from Costco is loud
OnlyChliches: this is my favorite part.
MrStereoX: i love the teacher VOICE
mokmuu: this will be the best clip ever
benchai18: receiver = “my ass”; doit(a)  doit(fuck)
brownyyyylocks: this tutorial sux
Ayyyy420Lmao: educational stream 4Head 4Head 4Head
braininavatt: shut up chat, im learning
K177: i accidently created a atomic bomb :( thanks george
kruzustv: i am dying of hyperpythonia
Taygetea: @Clevermacia they're similar, but the adhd is why he can't sit and read a tutorial which is so damn frustrating
simping4geohot: O OF N SQUARED
efiggs: This community is full of freaks... I just came here to learn about bioinformatics
crisofilaxx: nooooo
pedrovictortech: YAAA! Learn that chat
Clevermacia: like some poor high school kid just asked a question and hes' totally making him feel like he should kill themselves
thecoder15: LOL
kruzustv: so much... oython
crisofilaxx: you dont have to
mikenachos: you can do it in one line LUL
MrMcaustin1: gg
Incurs0: omg where can I buy your courses online PogChamp
equipollent_z: are we sorting Powerpuff girls?
Lizardan: D:
evnomics: PogChamp
zwisch: someone clip this
birkett0011: POG
L0ader: Pog
braininavatt: WOW elloWOW
sidthescikid: PogChamp Clap
esence: he's pretending, but that's what's happening in CS50 class
pjayys77: but.. he's actually teaching something
thickbordiga: PogChamp WHAT THE FUCK
evnomics: He's a fucking savage
tarunaditya: stonks
o______________________k: I enjoyed my stay mizkifSleepy mizkifSleepy mizkifSleepy mizkifSleepy mizkifSleepy
adorablejaay: @georgehotz Where can i find the udemy course nathanPepe
benchai18: Damn even when he’s bullshitting and joking I can’t understand what he’s saying
aj37z: CS degree speedrun @georgehotz
Jehhred: Low key I'm learning so much right now
dingus74: LOL
jimmyadaro: Look at my cool regex: /^[\p\p\p]+$/gm
Snobbysteven: wait you lost me at i .... start over please.
t00big2fl4il: I just logged in this stream is better than I heard
Penguino138: SeriousSloth SeriousSloth
crisofilaxx: in python you can do !!!!!! a, b = b,a
prakyath_kantharaju: PogChamp PogChamp SeemsGood SeemsGood
roreax6: Beautiful.
MurdocLIVE: LOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOL
THX1342: when are the HTML programming tutorials?
L0ader: Poggers
T3chHS: Fuck yeah
aar0npham: oh my god
braininavatt: BEST TUTORIAL EVER
joivan: LMAO
keith282: Thank you so much George!
kruzustv: someone clip it
Vagorge: actually good @georgehotz
l1ght5p33d: why
birkett0011: I AM LEARNIRNIGNIGN
simping4geohot: GEOHOT LOOK HOW MUCH BETTER RUST IS u cant even tell me this isnt better than python geohot: (1..5).filter(|x| x % 2 == 0).map(|x| x*3).collect()
MrStereoX: lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP lirikCLAP
mokmuu: CLIP THAT SHIT
sidthescikid: PogChamp Clap YES
imrooty: LMAO
heelyway: lmao
dprophecyguy: hell ywH
lolzmaster99: 5/7
aar0npham: fml
slimpimp007: yess King
o______________________k: yes master mizkifPainschamp mizkifPainschamp mizkifPainschamp mizkifPainschamp
rstk1: LUL
braininavatt: THIS IS CONTENT
Creamy_Goodness_: WHAT US PRO GRAM
happypuppppy: you went too fast slow down BibleThump
thecoder15: NOOB EAZZZIE P1THON TUT00RIALS YOOO
Incurs0: Clap
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp Clap
ClintBushton: hooray!
K177: 'python is not recognized as an internal or external command @georgehotz help me :(
fancyslimshady: your coffee is ready
jimmyadaro: regex /^[\p\p\p]+$/gm
Penguino138: I'm ready to build a self driving car now thanks @georgehotz
bcrscahh198987: Program a heap data structure in 20 minutes plz
aar0npham: thats makes me die
CreeepingDeath: SeemsGood
guinness84: another plz
benchai18: God damn chat just went insane
efiggs: No
zennydmt: dadda it was too fast
thickbordiga: mizkifSat NOW DO JAVA
aar0npham: inside out
asanti20: lmaooo
brownyyyylocks: im never asking again
Nussinov: noob python tutorials is the best name
ez_j21: Lmao
Landepbs: now you dont have anything left to show for next week
pedrovictortech: I am so glad this is going to youtube later
pjayys77: its funny cuz some thought it was funny, but definitely ppl in here who learned something lol
Eternallightning: GUYS I CAN MAKE A STARTUP UP NOW I KNOW PYTHON PogChamp GUYS I CAN MAKE A STARTUP UP NOW I KNOW PYTHON PogChamp GUYS I CAN MAKE A STARTUP UP NOW I KNOW PYTHON PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: Sarcastic teaching is actually educational
doctorgenus: that was actually pretty good, better than techlead stuff
TheArc_TV: reversed(list) Kappa
Bloodswordz88: Hail Brethren HahaThisisfine HahaThisisfine HahaThisisfine HahaPoint HahaPoint
efiggs: Lame
auqsto: LUL
o______________________k: squad200 squad200 squad200 squad200 squad200
maxjowett: coffee at 10pm
hastingspb: @georgehotz Can you do it for rust next??
maxjowett: beast
roreax6: Sounded condescending just like my highschool programming teacher.
bcrscahh198987: techlead is waaay better
latenightbj: W8 .....did he get more groceries ???
esence: @Eternallightning GOOGLE IS HIRING
MrMcaustin1: taught me more than a whole term of university did where I paid $15k a term
FusRoDead: Why did you delete the corona code for sorting?
Eternallightning: GUYS I CAN MAKE A STARTUP NOW I KNOW PYTHON PogChamp GUYS I CAN MAKE A STARTUP NOW I KNOW PYTHON PogChamp GUYS I CAN MAKE A STARTUP NOW I KNOW PYTHON PogChamp
Mint2bSpiced: A tale of two tails: why are terminal residues of proteins exposed? Link here: https://doi.org/10.1093/bioinformatics/btl318
THX1342: OMG I am a growth hacker now! I learned PYTHON
t00big2fl4il: Thanks for the micro tutorial that was sweet
icekrieg: is lua actually stupid I couldn't tell if you were being sarcastic or not
fancyslimshady: @georgehotz you got that coffee machine from costco
T3chHS: LET'S ALL START A START UP TOGEHTER
theonlymonkas: nice
dprophecyguy: I can be a growth Hacker now
thickbordiga: mizkifSat BUT MY HOMEWORK IS IN JAVA???/ @georgehotz
samthedogg: some people in here don't even in a how to pip install lol
K177: LULW not false
zennydmt: did u take operating systems at CMU?
Clevermacia: @Taygetea yeah when he acts like this really turns me off, like we get it bro you're. a genius but he tries to be little people and make them feel stupid just for asking questions
Penguino138: @georgehotz Can I use a for loop to build a Tesla?
treestompztv: Guys I took an IQ test and scored a perfect 100 :)
dprophecyguy: I can apply to google now
ahahahaitslit: thanks george, i finally got into FANG
dprophecyguy: I can do leetcode now
jimmyadaro: Cómo estas me llamo de biblioteques mucho gracia en mi por amor es epan aiken ook wenn ich spielen aufhoren hocchievehn!!!!!
zennydmt: who was your favorite professor at CMu
efiggs: Not funny
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Do binary search next PogChamp LUL
benchai18: He’s lost his shit
bcrscahh198987: how about reversing a palindrome? LUL
guinness84: is ur bubble sort implementation open sourced
THX1342: georgehotz how many years ago did you stop reading HN?
sidthescikid: @georgehotz when u starting your farm seminars?
andybergon: nit: You can swap with a,b=b,a
Taygetea: i mostly wish he would listen to the people who know what they're talking about here and maybe get on voice chat or something
Incurs0: LUL
K177: ok thx :)
hastingspb: does bubble sort work in C or no??
bcrscahh198987: 1 dollar per sort
aar0npham: hahaha
Ayyyy420Lmao: teach us zip() and itertools !!!
L0ader: 100 bits for the license LUL
braininavatt: PogChamp
birkett0011: FUC
Incurs0: dammit
K177: damn :(
o______________________k: mizkifBat how about no mizkifBat mizkifBat mizkifBat mizkifBat
Lizardan: D:
jimmyadaro: Thanks bruh LUL
Br4nnon: D:
iIyaRPV: PogChamp
Waldoqq: PogChamp
aar0npham: fuck u all
pjayys77: but what about gifters, we're ppl too
sidthescikid: :) Privilege
Eternallightning: wait i free Pog ?
brownyyyylocks: winning
pwnbase: BibleThump
esence: TY BASED GEROGIE
braininavatt: I CAN USE IT LOSERS
K177: any gifters? TriHard any gifters? TriHard any gifters? TriHard any gifters? TriHard any gifters? TriHard any gifters? TriHard any gifters? TriHard
Ayyyy420Lmao: teach us zip() and itertools !!
maxjowett: when will you be releasing the hhkb geohot edition?
Penguino138: @georgehotz How much faster is Python than C++?
doctorgenus: is bubble sort the cure to coronavirus?
westonwaldo: TY GEORGE!
L0ader: One of the subs leak it
bcrscahh198987: is the royalty cost O(n^2) for bubble sort?
MrMcaustin1: cant you bubble sort the coronavirus
jmv_chin: im losing brain cells
zennydmt: can u draw little bubbles on the screen so my kids have an illustration
syns0r: Boba Sort?
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 11 in the channel!
bloodstrive: can u teach bubble sort in HTML?
T3chHS: does the variable has to be named t ??
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to equipollent_z!
thecoder15: can you write lead sort
dprophecyguy: Can you implement bubble tea sort ?
jimmyadaro: @Penguino138 Like… 2.
latenightbj: what are the curly ribbons
K177: D:
t00big2fl4il: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k4RRi_ntQc8
Incurs0: LUL
OnlyChliches: random troll comment
prakyath_kantharaju: he is chewing
jimmyadaro: OH NO
l1ght5p33d: assembly now
birkett0011: !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1
ImJ4Gu4R: Thats pretty amazing. we can get subscriber list from twitch API?
Nussinov: hot
thebiggaeboi: what is ur keybrd
Penguino138: @jimmyadaro dope thanks lol
lolzmaster99: Why is protein folding NP-Hard?
mohammed1996mizab: DansGame
jimmyadaro: NO NO NO NO
K177: i haven't :)
K177: no :)
jimmyadaro: Cómo estas me llamo de biblioteques mucho gracia en mi por amor es epan aiken ook wenn ich spielen aufhoren hocchievehn!!!!!
aar0npham: aar0npham is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 1 in the channel!
aar0npham: aar0npham gifted a Tier 1 sub to Penguino138!
simping4geohot: GEOHOT AUDIT THE AUGUR CONTRACTS AGAIN
optimizely: you promised you won't chew ice
zennydmt: draw bubbles on the screen I need a picture since I'm slow
bcrscahh198987: How much does it cost to sort per n?
braininavatt: GHOTZ ASMR BEST FOOD ASMR Kreygasm Kreygasm
MrMcaustin1: haha
sidthescikid: PogChamp
bloodstrive: how can i hack nasa with html? @georgehotz
Thotshotgg: I will sub when you cure COVID-19
equipollent_z: :o
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
doctorgenus: what's a hype train?
happypuppppy: any of the subs want to sell me bubble sort in underground market for good price?
L0ader: PogChamp more tutorials PogChamp
PusiaPaker: do a tutorial on basic next
sidthescikid: I'm getting my card
westonwaldo: TUTORIAL!!!!
Br4nnon: hello world tutorial pl0x
dprophecyguy: I am very poor @georgehotz
nogunumo: Python or c++ ? Which one should I learn ?
Incurs0: Scam train PogChamp
fancyslimshady: You got that coffee machine from Costco
22helper: does George do tik tok?
ahahahaitslit: Please teach html
treestompztv: PogChamp
t00big2fl4il: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k4RRi_ntQc8
bcrscahh198987: You should learn C++
gaocaandra: do you really want us to pay a corporation
l1ght5p33d: rant!
kuj0oo: deff works in c++
sidthescikid: @nogunumo hide him, hes gonna roast you
jimmyadaro: @happypuppppy Sure, write me a dm
gaocaandra: thats not the spirit
Clevermacia: go on your raspberry pi rant for openpilot
Ayyyy420Lmao: woah
o______________________k: mizkifSip
t00big2fl4il: sick bubble sort tutorial
sidthescikid: PogChamp
dprophecyguy: Guys these Tutorials are a Scam !!
iIyaRPV: PogChamp
bcrscahh198987: Do hello world in brainfuck
zennydmt: can you type 1+1
braininavatt: is rust good for something ever?
K177: damn, didn't even need to implement std io
360Plato: Ill dox the next sub
K177: just like that
nogunumo: Why c++
OnlyChliches: I can do rust.
Br4nnon: PogChamp im ready for facebook
pedrovictortech: What is wrong with rust?
zennydmt: what is 1+1?
simping4geohot: println!("hello world!");
jimmyadaro: Brainfuck is fucked up
pwnbase: i learned to code from Durga software solutions
luigifrcruz: now do it in python 3
thecoder15: you know @georgehotz is getting tired when he starts ranting and raving
westonwaldo: George I was reading online that Elon Musk made you a deal that if you developed software for him he would pay you $12M but lose $1M a month if delayed. Is it true?
benchai18: U missed a TAB
Clevermacia: lol shit is it really real
theonlymonkas: PogChamp
roreax6: roreax6 subscribed at Tier 1.
MrMcaustin1: HYPETRAIN BITCHES
Incurs0: Scam train PogChamp
Clevermacia: I remember you drilled that guy into the flooor
braininavatt: HYPE TREAAAAAAAAIN
equipollent_z: hello world in Learn you a Haskell is chapter 9 lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: scamtrain PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
theonlymonkas: scam train!
braininavatt: PogChamp
benchai18: @westonwaldo yes that is true
jimmyadaro: YEAAAH THE BIG BITCHES TRAIN LUL GET HYPE
mikenachos: LUL
sidthescikid: HYPPPEEE TRAININNNN!!!
braininavatt: CHOOOOOOOO
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: tutorial.comma.ai PogChamp
mohammed1996mizab: Pog
jimmyadaro: SCAM TRAIN
braininavatt: HYPEEEEEEEEEE
jimmyadaro: HELL YEAH
jimmyadaro: Cómo estas me llamo de biblioteques mucho gracia en mi por amor es epan aiken ook wenn ich spielen aufhoren hocchievehn!!!!!
t00big2fl4il: Legit bubble sort https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k4RRi_ntQc8
braininavatt: TRAIIIIIIIIIINNN
c1tr0n75: cheer50
fancyslimshady: @georgehotz whats your favourite video game of the last year
jimmyadaro: traaainnnn
K177: Kappa
sidthescikid: HYPE TRAINNNN
doctorgenus: WHAT IS A HYPE TRAIN?!!!!!
benchai18: @westonwaldo I swear. That rly is tryw
jimmyadaro: suck my TRAIN PIPES
allbrakesnogas: choo choo mofos
dprophecyguy: Yes Hype Train
benchai18: True*
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp PogChamp <3
jimmyadaro: @doctorgenus SOMETHING COOL JUST DO IT
Ayyyy420Lmao: itertools tutorial!!!
Creamy_Goodness_: HELP. AM I BOT?
adotout1: hoiype
I2btw: when you take out the bags?
jimmyadaro: Like da-da-da-daaanceeeeee
lolzmaster99: what time are you going to bed
Br4nnon: tea
yungtoad1: hey george my credit card got stolen otherwise i would get the hype train goin
L0ader: >35 minutes in "things have started going downhill" LUL
Penguino138: never too late for coffee
westonwaldo: GEorge is Elon Musk 2.0!!!
Clevermacia: can you go on joe rogans podcast and debate with elon musk
birkett0011: HYPEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
jimmyadaro: NotLikeThis
simping4geohot: geohot lets hack some smart contracts
allbrakesnogas: chugga chugga bithces
AnAnonymousCheerer: Anon100
aar0npham: did i get timeout
aj37z: lol u just made it
pjayys77: pjayys77 is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
birkett0011: HYPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPEEEEEEEEEEEEE
pjayys77: pjayys77 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 360Plato!
pjayys77: pjayys77 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Roundlay!
pjayys77: pjayys77 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 4zimut!
pjayys77: pjayys77 gifted a Tier 1 sub to death_gadget!
pjayys77: pjayys77 gifted a Tier 1 sub to murkythunder!
sidthescikid: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1
simping4geohot: the bioinformatics nerds all left because they lost faith in you
jimmyadaro: HYPE TRAIN
treestompztv: PogChamp
westonwaldo: COMMA.AI > TESLA!!!!
happypuppppy: PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Level 2
jimmyadaro: YEAAAAAH
westonwaldo: HYPEE TRAIN
nogunumo: I’m learning c++ now
Clevermacia: stick it to him. 12 million to improve your autopilot, yeah fk you elon i'll make my own
aj37z: i got sub PogChamp
MrStereoX: @pjayys77 POGGERS
equipollent_z: cheskaVR
MrMcaustin1: hypetrain georgehotz
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Musashhhi: HYPE TRAIN
vruthlessv: oi
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp OhMyDog OhMyDog
braininavatt: HYYYYYYYYYYYYYYPE PogChamp PogChamp
doctorgenus: oohhh that's a hype train
treestompztv: CHOOOO CHOOOO
thediamnd: PogChamp PogChamp
Lizardan: gimme sub GivePLZ gimme sub GivePLZ gimme sub GivePLZ
jimmyadaro: SO HYPEEEEEDDDDD
360Plato: @pjayys77 Thanks for the gift sub!
doctorgenus: it's a twitch thing
Ayyyy420Lmao: woah credit stolen credit cards gang is here PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
ehisoka: :o
doctorgenus: lol
sidthescikid: CHOOOO CHOOOOOO
birkett0011: HYPPPPEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
OnlyChliches: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: CHOO CHOOOO MF
westonwaldo: GEORGE > ELON
kruzustv: "IndentationError: unexpected indent"
esence: HYPE, NEW TUTORIAL PLS
rstk1: PogChamp
braininavatt: kruzustv F
jimmyadaro: NEW TUTORIAL COME ON
ankitc: CHOOOOOO
doctorgenus: i guess george makes money from hype trains
I2btw: this rly work gep on DNA sycence?
Clevermacia: like everyone worships elon and here george is kicking his ass from his garage
birkett0011: CHOOOOO CHOOOOOOOO BOYYYYYYYYSSSSSSSSS
aj37z: now do merge sort
jimmyadaro: CSS TUTORIAL MF
Penguino138: CHUGGA CHUGGA CHOO CHOO
OnlyChliches: LUL
guinness84: selection sort next choo choo
jimmyadaro: SCSS TUTORIAL
pjayys77: @georgehotz jokes aside I do appreciate your curiosity about things
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Can you jailbreak a Linked List
Musashhhi: lvl 3 let's get it
eeXecute: eeXecute is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
eeXecute: eeXecute gifted a Tier 1 sub to eyesonlyug!
eeXecute: eeXecute gifted a Tier 1 sub to Jehhred!
eeXecute: eeXecute gifted a Tier 1 sub to tornpaperyoyos!
eeXecute: eeXecute gifted a Tier 1 sub to nozpheratu!
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp <3 <3
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL 3 PogChamp PogChamp
eeXecute: eeXecute gifted a Tier 1 sub to keith282!
braininavatt: george is really failing in the whole "dont touch your face" thing Kappa
happypuppppy: PogChamp
MrMcaustin1: poggers
benchai18: Wtf is going on here
luigifrcruz: java tutorial
jimmyadaro: OOOOOH DAAAAMNNNNNN
thediamnd: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
keith282: thank you for the sub bby
thickbordiga: dodged PogChamp
theonlymonkas: choooo choooo
Ayyyy420Lmao: woah credit stolen credit cards gang is here PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
westonwaldo: HYPEEE TRAINNN
Musashhhi: he's missing all the hype
benchai18: I’m too broke for this shit
asanti20: How to get a Girlfriend with Python
allbrakesnogas: DAMN THIS IS A LONG TRAIN B===D
treestompztv: PogChamp CHOOO CHOOO
aj37z: dodged PogCHamp
pjayys77: yeayUh
sidthescikid: Where's the new tutorial at? I wanna learn hello world!
braininavatt: LEVEL 3
Penguino138: TRAIN KEPT A ROLLIN ALL NIGHT LONG
rstk1: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
theonlymonkas: george
birkett0011: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
I2btw: XML is a misstake
pedrovictortech: burh
braininavatt: PogChamp
benchai18: I’m the unemployable reverse engineer
theonlymonkas: LEVEL 3!
jimmyadaro: UNIX'S "ECHO" TUTORIAL
vruthlessv: wjer
jimmyadaro: COME ON!!!
MrMcaustin1: georgehotz you got a hype train
mikenachos: met is the starting codon for open reading frames
gaocaandra: go on
fancyslimshady: @georgehotz My software dev program in college is making us take COBOL , I hate it ..
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL 4 PogChamp PogChamp
sidthescikid: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1
thediamnd: level 4 PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 12 in the channel!
dprophecyguy: @eeXecute Can i get one subscription ?
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to logi6000!
MrStereoX: This chat is Poping right now LUL
aj37z: hes too focused
jimmyadaro: NEW TUTORIAL
birkett0011: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChampPogChamp
thickbordiga: PogChamp WOW
Musashhhi: TUTORIAL TIME
Ayyyy420Lmao: PogChamp PogChamp 8=========D PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
K177: PogChamp wtf
kruzustv: print("console.log(echo("Hello"World)");
Lizardan: gimme sub GivePLZ gimme sub GivePLZ
westonwaldo: GEORGE HOTZ > ELON MUSK!!!!
pedrovictortech: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jimmyadaro: TUTORIAL TIME MF
roreax6: roreax6 is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Br4nnon!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to dr_set!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to raystriker98!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to devm0d!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Juankinator!
Br4nnon: havent coded in a week monkaS
architectzs: What is jupyter>
happypuppppy: PogChamp
Jehhred: @eeXecute Thanks for the gift sub!
Br4nnon: Oh sht
birkett0011: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
K177: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Ayyyy420Lmao: woah credit stolen credit cards gang is here PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
braininavatt: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Clevermacia: yo gift me a sub
K177: PogChamp hype
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
Br4nnon: @roreax6 Thanks for the gift sub! PogChamp
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp :( :( :( :( :( :( :( :(
vruthlessv: is this a different version or variant of Tmux ?
thediamnd: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
eeXecute: tutorial time :)
roreax6: np :)
sidthescikid: @roreax6 DANNGG HOMIE
thickbordiga: PogChamp GIVING MONEY TO JEFF BEZOS AND SOME OTHER RICH GUY
pedrovictortech: I want a free sub
Clevermacia: I love George but I can't afford since i'm already paying for comma prime lol
allbrakesnogas: 8=======D CHOOOOOOOCHOO
K177: PogChamp i'm coofing
ankitc: gift me too
pedrovictortech: hahaha
birkett0011: CHOOOO CHOOOOOOOOOOOO
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao OhMyDog
o______________________k: squadCozy COZY squadCozy COZY squadCozy COZY squadCozy COZY squadCozy COZY
benchai18: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL 5 PogChamp PogChamp
Musashhhi: lvl 5!
Chilmark: He doesn't even know PogChamp
braininavatt: GEORGE HOTZ > GOD!!!!
Penguino138: @georgehotz SENPAI NOTICE US
treestompztv: SUB NOTIFICATIONS OVERRATED
gaocaandra: jeff who joined the chat
360Plato: can mods ban the people giving subs
pedrovictortech: !hype
dorkmo: chooooooo
K177: 5Head
jimmyadaro: HYPE TRAIN MFS!!!
ankitc: who is the oprah
esence: CAN YOU GIFT ME A SUB
architectzs: What is the jupyter thing?
Clevermacia: Jeff who?
theonlymonkas: LUL LUL LUL
MrMcaustin1: choo choo mother fuckers
luigifrcruz: lvl 6?
westonwaldo: PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard PokMaskedpika PokMaskedpika PokMaskedpika
Musashhhi: choo choo
pedrovictortech: @architectzs its for lazy people
dr_set: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: TUTORIAL TIME MF WE'RE ON LEVEL 5 @georgehotz
gaocaandra: its an environment in wich you can write and test code
thickbordiga: if you beat level 5 it shows tits
braininavatt: FINAL LEVEL!!!!!!!!!!!!1 PogChamp
theonlymonkas: level 10
benchai18: 🤯
allbrakesnogas: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
treestompztv: DODGED B)
birkett0011: HOW MANY LEVELS OF HYPE ARE THERERERE
thediamnd: LUL LUL
benchai18: 🤔
sidthescikid: IGNORED LUL
architectzs: Why use it over a regular edition?
gaocaandra: used for prototyping
pedrovictortech: @architectzs its mostly used for research and machine learning
o______________________k: @birkett0011 5
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: FINAL LEVEL PogChamp PogChamp
Jehhred: I guess i'm important now
imrooty: imrooty subscribed with Twitch Prime.
jimmyadaro: LEVEL 5!!!! NEW HTML4 TUTORIAL!! OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog
Clevermacia: girl buys everyting from amazon, jeff bezos walks in , she doesn't recognize him
pjayys77: o, O
thickbordiga: thickbordiga subscribed with Twitch Prime.
c1tr0n75: cheer50
Musashhhi: lvl 6!
dr_set: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
gaocaandra: its like using word for writing a book
Clevermacia: girl can't afford anything kim k advertises, she recognizes her lips instantly
vruthlessv: GIB ME
braininavatt: PogChamp SO CLOSE
jimmyadaro: @Jehhred You can now use his bubble sorting code
ankitc: chooooooooooo
gaocaandra: but for code
mashafique: PogChamp almost there
pedrovictortech: @birkett0011 As many as you are willing to pay
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
gaocaandra: choo
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LEVEL 3 PogChamp PogChamp
allbrakesnogas: I FEEL LIKE THIS TRAIN HAS LOST ITS HYPE
mashafique: Someone gift me a sub Kappa
jimmyadaro: COME ON!!!
jimmyadaro: LEVEL 5MF
Ayyyy420Lmao: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp 8===SCAM==TRAIN===D
happy_hoppin_ppHop: Scam train almost complete PogChamp
esence: PUSH IT TO THE LIMIT
thediamnd: LUL
braininavatt: TRAIN STILL HYPEEEEEEE
t00big2fl4il: Charm++
c1tr0n75: cheer50
sokhibjke: loko lokomotif choo choo choo choo, choo choo choo choo
sidthescikid: 1 MORE SUB!!!!
theonlymonkas: LUL
TheArc_TV: Jupyter is PogChamp
jimmyadaro: HTML4 TUTORIAL!
thickbordiga: IF WE BEAT THIS LEVEL IT SHOWS TITS CMON GUYS
kruzustv: sub++
pjayys77: 97% just like California super tuesday results LUL well close enough
gaocaandra: bring it
360Plato: keep it here
jimmyadaro: OH YES, SHOW TITS
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: FINAL LEVEL PogChamp PogChamp
theonlymonkas: geo!
allbrakesnogas: 8====D LUL
MrMcaustin1: final levl
birkett0011: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: hype train lvl 6 === show tits
vruthlessv: IT SHOWS TIT?
Musashhhi: use that twitch prime
t00big2fl4il: you need the NAMD
iIyaRPV: 99% cmon guys
jimmyadaro: BRING THE TITTIES
birkett0011: WE ALL OUTTTT
mashafique: Almost there lads
sidthescikid: Watch an add quick
ankitc: CHOO CHOOO
Clevermacia: how much for pepperoni?
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to gaocaandra! They have given 6 Gift Subs in the channel!
jimmyadaro: LMAAAAO
MrMcaustin1: 1155 LOL
gaocaandra: @roreax6 Thanks for the gift sub!
mashafique: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: LUL
braininavatt: PogChamp
dr_set: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
K177: 100% PogChamp
Musashhhi: heyyyyyyy
eeXecute: PogChamp
vruthlessv: TITS COMOOON
braininavatt: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
sidthescikid: HYPPPPEEEEE PogChamp
birkett0011: WE DONE IT BOYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY
K177: Hyyyyyyyyyyypeeee PogChamp
kruzustv: congrats
happypuppppy: PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp PogChamp
braininavatt: TITTTTTTTTTTTTTTS
esence: PUSH IT TO THE LIMIT
thickbordiga: PogChamp I SAW THE TITS
happypuppppy: WE WON
t00big2fl4il: it's missing the NAMD
iIyaRPV: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Ayyyy420Lmao: StinkyCheese StinkyCheese StinkyCheese
eeXecute: VI VON
birkett0011: PogChamp PogChampPogChampPogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChampPogChampPogChampPogChampPogChamp PogChamp VPogChampPogChampPogChampPogChampPogChampPogChampPogChampPogChampPogChamp
Musashhhi: LVL 6 tutorial!
pwnbase: HypeUnicorn1
mrhdr: lvl 5
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
pedrovictortech: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChampPogChamp PogChamp PogChampPogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChampPogChampPogChamp
MrStereoX: Well Done BOYZ
gaocaandra: CHOO CHOOOOO
Clevermacia: wooo
happypuppppy: I WAS HERE PogChamp
Clevermacia: unicorn status
MrMcaustin1: 116% LOL
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
ClintBushton: PogChamp
iIyaRPV: we maxed it PogChamp
Clevermacia: screenshot my name
I2btw: omg this public pressure
thediamnd: can i get a sub？ Kappa
thickbordiga: PogChamp OBLIVIOUS STREAMER
jimmyadaro: LVL 6 TUTORIAL IS A BRAINFUCK TUTORIAL
Lizardan: gimme sub GivePLZ gimme sub GivePLZ gimme sub GivePLZ
mashafique: CHOOO CHOOO SCAM TRAIN COMPLETED
braininavatt: PHP TUTORIAL HYPE PogChamp
thickbordiga: PogChamp OBLIVIOUS STREAMER PogChamp OBLIVIOUS STREAMER PogChamp OBLIVIOUS STREAMER PogChamp OBLIVIOUS STREAMER PogChamp OBLIVIOUS STREAMER
guinness84: scammed idiots
pjayys77: LUL the different wave lengths George and the chat are on
vruthlessv: GUYS I SAW HUGE TIT
THX1342: bufer overflow the counte,r twitchies
jimmyadaro: SCAM TRAIN MF
t00big2fl4il: Check the Hype Sub
sidthescikid: PogChamp I WAS HERE
pedrovictortech: 116% Overachievement
K177: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
Clevermacia: georege has no idea he's blowing upthe interenet right now
theonlymonkas: george
jimmyadaro: @K177
jimmyadaro: im jealus
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 13 in the channel!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to programmer42!
Clevermacia: @K177 LMFAO
tornpaperyoyos: I was given a sub
jimmyadaro: jealous
happypuppppy: 132 PogChamp
braininavatt: 132% PogChamp
thickbordiga: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
mashafique: Someone toss me one LUL
K177: PogChamp
sidthescikid: 132% PogChamp
Clevermacia: @k gift me breh
Eternallightning: try this @georgehotz https://github.com/openforcefield/openforcefield
mikenachos: met is in every ORF
mineyful: lmao why the hell are you guys getting a hype train going
jimmyadaro: 132% LOL
Fosade: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
tornpaperyoyos: How was I given a sub when I wasn't even watching the stream? LUL
t00big2fl4il: Check the Hype Train Level
MrStereoX: COMN GEORGE READ CHAT
theonlymonkas: lol
treestompztv: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I’m fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I’m just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you’re a true fan
K177: PogChamp broke physics
THX1342: road to 1337%
thediamnd: Sub please) I wanna watch vods
pedrovictortech: @thickbordiga Fanboy
sidthescikid: Ignored LUL
latenightbj: does he hae no idea lol
jimmyadaro: GEEEOORRRGEEEEEEEE
zwisch: @georgehotz you have to move your groceries now
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Kreygasm
K177: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
jimmyadaro: LEVEL 6 MF
jimmyadaro: LUL
t00big2fl4il: HYPE
mineyful: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I’m fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I’m just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you’re a true fan
MrMcaustin1: haha
jimmyadaro: 132%
sidthescikid: PogChamp LVL 5 TRAINNNN!!!!
thickbordiga: @georgehotz you got like 100 subs
allSeasonDepression: Run it up
birkett0011: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
jimmyadaro: DO THE HTML4 TUTORIAL
happypuppppy: we won the hype train PogChamp
mashafique: HYPER TRAIN COMPLETED PogChamp
latenightbj: LVL 5 HYPE TRAIN
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: FINAL LEVEL PogChamp PogChamp
pjayys77: there's more important work out here chat
Fosade: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 14 in the channel!
Musashhhi: LVL 5tutorial
Clevermacia: @K177 pshh I've been following him since the first iphone jailbreka
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to schmxtzz!
pedrovictortech: Keep the hype going
gaocaandra: cause it`s hype time
esence: CHOOOOOOO
vruthlessv: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I’m fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I’m just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you’re a true fan
t00big2fl4il: bubble sort please in NAMD
T3chHS: LV 6 TRAIN SCAM!
Ayyyy420Lmao: TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati
roreax6: Yeah :D
MrMcaustin1: there still is
happy_hoppin_ppHop: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
braininavatt: Jebaited
sidthescikid: YESSS LUL
pjayys77: LUL LUL
THX1342: LUL
latenightbj: were on it now
syns0r: !claim
braininavatt: LUL
Clevermacia: you broke the internet
imrooty: LUL
jimmyadaro: 150% LUL
esence: 149%
braininavatt: LUL LUL LUL
K177: W OMEGALUL W
tornpaperyoyos: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
MrStereoX: WE ARE ON THE TRAIN DOOOODE
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: YES
braininavatt: Jebaited
getjump: PKA0
mineyful: LUL LUL LUL LUL
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
t00big2fl4il: BUBBLE SORT IN NAMD
stillgeting: LUL
sokhibjke: gl man
iIyaRPV: LUL
roreax6: <#
gaocaandra: bring itt
latenightbj: POG GEORGE
roreax6: <3
rasenjon: rasenjon subscribed with Twitch Prime.
K177: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
Clevermacia: 5 seconds
sidthescikid: PogChamp
eeXecute: LUL
jimmyadaro: YOU'RE TOO FOCUSED LUL
MrMcaustin1: 149% bb
Ayyyy420Lmao: itertools tutorial now
Incurs0: PogChamp
egb3: :)
allSeasonDepression: Hahahaha
braininavatt: PHP TUTORIAL TIME VoHiYo
pjayys77: tutorial Bros
simping4geohot: geohot <3
mikenachos: fortran tutorial PogChamp
thickbordiga: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
Clevermacia: TITTIES
asanti20: TUTORIAL HOW TO GET A GF
georgehotz: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn4
davidnzl: you rich now
MrStereoX: WE DID IT
L0ader: Can't wait to learn basic HTML!!!
tornpaperyoyos: K177: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan.
aar0npham: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
sidthescikid: @georgehotz TUTORIALS
c1tr0n75: Tchou tchou HypeUnicorn1
jimmyadaro: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
treestompztv: PogChamp
K177: W OMEGALUL W
Lizardan: @georgehotz binary search tutorial
pedrovictortech: @georgehotz making a lot of money rn
jimmyadaro: HTML4!!!!
Incurs0: 24hr stream PogChamp
guinness84: reverse bubble sort
Clevermacia: TIDS
mashafique: Jebaited
dr_set: seagSG
jimmyadaro: HTML4!!!! LUL
rustduck: tutorial
happypuppppy: he noticed PogChamp
Musashhhi: we moving groceries?
theonlymonkas: LUL
THX1342: lanaluNick
esence: BINARY SEARCH
simping4geohot: FREE GHOSTRIDING MACHINES FOR EVERYONE?
treestompztv: CHOO CHOO PogChamp
aar0npham: html4
syns0r: LETS GET HYYYYYYYPPPPPEEEEEDDDDDD
iIyaRPV: 20 subs PogChamp
PusiaPaker: teach us how to read bianary
t00big2fl4il: BUBBLE SORT CHARM++ Tutorial Please
thediamnd: PogChamp PogChamp
sidthescikid: 20 SUBS PogChamp
aar0npham: lol
iambdp22: SMOrc SMOrc SMOrc
Clevermacia: TITTEIS
L0ader: Entry level CSS! LUL
roreax6: Choo Chooo HypeUnicorn1
tornpaperyoyos: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
latenightbj: MOVING THE GROCERIES
guy_ross: level 5 storytime
jimmyadaro: SHOW US THE GROCERIES
theonlymonkas: it's completed
pedrovictortech: yeeet
benchai18: He’s scrolling up
jimmyadaro: SHOW US THE GROCERIES!!!
K177: i want a sub :(
pedrovictortech: !hype
benchai18: YEA
MrMcaustin1: gg boys
mineyful: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I’m fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I’m just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you’re a true fan
WooWhey: Groceries!
dr_set: I want an HTML tutorial
latenightbj: SHOW US TEH GOOOODS
tornpaperyoyos: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan.
ImJ4Gu4R: Lets, celeberate lol.
jmv_chin: LOL
jimmyadaro: GROCERIES OR DEATH
K177: groceries reveal PogChamp
T3chHS: lul
MrStereoX: OHHHH
jimmyadaro: HELL YEAH LUL
benchai18: Welcome to earth
T3chHS: LUL
pedrovictortech: PogChampPogChaPogChampPogChampmpPogChamp
Clevermacia: OMG THIS IS SOME PEDIEPIE SHIT
happypuppppy: HTML tutorial please i want to make an MMORPG BibleThump
jmv_chin: THIS IS WHAT IVE BEEN WAITING FOR
L0ader: Groceries stream!
Ayyyy420Lmao: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Br4nnon: is there bacon
K177: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: OMG THIS IS AMAZING
mashafique: PogChamp groceries hype
t00big2fl4il: Bubble Sort The Groceries
K177: PogChamp WTF
pedrovictortech: PogChamp PogChaPogChamp PogChamp PogChamp mp PogPogChamp PogChamp PogChamp hamp
allbrakesnogas: he;; yeeeah
benchai18: Show us ur tittles
pjayys77: mhmm very key
sidthescikid: PogChamp
vruthlessv: PogChamp
happy_hoppin_ppHop: TATERS PogChamp
benchai18: Tiddies
mashafique: Elite hacker nutrition PogChamp
theonlymonkas: GivePLZ TakeNRG
tornpaperyoyos: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
K177: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
gaocaandra: ge 380 1-Month Subscribertornpaperyoyos: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan.
treestompztv: PogChamp
MrStereoX: @benchai18 have you even seen this chat poping like that lul
eeXecute: LUL
thebiggaeboi: LMAOO
allbrakesnogas: hellll yeaaaaah
sidthescikid: PogChamp PogChamp
Fosade: SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood
pedrovictortech: Communist
Br4nnon: bacon?
gaocaandra: LMAO
Vertwo: PogChamp
theonlymonkas: GivePLZ GivePLZ GivePLZ
TheLifeIsYours: Lets make some Vodka!
birkett0011: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jimmyadaro: Do you like potatoes??
K177: it is ending LUL
sandmann00: SoBayed
stillgeting: UNBOXING
thebiggaeboi: french fries
T3chHS: TATOES OVERLOAD
tornpaperyoyos: Lmao you call yourself a GeorgeHotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan.
jimmyadaro: That's like… a lot of packaged farts
pjayys77: I mean, potatoes are the way to go
K177: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
brownyyyylocks: nice
braininavatt: WOW elloWOW
Ayyyy420Lmao: DoritosChip DoritosChip DoritosChip pastaThat pastaThat pastaThat StinkyCheese StinkyCheese StinkyCheese
pedrovictortech: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
sidthescikid: PogChamp RICE
imrooty: PO-TAY-TOES
mikenachos: LUL
Vertwo: Chat really need BTTV and FFZ
jimmyadaro: OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog
birkett0011: PogChamp APPPLES SS PogChampPogChamp
thebiggaeboi: CORONATATOES
K177: all going to go bad LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL LUL
benchai18: The groceries ? Seriously??
bluejimmy168: ??
jimmyadaro: Apples lmao
nat0w: Wash your hands, you dont know who touched it before you
doctorgenus: what about the condoms?!!!!!!!!!
sandmann00: panicBasket
T3chHS: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp ONIONS
WooWhey: How do you like dem apples!
esence: oniozzzzz
theonlymonkas: nice
K177: no can stuff? LUL
jimmyadaro: YEAH MAN, ONIONS!!!!!
Krakken_TM: 1M POINTS: 1% IN COMMA.AI LUL
jimmyadaro: EAT GARLIC
aj37z: why do you need that many onions lmao
11plus4thinking: eat a raw onion on stream PogChamp
whycopper: xqcC xqcC xqcC xqcC
latenightbj: WTF U GONNA COOK W THOSE
braininavatt: whatbout funions tho?
sidthescikid: @georgehotz Were you thinking of farming when corona go at it's worst?
dr_set: that a lot of onions man
brownyyyylocks: hell yea
t00big2fl4il: Did you get any frozen fish?
rimali: worst possible caloric density
Br4nnon: rip tangerines
Taygetea: raw onion
jimmyadaro: RAW ONION!!
theonlymonkas: LUL LUL LUL
Vertwo: LAYERS
treestompztv: PogChamp PogChamp
tornpaperyoyos: Thats a shit ton of onions wtf LUL
jmv_chin: ARE THEY ORGANIC
iIyaRPV: worth it
theonlymonkas: eat one
T3chHS: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp GROCERIES
AresRai: @Vertwo they dont, this is no twitch pleb chat, this is very 5Head chat
jimmyadaro: RAW ONION!!!
I2btw: I don't understand how georgehotz tolerates this chat. Spamming irrelevant memes and emotes. Constantly berating the streamer for the smallest mistakes. You guys are lucky you're not all banned.
K177: D:
Ayyyy420Lmao: based onionboy
ankitc: GARLIC
Taygetea: eat a raw onion
sandmann00: NomNom NomNom NomNom NomNom NomNom
Krakken_TM: 1M POINTS: 1% IN COMMA.AI LUL LUL
jimmyadaro: EAT DA ONION LUL
THX1342: so the world is NOT going to end? PixelBob
treestompztv: Where’s the tendies
Mint2bSpiced: are you making a stew?
Vertwo: :(
tornpaperyoyos: What kind of groceries were that?? LUL
birkett0011: LUL What the fuk are you gonna cook with potatoes onions annd rice
gaocaandra: i bought 320kg of rice
K177: I don't understand how georgehotz tolerates this chat. Spamming irrelevant memes and emotes. Constantly berating the streamer for the smallest mistakes. You guys are lucky you're not all banned.
Vertwo: 5Head
c1tr0n75: We should do another cooking stream one day LOL
MrStereoX: @MrMcaustin1 what does the hype train actually do ?
latenightbj: onions and potoatoes and apple casserole
roreax6: roreax6 is gifting 3 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 9 in the channel!
jimmyadaro: Now show the tts
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to InfiniteReddit!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to northumb!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to ar2zee!
granti7: @georgehotz did you clean all the packages with alcohol? you can get corona from that shit
Clevermacia: BEST WAY TO GET LAID. GO TO WALMART, GET A PACK OF CONDOMS AND SOME BEER, THEN ASK THE CASHIER WHAT TIMES SHE'S OFF
Vertwo: PogChamp
K177: PogChamp
gaocaandra: 4 real
treestompztv: PogChamp
T3chHS: World end stream PogChamp
jimmyadaro: LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL
awesomeo113: Cooking stream
jimmyadaro: Nah
benchai18: @k177 What do u mean??? Who’s berating him?
rstk1: LUL
K177: PepeLaugh
Vertwo: LUL
MrMcaustin1: MrStereoX basically means a lot of people give love to george
tornpaperyoyos: Are you just going to eat onions rice and potatoes forever?? LUL
t00big2fl4il: CHARM++ BUBBLE SORT nice!!!!!!!! NAMD
pjayys77: this sounds like the title of a book
localcanofdutchgold: love lul
gaocaandra: coronalove
braininavatt: are you writing a book? Kappa
Crime_Stein: martial law
Ayyyy420Lmao: woah that was a steven spielberg reference
happypuppppy: if we can beat the hype train we can beat corona PogChamp
latenightbj: george cooking stream ftw
roreax6: roreax6 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 10 in the channel!
roreax6: roreax6 gifted a Tier 1 sub to rstk1!
treestompztv: LUL
Krakken_TM: 1M POINTS: 1% IN COMMA.AI LUL
latenightbj: I want a sub lol
roreax6: No problem :)
MrMcaustin1: gg
sidthescikid: PogChamp @roreax6
theonlymonkas: raw onion
awesomeo113: Fuck it
Eternallightning: That movie is so good LUL
K177: np :)
architectzs: architectzs subscribed with Twitch Prime.
MrStereoX: @MrMcaustin1 does he get any extra perks from that ?
roreax6: Thanks for putting this together
vruthlessv: gimme
jimmyadaro: Cocking stream LUL
rstk1: @roreax6 Thanks for the gift sub!
Bloodswordz88: 500K deaths and then it will lay dormant. no worries
ankitc: giff mee oprah
doctorgenus: do you make money on hype train?
MrMcaustin1: george is making all his money back after the stock market from subs
MrStereoX: OMG cooking stream
Crime_Stein: 24 hr stream
pedrovictortech: Yeet
K177: full time streamer PogChamp
Crime_Stein: to save the world
theonlymonkas: cooking stream
latenightbj: georges kitchen
sidthescikid: @MrMcaustin1 LUL
T3chHS: Cooking stream when
o______________________k: @georgehotz streamlabs is something you need to use for stuf like that
pjayys77: train dun made a full lap before being noticed bruh
treestompztv: admHack admHack admHack admHack
whycopper: Is comma ai self quarantining right now @georgehotz
THX1342: @georgehotz I missed that stream LUL what did you learn that made you not worry
Organiik: Hype strain pog
Nussinov: was today productive I didnt watch :)
K177: small Kappa
latenightbj: cooking stream ftw
MrStereoX: SMALL
benchai18: So ur not worried abt it anymore??? Honestly tho??
slimpimp007: lessssgooo
pwnbase: small loan
jimmyadaro: Q&A time @georgehotz ?
ankitc: smoll
lolzmaster99: take tesla autopilot and transfer learn for openpilot
doctorgenus: are you guys working from home?!!!!
adorablejaay: Wheres our Sorting Algo Tutorial REE
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Please keep coming here daily
ImJ4Gu4R: HolidayOrnament
braininavatt: DO BETTER ECONOMY pls
Taygetea: hack the economy
Ayyyy420Lmao: comfy -$500k YTD
latenightbj: Are you going to apply for a disaster SBA loan ??
doctorgenus: rent is due soon. Can you guys pay rent?!!!
granti7: things will go back to normal once corona gets tired of killing people
dprophecyguy: We appreciate everything you do.
latenightbj: 1.5 mil
t00big2fl4il: In the ZONE that's why Hype trains get missed
THX1342: are you worried about your older relatives or friends?
architectzs: I subbed for the time i asked about the forsaken thing
T3chHS: What a chad
braininavatt: that protects you, yes
benchai18: @georgehotz you have a sick following when u stream regularly
braininavatt: Kappa
jimmyadaro: Q&A time @georgehotz ??
theonlymonkas: cooking stream
Taygetea: how much runway
MrStereoX: We rich boyz
braininavatt: you are now immune cuz of the motorcycle SeemsGood
Lizardan: @doctorgenus I saved up money to survive for a year without a job
sidthescikid: @georgehotz Where's the tutorial?
ahahahaitslit: please make a self driving motorcycle
Br4nnon: do you miss the office
jimmyadaro: cooking stream
MrMcaustin1: black swan events suck
dorkmo: comma leaks about total miles driven dropping from corona?
gaocaandra: the crisis was already here
slimpimp007: everyone working from home?
awesomeo113: Rule number 1. Don’t talk about ,,,,,,,
T3chHS: Can someone please give me a sub, I want to use Bubble sort
gaocaandra: the crash was only expected
jimmyadaro: High risk, high impact
architectzs: What is geohotz main job? \
theonlymonkas: *dies*
latenightbj: @georgehotz sba disaster loan at 3.75 percent . ma out at 1.5 mil . 30 year am
benchai18: @architectzs Comma ai
Krakken_TM: Yeah bro it's really a political thing. people should read about the anglo-saxon mission
TwitchahShadow: regardless of the coronavirus, the deleveraging was expected, it was due ever since late 2018s. the markets were rather inflated
thecoder15: @georgehotz what problems do you see can be solved with robotics but aren't currently ?
Hawklite: i'd go for 100%
Exclamation_mark_CODE: @georgehotz is government going to bail you out?
K177: only LUL
theonlymonkas: self driving motorcycle
awesomeo113: Are you still banning people geo
c1tr0n75: I personnaly got the Virus two weeks ago, and I am recovering slowly, the annoying thing is that its a very slow recovery and that you should be really careful with people
Ayyyy420Lmao: rookie numbers
braininavatt: monkaS
Krakken_TM: hahahahhahaha
AThousandHours: how do you calculate 30%?
MrMcaustin1: georgehotz https://www.reddit.com/r/dataisbeautiful/comments/fpga3f/oc_to_show_just_how_insane_this_weeks/
doctorgenus: hahaahaa
gaocaandra: no
o______________________k: yes
birkett0011: MR TANGERINE MAN WILL SAVE US !
gaocaandra: bio
gaocaandra: go
L0ader: Both LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: tutorial time
MrStereoX: @c1tr0n75 i hope you feel better fast :) <3
braininavatt: RANT TIME
jimmyadaro: BOTH
whycopper: LMFAO
Clevermacia: FIGHT ELON
doctorgenus: hey, there's a stimulus bill, you can get 1200
o______________________k: we love rants DUD squadBrug
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: BOTH
whycopper: YES
TheArc_TV: LUL
slimpimp007: I'm here for the rants
doctorgenus: that's a gpu right there
treestompztv: evo14USA
I2btw: i'm here to learn phyton
K177: holy shit
c1tr0n75: @MrStereoX Thanks man!!
K177: thats insane
Ayyyy420Lmao: 32sigma event
eeXecute: LuL
gaocaandra: holy
braininavatt: 4Head
Vertwo: george needs to mee t reckful
pedrovictortech: You should get more of track
gaocaandra: fuck
L0ader: LUL
TheLifeIsYours: PogChamp
mashafique: LUL
iIyaRPV: 4Head
adrijan1990: my state thrives on 30% percentage of unemployment. In fact, we happy if they get it down to that
jimmyadaro: Wow holy moly
l1ght5p33d: yea wtf is that
Krakken_TM: STAY HOME STAY SAFE 4Head
DragonNewLight: PogChamp
smalldiickrick: sinister laugh LUL
Nussinov: so beautiful
TheArc_TV: Fuck
THX1342: LUL
roreax6: That's absolutely insane.
doctorgenus: LOOLLLL
awesomeo113: We want to hear your opinions
pjayys77: why are you laughing, lol , why am I laughing
benchai18: I still think there’s something else behind the response to this virus. It’s real, but the response I think is partially driven by political shit. Probably wanting to ruin Trump. CDC wanting more funding... dems promise they’ll give it
TheArc_TV: LOL
jimmyadaro: LUL
c1tr0n75: LMAO
stillgeting: damn
gaocaandra: BOI
thecoder15: LOL
latenightbj: Back to work
guinness84: ur forgetting about the $1200 though
Ayyyy420Lmao: 32 sigma evnt
slimpimp007: we fucked lol
ImJ4Gu4R: Damn i feel cruel
gaocaandra: THATS A CRASH
Bloodswordz88: Stay home, no wait work work work
ImJ4Gu4R: I laughed
THX1342: house of cards
AThousandHours: how do you calculate 30%?
ahahahaitslit: aw jeez
allbrakesnogas: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ
Taygetea: decentralized tech go start a commune guys
jimmyadaro: Let's get back on track
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaS
stuffedcrust45: Does that account for the increase in population though??
doctorgenus: @georgehotz what you going to do with your 1200 dollars?!
MrStereoX: @allbrakesnogas fk
mashafique: Maybe you should address those questions that people ask all the time such as how to become a 1337 coder and hacker like you and how to be super smart and all that so people can stop memeing
treestompztv: NEETS RISE UP
gaocaandra: argentina
gaocaandra: is the oposite
vay_man: hey geo
esence: USA #1
gaocaandra: of us
jimmyadaro: @gaocaandra I'm from there
theonlymonkas: el diegote
pjayys77: solid question, quality
simping4geohot: LMFAO
o______________________k: Maybe you should address those questions that people ask all the time such as how to become a 1337 coder and hacker like you and how to be super smart and all that so people can stop memeing LUL
sandmann00: The peek/insight you have to how things work in the corporate world and just from your frame of thinking is insightful!
K177: 😎 1337
L0ader: Yeah aside from the president calling it a hoax and denying any threat LUL
THX1342: LUL
simping4geohot: those are awful questions
MrStereoX: Kappa
rstk1: LMAO
birkett0011: LUL
THX1342: OMFG
guinness84: oh no
Nussinov: ??????
t00big2fl4il: n00b
happypuppppy: secrets revealed PogChamp
THX1342: B A I T
vruthlessv: WHY
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
Clevermacia: ohh shit
ArosGeo: "practice"
Ayyyy420Lmao: @o______________________k hacks
thebiggaeboi: just be smart bro
vruthlessv: D O N T
localcanofdutchgold: 4Head <---- the answer
jimmyadaro: "Get shit done"
o______________________k: practice practice practice practice practice practice practice practice
benchai18: @georgehotz I don’t get it. Why is this being treated SOOOO differently than every other outbreak in my lifetime.
vruthlessv: REEEEE
vay_man: just woke up to this stream
tornpaperyoyos: HOW DO I SUPER SMART GEORGE
K177: B OMEGALUL OMEGALUL KS
L0ader: It's baaaaaaaaait
pikomane2: maybe
esence: here: l337
ankitc: I KNOW YOU WIILL SAY PRACTICEEEEEEEEEE
happy_hoppin_ppHop: Give them a meme answer to follow
mikenachos: it looks like a $500/month ponzi scheme
braininavatt: yes Kappa
Krakken_TM: Italy/spain said if they dont get bailouts from the europe in 10 days their leaving
MrMcaustin1: Yes the secret books of codes
Clevermacia: you triggered him
asanti20: HOW DO I SMART
ankitc: PRACTICEEEE
K177: monkaS
TwitchahShadow: online courses behind a $10000 paywall are the way @georgehotz
Crime_Stein: give us the books !
bluejimmy168: If you subscribe then you will be smart
happypuppppy: no reading a book is too much work :)
gaocaandra: they are trolling
rasenjon: IT'S NATURAL SELECTION
jimmyadaro: HOW DO I DRINK WATER
K177: they expect a json format
doctorgenus: it's IQ, it's nature
simping4geohot: it looks like BITCONNECTTTTTTTTTTTTTT
THX1342: Troll of the year
mashafique: That's not a question of mine. That's just something I see all the time here
jimmyadaro: @K177 LUL
allbrakesnogas: beers beets battlestar galactica
tornpaperyoyos: GIVE ME THE SMARTS GEORGE
doctorgenus: have smarter children
birkett0011: BITCOINS
TheArc_TV: Write a self help book Kappa
Clevermacia: yup you got it
localcanofdutchgold: Pog
esence: @georgehotz just tell them: "LEARN TO CODE"
awesomeo113: Stemming
bluejimmy168: sign me up
mikenachos: exactly
K177: LUL
volere: TECHLEAD OMEGALUL
thebiggaeboi: lmaoo
sandmann00: lol
gaocaandra: people want the results
Clevermacia: im going to create a course and source you'
awesomeo113: Being a savant
360Plato: he just wants to talk
sidthescikid: LUL
braininavatt: https://twitter.com/jonfriedman/status/1243359700470484994?s=20
lolzmaster99: There is a difference between knowing and understanding.
K177: D: stop
gabo_sk: yeas
Br4nnon: you gotta have a problem you want to solve LUL
happypuppppy: don't you just have a smart pill I can take :)
gaocaandra: not the wrk
pikomane2: did you take computer science classes in highschool?
asanti20: How to find a GF
jimmyadaro: You'd make A TON of money LUL
aj37z: TAKE MY MONEY
outlier2: techlead
birkett0011: MAKE A UDEMY COURSE
K177: hackforums has the ebook for sale
rstk1: LUL
theonlymonkas: NO LUL
ICAntF331MyFAce: LUL
stillgeting: LUL
smalldiickrick: LUL
o______________________k: @georgehotz we just want inspiration from you :)
tornpaperyoyos: bubble sort LUL
c1tr0n75: LMAO WE LOVE YOU GEORGE, AWESOME ANSWER
informalgarlic: but what blogs @georgehotz
sidthescikid: EZ Clap
localcanofdutchgold: scam train
thebiggaeboi: UDEMY BOIY
ankitc: https://norvig.com/21-days.html
gabo_sk: OMEGALUL
doctorgenus: lol @volere yeah techlead is such a scammmm lol
I2btw: I have all the books since i'm 12
jimmyadaro: You'd make A TON of money LUL !
mikenachos: I saw a documentary called "Limitless" and they said theres a pill that makes life easy
whycopper: how do I get pusc like you @georgehotz :(
awesomeo113: Lmao
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: only scam trains LULW
smalldiickrick: i went to a coding bootcamp PepeHands
jimmyadaro: @mikenachos Adderall?
Taygetea: You can't teach people a Thielian secret, they'll hear it and then ignore it! it sucks!
t00big2fl4il: Bubble sort in Charm++ Parallels!!!!!!!! Elite NAMD
mikenachos: jimmyadaro diddo
theonlymonkas: another book like the metamorphosis of prime intellect
THX1342: just. get. skilllllllllls. if you aren't curious to fucking go after knowledge you will not be a 1337 h4x0r sorry
pjayys77: I think they expect something like first you start with python, then you read the Hacker Manifesto, then you do a,, then b
Eternallightning: its pronounced METH IO NEENE
jimmyadaro: @mikenachos Dildo??
K177: PogChamp
informalgarlic: @georgehotz setup streamlab commands for this shit!! @georgehotz
gabo_sk: watching mr robot
K177: FIRST VIDEO LUL
eeXecute: LUL
Br4nnon: 1337 h4x0rz
braininavatt: Kappa
Vertwo: LUL
K177: oh god LUL
mikenachos: jimmyadaro no meth :)
WhiteTriad: 2003
esence: AMOMYNOUS
jimmyadaro: @mikenachos That sounds better
georgehotz: https://forums.introversion.co.uk/viewtopic.php?t=25196
K177: ty :)
jimmyadaro: LUL
liiiiiig0: have you seen Mr. Robot?
thecoder15: @georgehotz man there are so many noobs in here
mikenachos: LUL
vay_man: yes
stillgeting: GOT IT!
sidthescikid: LUL
volere: ok well that answers that question
K177: that website has my ip now :)
Mint2bSpiced: I would read your autobiography
happy_hoppin_ppHop: 😎 1337 Hacker reporting in
volere: next question
informalgarlic: @georgehotz setup streamlab commands for this stuff! @georgehotz
safire5: Meth eye oh neen
simping4geohot: geohot there are actually a lot of interesting smart contract exploits
awesomeo113: Do a worst of the tech industry Geo
Taygetea: cant teach thielian secrets!!!!!!
simping4geohot: that happened not too long ago
dorkmo: is that darwinia forum?
Chasewhip8_: have you looked at camostat mesylate? https://www.cell.com/cell/pdf/S0092-8674(20)30229-4.pdf
jimmyadaro: You'd make A TON of money LUL
adorablejaay: @georgehotz How did you come out with the hacker name georgehotz nathanPepe
simping4geohot: would you consider doing a stream analyzing some smart contract hacks?
Taygetea: @dorkmo probably uplink
360Plato: new copy pasta
o______________________k: @georgehotz you got me into programmign in 2009 when i was 13 :3
brownyyyylocks: @taygetea tell us a Thielian secret!!
MrStereoX: Today's stream is so great lul
allbrakesnogas: the new world order made my wife a lesbian
jimmyadaro: @MrStereoX As usual
austin__be__saucin: youtube how to pronounce methionine lol
Chasewhip8_: copy pasta lmfaoo
esence: XML HACKER
WhiteTriad: they're looking to jmp into hacking w/ a pop addiction. After you're IN they can hook something like peter pan and finally call the system like they do their mom
theonlymonkas: flexbox
o______________________k: they're looking to jmp into hacking w/ a pop addiction. After you're IN they can hook something like peter pan and finally call the system like they do their mom
mikenachos: Meth-I-O-neen
happy_hoppin_ppHop: based streamer and based streamies
THX1342: people are afraid to learn. afraid to get things wrong and feel lost. that' why step by step and tutorials are such a success... they lower the disappointment. but the problem is you end up limiting yourself and thinking like everybody else
tornpaperyoyos: BUT GEORGE YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO MAKE ME SMART WHEN I ASK YOU TO
allbrakesnogas: guys im hacking the mainframe bleep bloop im in
pjayys77: real answer to these questions, doesn't matter where you start just do it
jimmyadaro: @theonlymonkas Flexbox is THE shit, i love it, idk if more than css grid but…
mashafique: Didn't mean to trigger LUL was just tired of seeing it so I took the fall
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 Word.
MrStereoX: @THX1342 TRUE
Nussinov: alpha beta gamma
t00big2fl4il: I am waiting for the $1200 from Mitch and Nancy so I can sub
voxelfox0125: This the real answer https://guidedhacking.com/threads/start-here-beginners-guide-to-learning-game-hacking.5911/
Br4nnon: css monkaS
Taygetea: @brownyyyylocks lemme think of one
Taygetea: @brownyyyylocks ill get back to you in a sec lol
jimmyadaro: Cómo estas me llamo de biblioteques mucho gracia en mi por amor es epan aiken ook wenn ich spielen aufhoren hocchievehn!!!!!
SurajkAxim: is he running a md simulation?
awesomeo113: The real answer is becoming a script kiddie
o______________________k: yeah reverse engineering.. you just have to read shit and trial and error. just accept failures and learn to move forward through the problems :)
brownyyyylocks: @taygetea RIP
esence: JSON HACKER BY DAY, CSS L337 PROGRAMMER BY NIGHT
ahahahaitslit: we live in a simulation
architectzs: Are raspberry pi's good learning tools for coding?
theonlymonkas: @jimmyadaro no entendí wacho
THX1342: the real answer is you need an OSCP certificate BrokeBack
mikenachos: no that carbon has a double bond and two single bonds
informalgarlic: Hacking involves reading forums posts and learning how computers work on the lowest levels. bam
jimmyadaro: @theonlymonkas Es de un video, boludo xdd
o______________________k: if you have to take 3 months to understand pointers and Malloc then its gonna take 3 months no gimmics
aj37z: solid state drive
roletro: @georgehotz probably geometry shit
jimmyadaro: @theonlymonkas Wait, where are you from?
safire5: HB as in Hydrogen Bent ?
K177: standard def :)
Nussinov: the number of hydrogens might depend on the ph of the solution. you can lose hydrogens from an amino acid if the ph is high enough :)
safire5: Bent structure with N
t00big2fl4il: square deviation
MrStereoX: Have you every worked on kaspersky ? @georgehotz
C0deCane: @aj37z Network interface card
theonlymonkas: @jimmyadaro italy
tornpaperyoyos: MAKE ME SMARTER GEORGE OR SO HELP ME I WILL RETRACT MY SUBSCRIPTION
jimmyadaro: @theonlymonkas MAMMA MIA
theonlymonkas: LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL
mikenachos: is there an alanine next to the methionine?
austin__be__saucin: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5y4q-TNO5sc
theknip: from what library does forcefiled come from`?
t00big2fl4il: square deviation
o______________________k: @tornpaperyoyos too far DUD mizkifBat mizkifBat mizkifBat
Chasewhip8_: we making a real dictionary out here to translate whitepapers
Taygetea: @brownyyyylocks this one might be well known now bc elon, but manufacturing isnt that hard and you can make a fuckload of money and have a real impact on the world
informalgarlic: setup streamlabs for donos!! @georgehotz
architectzs: Are raspberry pi's good tools for learning?
voxelfox0125: https://www.learncpp.com/ For those interested this is a great place to learn C++
jimmyadaro: o_[…]_k your nickname is fucking me up
awesomeo113: HB-1 visa bb
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Depending on what you wanna learn
awesomeo113: I NEED A SPONSOR
tornpaperyoyos: @o______________________k im sorry dont hurt me plox
C0deCane: @architectzs just having a raspberry pi doesn't mean you'll learn anything
jagger_rsw: Do you still want subscription/popularity b/c in 'world of abundance' popularity will be the only currency?
architectzs: coding and other things like ethical hacking and circuitry
MrStereoX: I dont think he will ever setup streamlabs...
brownyyyylocks: @taygetea thats elon's secret. what is _your_ Thielian secret?!
jimmyadaro: @architectzs You can do it without one
o______________________k: @tornpaperyoyos squadW
architectzs: Yeah I know but you can do some things with the rasp
sokhibjke: SeemsGood
sidthescikid: Not me :)
aj37z: me
Vertwo: me
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Like what? Why would you need it for?
jimmyadaro: What*
architectzs: Like if I wanted to mess with my family by messing with their phones, would I be able to do that with just computer or do I need a pi
theonlymonkas: not me
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Any computer would do the trick
sidthescikid: @architectzs that's not ethical hacking tho
architectzs: How difficult would it be to perform that
jimmyadaro: @architectzs I have an old Acer with Kali Linux as its main OS and it works wonderful
SurajkAxim: can someone explain what he s doing? sorry LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL
thickbordiga: @architectzs just throw their phones in the trash worked for me
C0deCane: @jimmyadaro you're like being this guys conscious lol let him buy a raspberry pi LUL
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane He doesn't need to spend money on that!
awesomeo113: @surajkaxim finding the cure to corona
coloneljerkoff: Which biology classes do we need to take to understand what he's doing here?
C0deCane: @jimmyadaro I know LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL
jimmyadaro: U bad
SurajkAxim: @awesomeo113 but how
T3chHS: @coloneljerkoff the google classes in biology
jimmyadaro: Is he hacking DNA with HTML?
awesomeo113: @surajkaxim 1337 hacking
architectzs: How hard would it be to perform a hack like that on my family through the wifi or something that we are both connected to
voxelfox0125: @coloneljerkoff all of them
nudax: !uptime
C0deCane: @jimmyadaro I need you everytime I go to the store to tell me what i should and should not buy LUL Kappa
jimmyadaro: @architectzs It may take me like 5 mins
theonlymonkas: and CSS
gabo_sk: so how can i be a 1337 hacker?
architectzs: actually?
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane HAHAHAHAH LUL
wolphganng: @coloneljerkoff organic chemistry and basic dna knowledge
awesomeo113: By being on the spectrum
architectzs: how lmao
Taygetea: @brownyyyylocks i thought i had some, but if i do they're not explicitly formed in my head, i need to rethink my life lol
t00big2fl4il: RMSD - root-mean-square deviation SD square deviation https://www.ks.uiuc.edu/Training/Workshop/Urbana/Thu1.pdf
jimmyadaro: @architectzs You need to learn about networking and CS
jimmyadaro: CS = Computer science
architectzs: Ik
tornpaperyoyos: if george doesnt make me smarter i will unfollow him on instagram!! BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
happy_hoppin_ppHop: @gabo_sk Get an invitation to the secret hacker society
virtual_machine: the only way you can become this good is if you ARE the spectrum tbh
architectzs: How long would it take to learn how to do it?
thickbordiga: @architectzs the first step is to give yourself autism via a flu vaccine
thecoder15: do you think that you would end up end the hospital if you got sars-cov-2 @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: I'm working on a Medium post with a fuck ton of links with free courses
jimmyadaro: I'll share it later
architectzs: I friended u
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Where?
jimmyadaro: I'm everywhere
brownyyyylocks: @taygetea haha ok!! get back to me when you have!! :)
jimmyadaro: lmao
C0deCane: @jimmyadaro if i make my computer smaller will i become a hacker?
awesomeo113: Ima get the corona vaccine so I can be a savant
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane How much smaller?
awesomeo113: Brb
T3chHS: @coloneljerkoff I was not trollingabout the google stuff, george has just been googling bio stuff for the past 4 days. I don't believe he has a biology background
architectzs: I friended u on twtich
C0deCane: Idk how small are wood chips LUL
dprophecyguy: Use this to learn about network programming https://beej.us/guide/bgnet/
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Didn't get any notification yet
Chasewhip8_: next up sars-cov-2 vaccine causes autism
coloneljerkoff: cool, thanks. yea i can follow the programming but all this chemistry is like moon language
architectzs: Where can I freind u
architectzs: elesewhere if i need help with something is that ok ?
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Google my name, I'm mainly on linkeding
jimmyadaro: Linkedin*
dprophecyguy: Use this to learn C language https://beej.us/guide/bgc/
Chasewhip8_: What is he even working on rn
icyvran: Coronavirus Could Be a ‘Chimera’ of Two Different Viruses, Genome Analysis Suggests https://www.sciencealert.com/genome-analysis-of-the-coronavirus-suggests-two-viruses-may-have-combined/amp
t00big2fl4il: OXT https://www.ebi.ac.uk/pdbe-srv/pdbechem/chemicalCompound/show/OXT
MrTriharder: Hey George if you are looking for investment for comma.bio hit me up, I got my moms savings :) SeemsGood
wolphganng: What’s the point of reverse engineering the virus??
jimmyadaro: @MrTriharder LUL
awesomeo113: I got my rent Geo
jimmyadaro: @wolphganng Get some MONEY
mobal: heyo george o/
awesomeo113: I’ll throw in
MrTriharder: @jimmyadaro LUL
o______________________k: @wolphganng to be less ignorant and learn the best your can to understand a pandemic :)
gabo_sk: i got my coronas bond
eeXecute: I'll send in my welfare check SeemsGood
awesomeo113: Just wait till my relief check hits
onu4r: yo my boi
coProof: I remember the coding streams PepeHands
franky4l: @georgehotz shouldn't OXT coordinates also be displaced ?
thickbordiga: I have some money I stole from some moron named geohot on Augur I can give you
jimmyadaro: @coProof He did a Python tutorial earlier today LUL
onu4r: my man trying to vind an exploit vector for coronavirus 😃
onu4r: find*
lithiumx4900: I thought pdb files were microsoft debugging files.
o______________________k: LUL
mobal: @lithiumx4900 extension means nothing :)
coProof: @jimmyadaro payoTitinu
C0deCane: ain't nothin fightin Corona better than them good ole USD's
jimmyadaro: @coProof OhMyDog
o______________________k: hey you guys know hassanABI?
liiiiiig0: yea, why @o______________________k
voxelfox0125: Geohot is one of the few people that can use the internet to learn all most anything and apply it within a few days.
thickbordiga: hasWeird
lithiumx4900: @C0deCane germany came up with better tests. dyson invented a ventilator.
wolphganng: Yea I know that dude
o______________________k: imagine George vs HassanABI debate LUL
informalgarlic: Geo is a messy desktop guy, jesus.
wolphganng: Geo would win
jimmyadaro: @informalgarlic OH NO
shr3knad0: What are you working on
C0deCane: @lithiumx4900 not without money my friend
o______________________k: @wolphganng hassan would get so mad LUL
shr3knad0: What is he working on?
onu4r: bosch just built a new test method with %95 accuracy and needs no lab
informalgarlic: Geo sucks at government and ecomonic stuff. No offense. He’s a capitalist
jimmyadaro: @shr3knad0 Hacking coronavirus
o______________________k: @shr3knad0 self studying virology
senpagax: 28 days later geohot lowkey shipping bootleg corona virus vaccines
TheFallDamage: he is literally about to defeat covid-19
wolphganng: Yea he would malding and yelling LUL
thickbordiga: hasKAYAYA
wolphganng: Be malding*
C0deCane: @lithiumx4900 just fuckin around anyway LUL but seriously Germany is just better a lot of things
DraxenOK: yo guys just joined, whats going on here?
guy_ross: @informalgarlic boo
o______________________k: oh no @thickbordiga OHHH
DraxenOK: we mapping out molecules
MrStereoX: ש
Taygetea: flailing at molecular simulation of proteins of the coronavirus @DraxenOK
lithiumx4900: @C0deCane i'm just dismayed at how we are unable to manufacture appropriate testing and ventilators at any kind of scale.
thickbordiga: george knows about cybersyn he would own hasan who does not know about cybersyn
guacDev: @DraxenOK were finding a cure for the coronavirus
DraxenOK: EPIC
C0deCane: @lithiumx4900 why are you amazed we have literally like no manufactures here of any kind
limnick: I hear if you run the proteins into a tracker it makes some sick tunes
TiPera: hey guys, I just joined what is he doing? dizzyUp
saucefoong: StoneLightning
jimmyadaro: @TiPera Hacking COVID-19
awesomeo113: Can we pin a comment saying what he’s doing
lithiumx4900: @C0deCane we have plenty. we just give money to companies like Quest Diagnostics instead of offering real solutions.
informalgarlic: @guy_ross it’s a computer genius but...can’t figure out that automation in a capitalist society doesn’t work. Einstein sucked at some shit too
t00big2fl4il: bubble sorting covid-19
FancyDawg_: https://github.com/geohot/corona/issues/7
limnick: got some real bernie fans in chat LUL
awesomeo113: Is this part of Googles technical interview ?
awesomeo113: Reverse Covid-19
informalgarlic: Capitalism doesn’t work in a fully automated society chat.
Taygetea: @FancyDawg_ cooool
theonlymonkas: DBstyle
allbrakesnogas: bernie sanders is my crush shhh dont tell anyone
happypuppppy: where did you get the pdf from
jimmyadaro: @informalgarlic Shut up
SHAVEYY_: how do install on linux @georgehotz
TiPera: @jimmyadaro thanks, is he trying to make a vaccine or what dizzyLul
t00big2fl4il: stimulus package = 1000x Subs
I2btw: When he creaks this, i go in this industry for 11€/h
informalgarlic: @jimmyadaro stop crying
limnick: productivity doesnt matter in a modern economy -bernbrain
Nussinov: nope
localcanofdutchgold: Kapp
aj37z: no
pjayys77: do you even biology bro
presidentkanyewest2024: Kappa
theonlymonkas: alto genio
Taygetea: scihub must be legal in some jurisdiction
jimmyadaro: @informalgarlic Make me stop crying *winks both eyes*
MrStereoX: @westonwaldo you sent it
MrStereoX: ?
gabo_sk: alto genio
informalgarlic: Lol
mathnerd314159: they read the proposal pretty carefully
awesomeo113: In order to install Linux you have to delete system.32
jimmyadaro: @gabo_sk No, vos.
liiiiiig0: i'm copying the book from the stream as we speak Kappa
gabo_sk: u.u
Lizardan: It totally makes sense 4Head
Taygetea: i really hope george has the ability to go and quietly read a book off stream and he does that tomorrow before stream 7
jimmyadaro: @gabo_sk Mentira tkm
t00big2fl4il: organic chemistry
Nussinov: get "molecular biology of the gene" that textbook is fucking lit
lithiumx4900: @Taygetea george reminds me of Mr. Robot talking to himself.
slimpimp007: bio teachers have the power to induce deep sleep
guacDev: you read 11 mph
allbrakesnogas: disappointing
theonlymonkas: ahora es en español el chat?
onu4r: gates reads 500 wpm
jimmyadaro: 3 pages at the same time?
Taygetea: if you read as fast as you google
pjayys77: gotta be honest, seems like you're a pretty fast reader
awesomeo113: MITOCHONDRIA IS THE POWERHOUSE OF THE CELL
Chasewhip8_: im still rooting for camostat mesylate comming in clutch
gabo_sk: 👀
jimmyadaro: @gabo_sk Qué onda capo
mashafique: big mood LUL
L0ader: Is there an end goal for this "project" or are you just doing it to learn some new shit? @georgehotz
benchai18: Fuck that was way longer than I realized.
MrMcaustin1: jimmyadaro and gabo_sk english in chat please
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 What?
jimmyadaro: @MrMcaustin1 Sure, sorry about that
senpagax: there's never an end goal with his streams..
gabo_sk: monkaS
limnick: "end goal" non programmer spotted
limnick: Kappa
awesomeo113: lmao
EXSNarrow: LUL
limnick: the goal is to find the next bug LUL
TiPera: lol
awesomeo113: The end goal is 1 million followers on Instagram
wolphganng: I speed read chapters to get a sense of what I’ll be learning then I go back and read word for word
I2btw: omg that reminds me of my chemistry teacher at the age of 14, he was right
MrStereoX: @MrMcaustin1 Do you code?
MrMcaustin1: yes sire
whycopper: The goal is to smash Riley Reid
jimmyadaro: He needs some milk
raykuhs: is george programming the cure guys ?
awesomeo113: Riley Reid ??
awesomeo113: More like Lana Rhodes
pjayys77: next step in this streaming channel, getting one of those bio hackers on stream for questions
c1tr0n75: George is starting to consider Comma Bio seriously
onu4r: @raykuhs nope he's more like having fun
sidthescikid: does sci hub work on this?
MrTriharder: Lana grosses got surgery DansGame
MrStereoX: @MrMcaustin1 whats your fav lang
nitrixen: Magnets, how do they work.
AresRai: good stream :)
Santiago_LHC: commit!
MrMcaustin1: MrStereoX depends on the day
MrTriharder: Rhoades *
allbrakesnogas: does anyone have any tips on breaking into the jobs market? no one will hire me 8==D
dorkmo: choo chooooo
jimmyadaro: @MrMcaustin1 What if it's a rainy day?
wigglebeans: u called me
MrTriharder: @chat do proteins have a functional group?
MrMcaustin1: then jimmyadaro py2
awesomeo113: I’m just enjoying that free PH premium
I2btw: so many data
t00big2fl4il: In bioinformatics, the root-mean-square deviation of atomic positions (or simply root-mean-square deviation, RMSD) is the measure of the average distance between the atoms (usually the backbone atoms) of superimposed proteins. Note that RMSD calculation can be applied to other, non-protein molecules, such as small organic molecules.[1] In the study of globular protein conformations, one customarily measures the similarity in three-dimensional structure by the RMSD of the .........wikipedia
raykuhs: so what is he programming guys can some1 xplain
onu4r: @georgehotz commit to gj
AresRai: @raykuhs nothing for now justl earning a lot of learning
onu4r: @georgehotz commit to gh*
KOSMOswiterok: KOSMOswiterok subscribed at Tier 1.
sandmann00: George + Josiah Zayner = Corona 🧬Cure
doctorgenus: yesssssssss
c1tr0n75: George is starting to consider Comma BIO seriously LOL
guacDev: :/
sidthescikid: @georgehotz Where's the tutorial?
allbrakesnogas: daaate
doctorgenus: got a hot date?
salem8salem: which type of math most important in programming?
asianboychris: hey @georgehotz
MrStereoX: Whats your favorite work you ever done ? @georgehotz
birkett0011: :(
Chasewhip8_: take a look at this before you go https://www.cell.com/cell/pdf/S0092-8674(20)30229-4.pdf
pjayys77: when are you gonna become a full time streamer
lolzmaster99: What is a typical working day for you like at comma?
jimmyadaro: Ok but wash your hands
Taygetea: @georgehotz i just remember what you said on lex friedman about not being able to rotate a matrix and i'm hesitant about you being able to learn this as well as you could
birkett0011: :/
o______________________k: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
whycopper: Who’s your favorite pornstar @georgehotz
awesomeo113: @salem8salem probably linear algebra
t00big2fl4il: How do I become an elite bubble sorting NAMD programmer
presidentkanyewest2024: monkaS
MrTriharder: @georgehotz no stream tomorrow DansGame
doctorgenus: are you guys working from home?!
guacDev: what happened to the girl that lived with you
awesomeo113: Yeah @doctorgenus
gabo_sk: favorite pokemon? mine is geodude LuvBlondeR
birkett0011: PogChamp
pjayys77: mhmm go on
slimpimp007: ....and although his coding skills are great, he has a lot to learn before he's ready to save anyone. But I believe George can save the world
benchai18: @georgehotz Do you think there’s anything behind the response to this virus? An agenda? Virus is real for sure.. I just mean the extreme measures being taken. Maybe a political opportunity to ruin Trump for elections? Or a push to create public outcry for funding for something (CDC)? I’ve never seen anything like this in my entire life... and it’s not fucking ebola dangerous.
zzorken: PogChamp
blizzside69: hello george u are awesome
wigglebeans: wiggle
aj37z: thats inside you
doctorgenus: @awesomeo113 you work at comma?
jimmyadaro: LUL
360Plato: calling you low iq
allbrakesnogas: if you were a pormstar would your name be geothot
jimmyadaro: Wash your hands and eat onions, i love ya, kisses @georgehotz
sandmann00: George + Josiah Zayner = Corona 🧬Inhibitor
Penguino138: @georgehotz thats true politicians are too dumb to have a plan
t00big2fl4il: do you think I will sub with the proceeds from the stimulus check?
sokhibjke: @georgehotz which key board are you using
lithiumx4900: @benchai18 Ebola doesn't spread nearly as much as this.
MrStereoX: Whats your favorite work you ever done ? was it your own project or at a corporate ? @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: @allbrakesnogas That was pretty good actually
awesomeo113: @doctorgenus I wish lmao. I’m a quant
nitrixen: @sokhibjke Don't.
C0deCane: The news is finally getting viewers LUL
doctorgenus: what kind of mouse do you use?
happypuppppy: @sokhibjke monkaS
Chasewhip8_: I wonder how long it will take for life to get to normal
ackxhpaez: The CDC kept losing paperwork.
THX1342: georgehotz what made you change your mind? the age group of the risk group? the fact they are not economically active?
allbrakesnogas: @jimmyadaro thanks my dude
SHAVEYY_: based
eeXecute: that guy is woke LUL
dorkmo: skull and bones
tornpaperyoyos: George, if you don't make me a 1337 hacker then I will unfollow you on instagram @georgehotz
Hawklite: do you think an objective morality exists?
wigglebeans: america overreacted by not stopping the spread and having the most cases. yeah def.
whycopper: Where did you know where to start hacking the ps3?
AresRai: yea
Penguino138: @georgehotz does North Korea have Covid problems?
gabo_sk: yes
presidentkanyewest2024: monkaS
TheFallDamage: fb is behind all of this
dr_set: They are not friends, they are bought by the same interests
localcanofdutchgold: KKona clap
salem8salem: adrerrall or enthusiasm? youre awesome
allbrakesnogas: they let lions loose on the streets of russia
awesomeo113: Execution is the vaccine in North Korea
ankitc: hahhaa
sokhibjke: @happypuppppy does this word has story behind it ?)))))
jagger_rsw: on scale this can work
Penguino138: @awesomeo113 this is true
C0deCane: who wants to make a bet Lebron James runs for president in the future?
gabo_sk: KKona freedom
benchai18: @georgehotz I think the lengths being taken to ruin Trump by elections are super strong. Desperate even. Fake news, misleading people, false accusations BY Dem politicians... I dno
t00big2fl4il: in Russia they are playing car curling!
THX1342: yeah... slippery slope
sidthescikid: !adderall
ackxhpaez: NK has a pretty effective coronavirus containment strategy
THX1342: hat made you change your mind? the age group of the risk group? the fact they are not economically active?
birkett0011: 100%
c1tr0n75: You should do a cooking stream after this Coronavirus shit is over man
aj37z: sounds liek a good idea
presidentkanyewest2024: snowden said the surveillance state we are developing right now will outlast the virus
256k1: amen
pjayys77: If we're being real here TheIlluminati , the Rothschilds and the Rockefellers are running/ruining everything
MrStereoX: Whats your favorite work you ever done ? was it your own project or at a corporate ? @georgehotz
t00big2fl4il: Black phone 3
fuggiaccunda: tracking is the logical next step in government
maxsokolich: How are the stocks george
360Plato: cellphone is already being tracked trust me
Penguino138: @THX1342 changed his mind about what?
Chasewhip8_: link the paper?
THX1342: Penguino138 threat of the disease
Penguino138: @THX1342 as in it is less concerning or more now?
THX1342: Penguino138 he is not concerned
eeXecute: They need to have a separate chart of who is unhealthy
benchai18: @georgehotz I can see Dems telling CDC-type orgs “make them realize how bad this is. They’ll cry out to fund u more. We’ll use it to beat Trump, and in turn give you more funding”
wigglebeans: cull the oldies
SHAVEYY_: 2
aj37z: more people die from diabetes
awesomeo113: Population control baby
bluejimmy168: Ok let me tell my grandmom real quick. BRB
allbrakesnogas: diabeetus
rustduck: D:
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
mritzing: In that calculation you have to include the people who are going to die from hospitals being overcrowded, not being able to get treated for other things
wigglebeans: so many more young die when there's overloaded hospitals though
lolzmaster99: But still very bad, just not end of the world bad
wigglebeans: i live in society
THX1342: georgehotz what about the collateral of an overflowed health system?
guinness84: probly get lots of person years lost from permanent lung dmage to ~30-50 year olds
AresRai: @mritzing he used a simulation some reputable site made, it included crowded bed in there
awesomeo113: @wigglebeans we live in a society
I2btw: what about he is talking about
I2btw: ok he talking to block
c1tr0n75: I think that the problem is that the hospitals being saturated and other people with other diseases getting less care
t00big2fl4il: Do you think Ray Kurzweil is worried about covid-19
AresRai: @mritzing and he doubled the %, made 1m death in us, so yea...
doctorgenus: I have an idea!
Taygetea: @georgehotz what does your stock portfolio look like? can be in broad strokes if you dont want to say specifics. and how much of it is TSLA?
ahahahaitslit: yee
onu4r: @georgehotz How would you build a system that predicts outbreaks in advance?
4lgor1thm: Well, it's the only solution we got so far.
guacDev: george where is your closet?
presidentkanyewest2024: I saw a video of a guy who got rejected in a chinese hospital with corona because they didnt want to report a new case LUL
wigglebeans: should we invest in commodities
I2btw: This guys only work by rules.
benchai18: @georgehotz I can see Dems telling CDC orgs “make them realize how bad this is. They’ll cry out to fund u more. We’ll use it to beat Trump, and in turn give you more funding”
doctorgenus: implant a microchip in everyone that routinely tests their blood for virus and sending it to Apple
sidthescikid: ..
dorkmo: my buddy that works at a hospital said they aren't doing mamograms
ahahahaitslit: they couldn't treat him and not report it as corona tho?
onu4r: You can use wearables to actually map people with the disease
THX1342: I get your points and have been considering them as well recently but its a tough pill to swallow.... having older relatives I care about, it's not easy...
UnAlpha: its fine if the virus is reintroduced it just cant overwhelm the health system
rimali: @georgehotz herd immunity increases and developing vaccine should make identical repeats less likely
I2btw: My point of view: just let it flow
THX1342: but the economy death is also scary af
wigglebeans: at least the first explosive wave could be lowered to prepare more hospitals. overloading seems inevitable, but "flattening the curve" at least lets us RAISE the bar which we're trying to keep the curve under
bluejimmy168: True
alfyfav: Exactly bro
ahahahaitslit: Sheit....
awesomeo113: I don’t believe the economy will collapse
devbysalas: I agree
I2btw: 200 years ago most ppl die with 35
thickbordiga: stock market line go up tho
lithiumx4900: @I2btw what?
rndmsqnce: deaths haven't started hitting the US hard yet
t00big2fl4il: 2 Trillion Aid Bill = Mucho Subs to this Stream
alfyfav: Here in Mexico we don't have that much cases of coronavirus but I think we must isolate not because of the disease but because of the economy, if we get to be like Italy, we're totally fucked economically
thickbordiga: initial jobless claims go up stock market line go up
c1tr0n75: I had the Virus and I am recovering slowly, I really would want to know if I developped immunity, and for how long?
I2btw: is hard
t00big2fl4il: 1980 there could have been something that they didn't even register
ackxhpaez: In potential earnings
localcanofdutchgold: what was your initial view that made you worried?
I2btw: to not pick
allbrakesnogas: obama turned my frogs gay
I2btw: just let it flow
niiq: already more and more young people are dying from corona
Markkims: that's a tough decision to make
TheArc_TV: @c1tr0n75 they think so, right now
aj37z: GDP output
Rairden1: keep talking
eeXecute: @c1tr0n75 you will know in a couple months
lithiumx4900: There is a non insignificant amount of children < 5, especially < 1 who have gotten this bad according to initial Chinese statements.
t00big2fl4il: 85,991
t00big2fl4il: cases not subs
thecoder15: @c1tr0n75 You get any long term lung dammage ?
sony193: Hello Corohotz virus
culpritgene: in 1980 HIV pandemic started and it was pretty impactful
I2btw: bullshit jobs will disappear when this re-start
ackxhpaez: then herd immunity
wigglebeans: lots of 60 year old masters of their craft losing the ability to train others though, if they suddenly die off. think of all the surgeons, professors... that's a lot of valuable lives lost. maybe 20 life years, but they're insanely valuable
Penguino138: @georgehotz every country and state is on a different trajectory, with different populations and numbers of cases
allbrakesnogas: europe is a scam
THX1342: What really pisses me off is that early warning was given and most governments did nothing about it... this could have been handled so much better
guinness84: just wait till the quarterlys come out
niiq: the average age of corona deaths is getting lower @georgehotz
thickbordiga: @georgehotz how would you stimulate the economy? I've never heard someone with your political opinions call for a stimulus before so I'm curious.
iambdp22: the Spanish flu was also exacerbated by WW and movement of humans , especially young
awesomeo113: Corona fucked my TC
I2btw: ICU
doctorgenus: it's actually pretty high
doctorgenus: Survival rates were 66.6 percent to weaning, 61.1 percent to ICU discharge
C0deCane: @THX1342 don't blame other countries for something that could have been prevented entirely
c1tr0n75: @thecoder15 I don't know man I am really afraid of that, I used to be able to run for over an hour a day, for now I can't run over 12 minutes
ackxhpaez: We'll have to A/B test that
allbrakesnogas: l'hopital oui oui oui
doctorgenus: Survival following mechanical ventilation for acute respiratory ... https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov › pubmed
wigglebeans: what if it turns out ther's a blip where people who are exactly 30 years old are at high risk
t00big2fl4il: worst states NY, NJ, and CA
josalt: hmm...
I2btw: DO IT FAST
dorkmo: it's been 3 months in china, still lockdown
MrStereoX: You need to listen to Yuva Noah Harrari talking about how they acted on a virus and how much we are are in a better place right now then back then. he goes on and talking about what we need to do in the future and hes an absolute genius @georgehotz
lithiumx4900: The other question you're not asking is how many people with regular illnesses will get bumped out of ICUs because they're full. Car crash victims, etc.
thecoder15: @c1tr0n75 Did you end up in the hospital ?
bluejimmy168: 2x is worth it, no?
allbrakesnogas: mereka punya kucingku
t00big2fl4il: New Jersey is Second
t00big2fl4il: What happened to Washington
benchai18: @georgehotz I can see Dems telling CDC orgs “make them realize how bad this is. They’ll cry out to fund u more. We’ll use it to beat Trump, and in turn give you more funding”
awesomeo113: China is a much higher concentration of people though
I2btw: ok
doctorgenus: learn from their mistakes
Penguino138: @georgehotz It's hard to put a blanket quarantine timeline on the whole country when every state is having different infection rates
thickbordiga: @georgehotz okay my bad
wigglebeans: this isn't politics. but if it was, it would be libertarianism LUL
jimmyadaro: Meaning of words
t00big2fl4il: state of washington
c1tr0n75: @thecoder15 no, I get phone calls everyday from doctors and a weekly visit, but they seem really uncertain man
pjayys77: I think no matter if you say it isn't politics, someone will take it that way
fa_k: @MrStereoX why should he listen to (((him)))
Crime_Stein: this is important talk
awesomeo113: And health in China is not great considering air pollution and shit
THX1342: that was the first sign that shit was bad... China locking up 11million people? In a city that has a biolab? that set all my bells and whistles off
thebiggaeboi: REVERSE ENGINEERING? MORE LIKE EPIDEMIOLOGY
360Plato: its policy
thecoder15: @c1tr0n75 That is the real reason I'm really worried, i highly doubt i would die from it but damn also what is you rage range. Im 22 BTW
benchai18: That doesn’t mean there’s ZERO politics involved in our actions here
ArosGeo: what's wrong with politics?
I2btw: Just a other Euthanasia Coaster
C0deCane: China learned from their mistakes LUL Chinese propaganda they are definitely misleading us they lied from the beginning
chlenososik: did he find anything? I fell asleep xD
theknip: @georgehotz sure but what would be the consequences if there was no quarantine?
aj37z: scams
SHAVEYY_: based
Lathendros: holy shit u read Yudkowsky
jagger_rsw: ah.. eliezer :)
lithiumx4900: There is an american youtuber who lived in china many years and was sent a link to a Wuhan lab job posting looking for someone who studies bats and immunology
c1tr0n75: @thecoder15 I am 29 and I wasn't afraid of it at first but it can get very annoying
chetta: tribalism trash
benchai18: @georgehotz I can see Dems telling CDC orgs “make them realize how bad this is. They’ll cry out to fund u more. We’ll use it to beat Trump, and in turn give you more funding”
jimmyadaro: https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/9weLK2AJ9JEt2Tt8f/politics-is-the-mind-killer
Lathendros: @georgehotz what do u think of transhumanism, then?
Penguino138: @georgehotz how long is CA under lockdown? Idaho just got another 3 weeks
64pillars: same like religion
rimali: its not politics per se, its Ideology
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz when did you start to read eliezer essays?
ahahahaitslit: U gonna listen to lex fridman nick bostrom?
doctorgenus: oh I read a detail article that said UK isn't letting coronavirus go wild, the PM is using reverse psychology!!!!!
t00big2fl4il: It does shine light on Politics. Like you said Legitimacy killer. Big events like this pokes holes in their legitimacy
aj37z: tribal
萊萊萊萊特密: BibleThump
pjayys77: but them torquiose .. bad joke
THX1342: blind following
blondephilia: there has to be a rejection of ideology. agreed
tornpaperyoyos: MercyWing1 DarkMode MercyWing2
c1tr0n75: SOCIALISM IS THE ANSWER GEORGE
slimpimp007: 2 party system problems
pjayys77: and spelling..
t00big2fl4il: hack
Ayyyy420Lmao: protesting the prosecution of serial killers Kappa
twinprimes71: !uptime
I2btw: Politics volks work on both site guys
awesomeo113: Can you go on Joe Rogans podcast @georgehotz
thecoder15: you have any underlying conditions how does that happen, i know of someone who died but they were 50+ and unhealthy @c1tr0n75
niiq: what?
kostilin13: libtards and trumpcucks all over = na politics ResidentSleeper
Penguino138: Covid popped the bubble that was patched up in 2008
Ayyyy420Lmao: @c1tr0n75 the answer to overpopulation maybe
doctorgenus: you don't think we are too late?
presidentkanyewest2024: the WHO leader praised trump for his politics on corona
McGoopin: lowest deaths per cases of any country right?
allbrakesnogas: obama should start a resort in the carribean called the OBahama
dorkmo: george obviously not listening to the scientists
doctorgenus: It's GG for NYC in 2 weeks, no?
echotaco: Weren't they freezing rents in California? How did your friend get kicked out
adorablejaay: nathanYikes
pjayys77: @georgehotz how do you feel about placing moratoriums on leases, mortgages, student debt, just a pause on these non essential activities government with the government forgiving this paused period when the economy returns
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Has imposter syndrome mess with you at any given time?
THX1342: I'm under 40 but will probably die if I get it... pepeHands
eeXecute: In NYC all the homeless are gonna be GG
I2btw: How you will bring thow ppl back in to work!
josalt: It's crazy how its just come out of nowhere...
doctorgenus: tell us a fire story!!!!!
zennydmt: why do u fire people?
o______________________k: mizkifPout mizkifPout mizkifPout mizkifPout mizkifPout mizkifPout mizkifPout mizkifPout
doctorgenus: what he do?
doctorgenus: too dumb?
I2btw: This is a total reset
glitch3dout: When the president says the economy is more important than saving lives, I would call the response is bad
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Has imposter syndrome mess with you at any given time?
josalt: Think of all the people who don't have a job now...
benchai18: @georgehotz I feel like you’re consciously avoiding a potentially controversial discussion about whether or not politics play a role in America’s response. I’m not saying it’s bad. But it’s already being used to try ruining Trump. I’m not saying it’s a conspiracy. I’m saying that it seems that some local gov is willfully ignorant or uninterested In the economic effect these measures are having on Californians.
zennydmt: why did u fire people? because of incompetence?
fydtkadl: ㅏ
aj37z: how smart is ur sister
THX1342: georgehotz I have bad lungs unfortunatelly... ex-smoker and asma
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 He talked about that yesterday mf
Ayyyy420Lmao: @aj37z the question is... she hot?
jimmyadaro: @THX1342 Damn man
aj37z: @Ayyyy420Lmao good question
dorkmo: guy I knows wife has copd
awesomeo113: Fax
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Missed that shit mf. I dipped before it ended. Beginning middle or end? So I can check the YouTube
C0deCane: @THX1342 bad lungs != bad immunity
awesomeo113: Is your sister also a savant
Taygetea: feeling dark
MrStereoX: @THX1342 stay home buddy. my girlfriend is with asma too havnt seen her for a month because of it
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Idk, do i look like a fucking clock mf? LUL
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Send link 😉
c1tr0n75: @thecoder15 no underlaying conditions for me man, none. I also try eat healthy and do a lot of sports, I mean I have 8% body fat, can run over 10 miles / day, now I cant' run over 1 mile... the doctors said to me that it's maybe to early to do any of that because the complete recovery from this may take months =, but they're not sure
onu4r: it's all about mutation
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 LUL LUL LUL LUL Love ya man
benchai18: @jimmyadaro take it easy puto, you’re my homie
sidthescikid: hmm
Penguino138: @georgehotz Gonna say this every stream but keep it up. Keep feeding us facts and calm, much appreciated!
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Hahahaha
benchai18: @jimmyadaro ❤️
t00big2fl4il: but remember none of this touches hacking. they/it can't ruin hacking......self-reliance is the original hack
THX1342: @georgehotz read my last
dorkmo: what was death rate at kirkland?
onu4r: but it is slow in terms of mutating that causes its benefit
Ayyyy420Lmao: an XXX event
levinson2504: 200x
liiiiiig0: for 60+ yrs old its almost 100x
zennydmt: would u say u are a multitasker or focus only on one thing at a time
Radar_CS: Not yet :3
aj37z: 100x bitmex
twinprimes71: !uptime
glitch3dout: What's. a100x event in your opinion?
slimpimp007: what does that mean?
t00big2fl4il: 1200x event
gabo_sk: event
liiiiiig0: 100x risk of dying compared to younger than 60 yrs
awesomeo113: Hunnid
thickbordiga: @georgehotz can you explain what 100x means? I am lost.
jimmyadaro: 1Bx
AresRai: 500k
Radar_CS: 10x
senpagax: aj37z yusss lol
presidentkanyewest2024: 5 mil
360Plato: @thickbordiga casualties
c1tr0n75: @georgehotz a 101 year old man survived Coronavirus yesterday,
benchai18: OK ENOUGH OF THIS BULLSHIT LETS GET SERIOUS. @georgehotz Do you eat ass????
Crime_Stein: check out this data. It shows how severe this actually is.
thecoder15: @thickbordiga 100X worse than the common cold
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Has imposter syndrome mess with you at any given time?
Crime_Stein: https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/03/25/opinion/coronavirus-trump-reopen-america.html
thickbordiga: oh gotcha thanks guys
levinson2504: world war was a 1000x event Kappa
TigerstarZ: i'm a big smoker and got covid-19, i just have lost the sense of smell
THX1342: if nothing is done in Brazil, for example, 1 million will die
C0deCane: @georgehotz what would be a good sign we are getting to the tail end of this thing?
awesomeo113: 5 mill
allbrakesnogas: guys we should bring back the plague
I2btw: in the end is just a flu, but faster
dorkmo: my guess is 4 million
glitch3dout: But the flu doesn't make whole countries go in to shutdown
fri3d_: why does everyone only measure deaths and not hospitalizations
blondephilia: LUL
glitch3dout: So you cant just look at deaths
Sim_Ayo: Sim_Ayo subscribed with Twitch Prime.
jimmyadaro: 100Tx
AresRai: @georgehotz did you watch joe rogan podcast with the disease expert/detective ?
benchai18: Is it safe to eat ass during corona pandemic
guinness84: raining in san diego monkaS
wigglebeans: @I2btw flu but faster and also deadlier
Strictoaster: https://neherlab.org/covid19
jimmyadaro: @AresRai I'll check it out
THX1342: this https://neherlab.org/covid19/ ?
awesomeo113: That’s how everything is @glitch3dout people only care about deaths
AresRai: @jimmyadaro its good
o______________________k: loooooool
jagger_rsw: What are the general measures in US? Is it like per-county? Are there any lockdowns (people strongly suggested to stay home)?
THX1342: oops sorry for repost
presidentkanyewest2024: italian politicans are reporting that they think the hospitals are lying about the number of deaths and its actually higher than reported
blondephilia: There are no intelligent mainstream positions. Insofar as I agree with them I do so for much more logical and prescient reasons.
I2btw: @wigglebeans it expose the US metical system YES.
guacDev: lol
levinson2504: Israeli scientist predicted 60% will get corona eventually, plug in the mortality rate
nremind: America flew a bunch of infected people from the cruise ship back to the US on an airplane full of healthy people against the CDC's recommendation https://www.snopes.com/news/2020
AresRai: @jimmyadaro and his number do align with george's on deaths
dorkmo: once they run out of hospital space, how does death rate increase?
jimmyadaro: @AresRai Cool
glitch3dout: @awesomeo113 That's sad :(
THX1342: don't worry, brazil's bolsoNERO gotcha
C0deCane: how well do you think they are tracking things, and do you think they are more reluctant to say someone recovered or no? @georgehotz
AresRai: @georgehotz did you watch joe rogan podcast with the disease expert/detective ?
lolzmaster99: Paper with predictions https://www.imperial.ac.uk/media/imperial-college/medicine/sph/ide/gida-fellowships/Imperial-College-COVID19-Global-Impact-26-03-2020.pdf?fbclid=IwAR1IMEC8YWaGhgpOJ0_kVvSeeVKpBf68H4B1vmt71wfcsVEFj-kGP4muCb8
MrStereoX: @levinson2504 Well in the long-run its probbly ture
awesomeo113: @glitch3dout it’s like mass shootings here. People neglect to think about those who are injured
I2btw: most have it for 14 days
lolzmaster99: "Without measures 7 billion infections"
jagger_rsw: That's an intriguing idea, if US was metric, then social distancing would be 6meters instead of 6feet, so it'd be harder to contract it.
pikomane2: occasionally u mumble and its hard to understand you. do you take adderall?
I2btw: othing happend
liiiiiig0: about 40-80% of ppl will get coronavirus, and about 2-4% of them will die
liiiiiig0: do the math
I2btw: nothing
Crime_Stein: the problem with corona virus is that people with no symptoms still infect 2.5-3 people on average.
benchai18: @aresrai The guy selling a book and wrapping the whole episode up with a cry for more funding? BTW- I think that research SHOULD get more funding. I just can’t help but consider that all humans are fallible, and how much does his (good) goal effect his tone?
Radar_CS: It's been 3 months and covids has like 1/3 of average flu death/year. 12x event imo
niiq: 70-80% gonna get it probably if you dont do anything
levinson2504: 2% of 7 bil is a lot
C0deCane: @liiiiiig0 LUL how can you say do the math and give a literal 40% gap hahahaha
AresRai: @benchai18 did he wrap it up with a call for funding ? lol didn't finish the last last part
Taygetea: @benchai18 he deserves credit for predicting it
MrStereoX: Did the virus get to india yet? i think over there will be a BIG wipe..
jagger_rsw: merekl said 60% will get it
niiq: that what experts say
senpagax: THE MAN IS NOT ON ADERALL lol
THX1342: the r0 is pretty strong
lolzmaster99: Read paper above
Ayyyy420Lmao: why wouldnt they? what will stop it?
smalldiickrick: indias on lockdown already i think
blondephilia: The solution was always to be more populist/nationalist. Don't have enough medical equipment (masks, ventilators, beds, etc.)? Bring manufacturing back to the US. Infection started overseas? Unequivocally shut the borders, no questions asked. Citizens under lockdown, losing their jobs? Bail them out, not the globalist corporations. It's a very simple formula.
glitch3dout: @MrStereoX I'm from India. Our whole country is in shutdown for 21 days
levinson2504: top 1% don't get it
liiiiiig0: @C0deCane that's because those are the estimations which the scientists have given
I2btw: Be happpy most of us will die in the wild
benchai18: @aresrai Yeah big time. It was like the convo trailed off into his message to the public (which again, I generally agree with)
AzzoDio: we see in most clusters that pretty much everyone can get infected so it's going to reach about 50% just like most viruses that do that
VANRA: @georgehotz wait im dumb is the purpose of these streams trying to literally cure corona?
MrStereoX: @glitch3dout Good to hear! did people dier ?
64pillars: well thats what the headlines are not necessarily what experts are gonna say 100% rather the worst case scenario
MrStereoX: die*
Hawklite: guess i can't go outside for the next 2 years until a vaccine is made since i have an autoimmune disease
theknip: @georgehotz your latency and infectious period are low.
dr_set: if only a 20% got it on a cruize ship, there's no way in hell that 80% are going to get it
dorkmo: short cruuise
pjayys77: "r naught"
AzzoDio: look at any cluster that is the cruise ship hospital wards choir groups etc
Chasewhip8_: A lot of the cases are not reported as they are asymptematic at the moment. Tests also take up to a week to come back which causes them to spread to others in their communities easier. Thats why the number is going to get so high and most likely up to at least a 50% infection rate
THX1342: but that's the thing. bolsonaro in brazil is pushing a 'zero fucks' policy
Penguino138: @georgehotz Is it true each infected person needs to spread to less than 1 other to blunt the curve?
levinson2504: @MrStereoX known cases are below 700 I think
C0deCane: LUL @liiiiiig0 those scientist should be ashamed of themselves for publishing shush garbage
AresRai: @benchai18 but the guy been a disease "detective" for decades and even us government does ask for his opinion, hes not fake
benchai18: @taygetea I don’t disagree
dorkmo: two week cruise not enough time to fully spread
niiq: u cant compare it to a cruise ship
presidentkanyewest2024: did they not get it at all or did they show now symptoms? @georgehotz
wigglebeans: @dr_set they were only on that cruise ship for so long. we're here on the earth for a while
liiiiiig0: @C0deCane aight dud
Crime_Stein: the problem is people with no symptoms arent being tested so the r0 could be far above 3. which is very very bad.
I2btw: bad wut?
Saltyballss: did they test everyone on the ship ? or just ppl with symptoms?
glitch3dout: @MrStereoX https://www.covid19india.org/ But then again our testing is insanely low. Too early to say anything
blondephilia: @dr_set this. That princess cruise is the best case "in a vacuum" for the true numbers. And that's after ignoring latent biological factors.
AzzoDio: sure
pikomane2: yess
the_EZPZ: yes
MrStereoX: @glitch3dout Stay home dude :)
levinson2504: yes
doctorgenus: @georgehotz if you're president, what is one thing you will do right now?
THX1342: yes
niiq: if they want to yes
nitrixen: Is it time for Buddism, yet?
pikomane2: hopefully me
levinson2504: id go
slimpimp007: yea
localcanofdutchgold: didn't we do that with the moon?
dr_set: yea
benchai18: @aresrai Agreed. I’m not discrediting him at all. I’m just saying he’s a human being. And when u give a human such a HUGE platform, it’s almost always an opportunity— perhaps subconsciously
smalldiickrick: no
THX1342: @georgehotz any findings/thoughts on Chloroquine?
360Plato: I would do it
roreax6: Hell yeah.
presidentkanyewest2024: PogChamp
MrStereoX: Kappa
liiiiiig0: KKApitalist
L0ader: Pog
360Plato: we wouldnt
blondephilia: Who's "we"? Most people have zero understanding of the world.
doctorgenus: LOL
eeXecute: LUL
pjayys77: when ppl threw out all there morals as quick as they did to fight over Toilet Paper, yes... I believe it
chetta: @georgehotz I remember finding the slate star codex via his article on adderall risks. really amazing writer, everything you read/bring up is amazing though.
Saltyballss: but how do we get there?
TheFallDamage: SAVAGE PRESIDENT
smalldiickrick: fuck mars LUL
Penguino138: @georgehotz Is it true each infected person needs to spread to less than 1 other to blunt the curve?
allbrakesnogas: i'd spend the money on a big ass mars bar
AresRai: @benchai18 I'd do the same tbh, there are worse ways to make money than selling a book lol
Saltyballss: spend it to elon
the_EZPZ: not the social security BibleThump take the military budget
liiiiiig0: LUL
AzzoDio: I think human space travel is a waste of money. if it colonize space it will be with robots
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz so which yudkovsky's essays do you recommend to read the most? have a list?
t00big2fl4il: In the end what will have the most traction? Covid-19, Mars Rover, NAMD, UM?
niiq: how about a wall Kappa
rimali: why bother there are pyramids already on mars, ancient aliens brooo
levinson2504: egypt
MrStereoX: You could join the Kanye West Movment @georgehotz
TheFallDamage: Elon Tusk
I2btw: What about HUMANS can all DIE on earth/Mars. Nothing change.
benchai18: @mrstereox I heard in jpost that Israeli doctor in Italy said they’re not giving 60+ access to ventilators. Dno if it’s true
360Plato: 1.5 trillion $ grave
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: 👽 Kapp
presidentkanyewest2024: the gizeh pyramids are >20k years old
Penguino138: @georgehotz how/when do you think the great pyramids of giza were built?
jimmyadaro: 200 trillion grave for me pls
toasty_jk2: aliens
pjayys77: its a lofty goal, just about Far Fetched think everyone is thinking Elon
avastt41: pharaoh khufu Kappa
jagger_rsw: US builds underground storage for nuclear waste that should last 1M years
Ayyyy420Lmao: it will become a mountain
tornpaperyoyos: Is that the TempleOS guy? LUL
THX1342: @georgehotz did you find anything about Chloroquine as cure?
mattdougherty22: we store all the Bigfoots in there
Vertwo: KKona
AzzoDio: Tesla is cool by human space travel is a waste of money
t00big2fl4il: Pyramid Scheme
Ayyyy420Lmao: just like the pyramids in romania built by aliens
c1tr0n75: are you still leaving in the cloud @georgehotz ?
AresRai: a mile high LUL
nitrixen: Space elevator
dr_set: @wigglebeans I understand that, but in the cruise ship you are very cram with other people and everybody is touching the same surfaces
levinson2504: we can destroy another planetbmonkaS
pikomane2: you ever check out the memphis Bass Pro pyramid?
guinness84: holy shit whered they get all this sand
sidthescikid: didnt nikolas tesla want pyramids
wigglebeans: for storing grain
martonlanga: pyramids are underrated
Vertwo: hell yeah KKona
I2btw: sounds a blockbuster
Ayyyy420Lmao: it will get covered by dirt and eventually trees man
tornpaperyoyos: templeOS guy? LUL
garydsmith1: why should't corona virus be blamed on china's way of eating? just want to know not being racist - mostly to give an answer to my dad - when did you turn on follower only chat? new account only made twitch to watch your stream
playerg0at_: r u ok bro
doctorgenus: will u be buried under it?
smalldiickrick: @pikomane2 that building is PogChamp
THX1342: made of what?
jagger_rsw: mile by mile by mile doesn't work ;)
FusRoDead: why north dakota?
the_EZPZ: make it a tetrahedron
MrStereoX: @benchai18 Its true...
volere: chick norris jokes
volere: is this 2010
pjayys77: When do you think Trump will add his face to Mt. Rushmore
iv4nhoe: a mile LUL
Penguino138: @georgehotz how/when do you think the great pyramids of giza were built?
benchai18: @aresrai Agreed. He wrote that book before all this. That counts for something (though, what he wrote is very similar to the previous recent viruses. Swine, sars, wtvr... I don’t remember when he wrote it)
THX1342: next, india bombs everybody because we eat cow
tkdboy555: We should be using biohazard masks instead of shitty N95 masks that do basically nothing
AzzoDio: if you can find the original pangolin pretty sure you can find the cure. isn't that how it works
Chasewhip8_: we cant blame them because thats not the cause https://www.sciencealert.com/genome-analysis-of-the-coronavirus-suggests-two-viruses-may-have-combined/amp
volere: if you blame it on china's way of eating, im sorry. you are severely misinformed
Chasewhip8_: read that
Ayyyy420Lmao: not aliens?
pikomane2: @garydsmith1 corona is north korea's "christmsa present"
C4TFive: Egyptian....aliens
t00big2fl4il: Chuck Norris has sick NAMD Bubble Sort Skillz. Didn't you know yo'
dorkmo: slaveryyy
beaverater: The real tragedy of this whole thing is that after it's over it's going to be impossible to get a really good bat soup anymore.
mattdougherty22: Easter Island is some cool shit
TheFallDamage: how do u know if this virus is not human made? @georgehotz
levinson2504: but that have to make stricter laws regarding their wet markets
niiq: u actually think humans build the pyramid? LUL
I2btw: lul
zennydmt: have you read the bhagavad gita?
360Plato: can you imagine an industry dedicated to faking human accomplishments
garydsmith1: @pikomane2 what do you mean?
archeadis: @volere what?
porteus: monkaS super virus
presidentkanyewest2024: its not a conspiracy, you are just not educated enough @georgehotz
MrStereoX: I think it was slavery too @dorkmo
sidthescikid: someone linked that earlier in the day
slimpimp007: those Egyptians were clever af, the Pharaoh had them working working
AresRai: 2 processors virus monkaS
levinson2504: @360Plato nasa Kappa
C0deCane: @Chasewhip8_ is that a Chinese source LUL
benchai18: @georgehotz (Hmm. This is super random... are you familiar w this publication and is this true? I mean not necessarily based on your Italy knowledge but on your israeli publication knowledge 🙈🥴. https://m.jpost.com/International/Israeli-doctor-in-Italy-We-no-longer-help-those-over-60-621856 )
aj37z: earth rebelling
I2btw: rebelling for what?
benchai18: Sorry, the message wasn’t meant to be pasted
benchai18: Just the link
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 That's fiucked up
blondephilia: just run a -diff LUL
jagger_rsw: "Egiptians were patient people, but when their pharaohs went bad on them, not even 3000 years have passed, and pharaohs were removed from power"
mattdougherty22: ERIC WEINSTEIN THE PORTAL STORY (3 MIN): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
jimmyadaro: @blondephilia LUL
C0deCane: how reliable is "sciencealert.com"
blur3n: blur3n subscribed with Twitch Prime.
pikomane2: @garydsmith1 remember North Korea warned US to prepare for a "Christmas gift"
benchai18: @jimmyadaro maybe. I dno. Hard to judge something via an article u know
guinness84: how reliable is viagra
the_EZPZ: very.
alfyfav: HAHAHAH
allbrakesnogas: whats your favourite programming language
TheFallDamage: how do u know if this virus is not human made? @georgehotz
t00big2fl4il: egyptians were hackers as well
sidthescikid: @guinness84 test it, ill be control
benchai18: https://www.jpost.com/International/Israeli-doctor-in-Italy-We-no-longer-help-those-over-60-621856
tkdboy555: they literally have animals
the_EZPZ: that is a conspiracy
doctorgenus: if you don't know how to code, what will you be doing right now? will you be a redneck with a tanktop shooting guns?
tkdboy555: shitting on top of each other
Chasewhip8_: nut it didnt come from JUST bats
tkdboy555: in the markets
Chasewhip8_: but*
THX1342: what is the probability of a super contagious disease appearing on a city with a biolab
I2btw: how long he will be self-driving to find out stuff Kappa Kappa
wigglebeans: it makes it slightly more likely to be from the market actually, just by the stats of how many animals come in contact with each other
AzzoDio: you can't know for sure that viruses like this occur naturally all the time
tkdboy555: this is a result of poor hygiene for animals
pjayys77: this was a failed NSA zero day , it back fired
I2btw: ok
Vertwo: monkaS
I2btw: china is old 1000 years
Radar_CS: hmmm
Hawklite: yes
martonlanga: it would be much more similar to SARS if it would be human made
MrMcaustin1: no
Sim_Ayo: no
MrMcaustin1: Not as extreme as china
jimmyadaro: @tkdboy555 Nothing to do with chinese people eating them am i rite?
360Plato: someone was talking the other day about looking for virus IDs in one strain
nremind: engineered bioweapons would be more targeted
THX1342: if it started in a city that had a biolab, yes LUL
syns0r: there wasnt lockdowns with H1N1 and it started here
ahahahaitslit: yes
slimpimp007: well at least there wouldn't be suppression of speech
MrStereoX: Depends how bad it was speding around
tkdboy555: @jimmyadaro well they ate the animals that got shit and pukled on by other animals
wigglebeans: i don't even get how SARS and MERS managed to get stopped. seems lucky
tkdboy555: @jimmyadaro and for some icing on the cake, probably didnt cook them well enough
jimmyadaro: @tkdboy555 NotLikeThis
sidthescikid: LUL
ahahahaitslit: why would there not be lockdowns? Look at NY and Seattle
I2btw: is now all overall, no look down works now
AresRai: what stops people from spreading sars monkaS
the_EZPZ: in December our politicians were selling all their stocks :/
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC
ahahahaitslit: The evidence is there already
localcanofdutchgold: lul
smalldiickrick: madagascar monkaS
MrStereoX: Greenland and moroco
wigglebeans: "madagascar" is the meme
Markkims: lul
jimmyadaro: lul
jimmyadaro: LUL
presidentkanyewest2024: its always greenland or new zealand LUL
garydsmith1: try using duckduckgo for this stream? @georgehotz
sidthescikid: or madagascar
ReasonableLoL: LUL
11plus4thinking: yes
tkdboy555: We're not doing containment right
tkdboy555: That's why
pikomane2: LMAO plague inc
THX1342: #FlatteningTheCurve
tkdboy555: These government leaders are borderline treasonous
stalys_: Didn’t people with SARS show symptoms early making it easier to contain
pikomane2: evolve as fast as possible
ReasonableLoL: CoolCat
11plus4thinking: a lot of people will die
AzzoDio: Korea says yes. also waiting on monoclonal antibody treatment. a few months
Wireballz: how did spread so far ??
presidentkanyewest2024: did he say 15 or 50%
the_EZPZ: @tkdboy555 straight up. sit and wait strategy
pikomane2: The media hysteria was unprecedented with this virus so no
AresRai: 15%
wigglebeans: gotta think about the % hospitalized
Penguino138: Small countries can probably handle longer lockdown
asaalgk: you bet your ass no one will open the borders to america then
AzzoDio: we could try everyone wears masks strategy
11plus4thinking: 24k deaths vs 122k recovered monkaS
THX1342: DENGVAXIA
THX1342: DnA vaccine
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz yes, against crohn's disease - "remicade"
THX1342: failed hard
THX1342: google it
wigglebeans: we live in a world
alfyfav: We live in a society
blondephilia: we live in a society 🤡
smalldiickrick: a society
11plus4thinking: we live in a society BrokeBack
ReasonableLoL: LUL
AzzoDio: Korea had their first case on the same day that the United States. but now they're way less lockdown than us and have fewer cases.
wigglebeans: most landlords are over 60. let em die
dorkmo: REIT
MrTriharder: @georgehotz India has a month long lock down . Prime minister made it compulsory.
voxelfox0125: So correct me if i'm wrong, but did goehot know absolutely nothing about the biology information he talks about in these streams 2 weeks ago? If that's true i'm very impressed.
THX1342: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dengvaxia_controversy failed DNA vaccined in 2018. 800K vaccinations done.
psychedelictw9t: hi Georgy(:
AzzoDio: can I have the first case on the same day as house and everyone is still working in Korea and have less cases
garydsmith1: try using duckduckgo for this stream?
360Plato: debt crisis
PiroFloydian: mortgages are frozen rn
tkdboy555: The middle class has been getting screwed by the Fed for years. Time to take our money back
MrTriharder: @voxelfox0125 He studied biochem back in Rochester
c1tr0n75: I thought you lived in the cloud @georgehotz
zennydmt: have you been to india? do u think the indian lockdown will work?
tkdboy555: Fuck the Fed, fuck the treasury, fuck Congress, fuck the president
tkdboy555: we want our money
alfyfav: Is Geo a dropout?
blondephilia: So what you're saying is that we must demolish the capitalist order... SeemsGood
Wireballz: @georgehotz How do you think it spread so far and wide birds ?
gabivlj: poor landlords ! :(
THX1342: yes
alfyfav: Nice
AzzoDio: the question is how is South Korea still functioning and still has a good economy
Penguino138: @georgehotz Someone killed a young boy in Horseshoe Bend Idaho because he thought Covid was ending the world. Do u think we'll see more psychos like that?
garydsmith1: @zennydmt he has't been to india, he said after corona he will visit
jagger_rsw: I'm not sure if that's the type of monoclonal cell therapy you were talking about - but look for Infliximab on wiki
dorkmo: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Real_estate_investment_trust
Chasewhip8_: I think they might have actually had progress on finding a human monoclonal antibody blocking SARS-CoV-2 https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.11.987958v1.full
levinson2504: India banned export of dengue vaccine because it might be able to cure corona somewhat
voxelfox0125: @MrTriharder That explains it thanks.
prakyath_kantharaju: if lockdown doesnot work india is fucked
tkdboy555: @AzzoDio they have universal healthcare
t00big2fl4il: https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2018-10-04/the-big-hack-how-china-used-a-tiny-chip-to-infiltrate-america-s-top-companies
UberFreak9000: @MrTriharder it's exceeded 500 cases right?
nremind: Containment is possible in less democratic societies, it just requires heavy lockdown
AresRai: @georgehotz look up pan-drug resistant bacteria
THX1342: watch this later, dengvaxia is mentioned. excellent video about RNA vaccines https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MtDMXypfnTY
MrTriharder: @uberfreak9000 700
niiq: tell that trump LUL
dorkmo: someone said upcoming reit crash https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Real_estate_investment_trust
levinson2504: @UberFreak9000 650 rn
AzzoDio: Korea is just going to test every single person that goes to a public event at the door now. they're going to just keep working and literally test everyone multiple times a day pretty crazy
wigglebeans: autistic people are highly represented in the STEM fields so autism causes vaccines
Santiago_LHC: Vaccines cause altruism
MrTriharder: @levinson2504 I think I saw 700 but don’t know
Chasewhip8_: george look at that link i sent it is a good read
blondephilia: There are many side effects of certain vaccines that are downplayed in pop culture.
THX1342: @georgehotz https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MtDMXypfnTY
thecoder15: Vaccines dont help with autoimmune diseases though, at least some of them
Penguino138: @georgehotz Someone killed a young boy in Horseshoe Bend Idaho because he thought Covid was ending the world. Do u think we'll see more psychos like that?
garydsmith1: y using duckduckgo for this stream?
Chasewhip8_: https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.11.987958v1.full
AresRai: @georgehotz look up pan-drug resistant bacteria.
theknip: @georgehotz China now have 3000 active cases thanks to quarantine. Quarantine works, but at the cost of the economy. the question is what the cost would be if everybody would be infected
the_EZPZ: @wigglebeans LMAO
puffgrape: should be reconsidered current extreme globalization after covid-19 is over? what are your thoughts man
garydsmith1: try using duckduckgo for this stream?
UberFreak9000: @MrTriharder I heard they are planning to extend the lockdown till april 15
Ayyyy420Lmao: some MMR version or batch defo caused autism and it was covered up so the government didnt have to pay reparations
Krakken_TM: @georgehotz sent you a video from a journalist back in 2010 that had a military friend that accidentaly joined a senior mason group in london. hes predictin conflicts with israel iran and the biological weapons of a flu like virus in china. so if yo uare interested when u finish streaming sit and watch it its very interesting
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz https://coronavirus.medium.com/
Krakken_TM: in twitch whisper
jagger_rsw: bloomberg never retracted it
MrTriharder: @uberfreak9000 It is fixed till 15 April. Confirmed by prime minister. We learnt our lessons from Other countries
garydsmith1: can someone gift me a subscription? please?
Penguino138: @georgehotz Someone killed a young boy in Horseshoe Bend Idaho because he thought Covid was ending the world. Do u think we'll see more psychos like that?
sidthescikid: medium......
Strictoaster: @georgehotz do you think we'll get a clearer picture in 2-3 weeks? whether or not lockdown was better or worse?
martonlanga: Origin of SARS-CoV-2 https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0820-9
jimmyadaro: It is news-y
Drathimos: do we know how long the coronavirus antibodies last
allbrakesnogas: if you were a pornstar would your name be geothot
wigglebeans: what an uninteresting question
AresRai: monkaS
tkdboy555: oh so you mean to tell me that powerful people say things to make markets move? wow tell me more about how capitalism is about faux-speculation and faux wealth generation
Chasewhip8_: I live in idaho wheres the link
blondephilia: "vaccines cause autism" is a strawman. There are verified cases of certain vaccines causing severe side effects in specific children that even the CDC has recognized.
pikomane2: schizos gonna tweak out occasionaly
doctorgenus: @georgehotz I have a startup idea. Can you tell me it's a good idea? The idea is instant wills through an app for people that are dying from covid19
beldodogium: :)
jimmyadaro: @doctorgenus Fucked up
Penguino138: This is true any of the weirdest news and scariest WILL get reported
AzzoDio: @georgehotz how can Pokemon Go adapt their ganeplay to our new quarantine lifestyle
eeXecute: @Penguino138 can i get the link to that
MrTriharder: @georgehotz if u want to see a real dumbo, search for kanika kapoor corona FailFish
garydsmith1: @doctorgenus how would you make money?
THX1342: so true
Wireballz: @georgehotz how do you think virus spread far and wide ??
martonlanga: origin of SARS-CoV-2 https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0820-9
doctorgenus: charge 1 percent of someone's fortune
doctorgenus: lol
pjayys77: intelligence operative? or News Anchors
AresRai: @georgehotz look up pan-drug resistant bacteria. monkaS
Penguino138: @eeXecute https://www.ktvb.com/article/news/crime/boy-shot-killed-horseshoe-bend-benjamin-poirier/277-208fa4de-4587-4d5f-8909-ac94c9bd557c
jimmyadaro: Groceries bag again!!
tornpaperyoyos: How tf did the faroe islands even get the coronavirus???
MrMcaustin1: george make a podcast with your views on it
jimmyadaro: Show us the onions
zennydmt: do you use app blockers?
t00big2fl4il: how do I become an elite bioinformatics ninja?
MrMcaustin1: I will totally listen to it
Penguino138: @georgehotz I didn't mean to spread scary news about COVID panic murder, but it is sad to see people taking it to that level
jimmyadaro: @MrMcaustin1 That would be awesome
Chasewhip8_: That dude that killed the boy looks like a crack head on meth
sidthescikid: why would you even do that? Why would that be your immediate response?
smalldiickrick: huh
koreanfoodyum: Nice to see you live again today! ^-^
MrTriharder: @tornpaperyoyos Surprisingly enough faroe island and island are one of the highest fossil fuel users per capita because they take alot of flights. They travel a lot
tkdboy555: you've been living through one for about 19 years now
MrStereoX: @MrMcaustin1 We need him with Joe rogan
tkdboy555: its called the middle east situation
blondephilia: polls LUL
MrTriharder: @tornpaperyoyos Iceland *
pjayys77: "real war"
pjayys77: cmon ppl
jimmyadaro: Geohotz + Joe Rogan <3
samuriia: I think we're handling the virus pretty well in Australia all things considered
doctorgenus: hey @georgehotz if you catch the coronavirus, will you fill out a will?
Santiago_LHC: Happy
martonlanga: origin of SARS-CoV-2 https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0820-9
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you think different states will reach the apex of their infection curve at different times?
phrixus_bro: thanks@
klarmacher: yeah when u gonna hop on joe rogans podcast
jimmyadaro: HELL YEAH
volere: how are u feeling
mattdougherty22: WATCH THIS @georgehotz ERIC WEINSTEIN THE PORTAL STORY (3 MIN): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
thecoder15: military action aint war son
garydsmith1: would you ever run Ads on instagram>
tkdboy555: You mean retarded combat tactics defines "real war"?
MrStereoX: Whats your favorite work you ever done ? was it your own project or at a corporate ? @georgehotz
ooMariaoo: OHH
Repunk: have you watched tigerking?
koreanfoodyum: If you could use 1 programing language not python, which would it be? :O
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz thoughts on spicy food?
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz have a list of yudkovsky essays you'd recommend? he produced like 10k of them
sandmann00: Silent Weapons for Quiet Wars! Great Read!
ahahahaitslit: u gonna watch nick bostrom lex fridman?
MrMcaustin1: Joe Rogan + Geohotz?
Chasewhip8_: my question is read this https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.11.987958v1.full and my answer will be next stream when you read it
360Plato: its real if your from middle america
wigglebeans: what emerging technology should i care about
ahh_me: Youre gonna give the money to the gov??
doctorgenus: my business idea is instant wills and charging 1% of someone's fortune
sidthescikid: @georgehotz how do I download the bio textbook in that legitimate way you did
puffgrape: THOUGHTS ON GLOBALIZATION'S IMPACT ON COVID-19
roreax6: If you had an inspiration in your life, who would it be?
koreanfoodyum: ROGAN!!!!!
garydsmith1: what text books did you buy?
the_EZPZ: we are never the victims of our wars. some people are though
zennydmt: should I stay inside if I live in NYC
mattdougherty22: watch lex and nick Bostrom and let us know about it
MrTriharder: @georgehotz do quarantine make making self driving cars easier? No signals no humans just increase speed 4Head
smalldiickrick: is golang worth learning?
jimmyadaro: Joe Rogan + Geohot?
koreanfoodyum: Geo X Rogan, the best crossover
roreax6: Thanks man.
Vertwo: PogChamp
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz do you like spicy food?
gabo_sk: pay to win
brownyyyylocks: book recommendation
sidthescikid: PogChamp
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you think different states will reach the apex of their infection curve at different times?
C0deCane: @georgehotz Build a biological firewall for us
SHAVEYY_: inb4 steve jobs
jimmyadaro: Joe Rogan + Geohot
roreax6: Just an iconic person in your life, someone you look up to, etc.
haircutjimmy: morning
roreax6: Sure.
ZemkeCWT: In the Lex Friedman you said Python might be a bad choice for comma.ai. What would you use instead?
beldodogium: what do u think about numpy
slimpimp007: do you lose lung function once you beat Corona?
brownyyyylocks: don't idolize someone you haven't met in real life
garydsmith1: @ZemkeCWT C++?
wigglebeans: is John McAfee crazy?
Vertwo: billy herrington
volere: gratification
ahahahaitslit: just say elon bro
zennydmt: Eureka moment
benchai18: @jimmyadaro I’ve tried. I’ve asked if he wants to be on JRE and he declined. Said he doesn’t want the attention. I tried mate 🤷♂️
zennydmt: the Eureka moment?
brownyyyylocks: xerox park
MrTriharder: Billy Herrington is everyone’s inspiration SeemsGood
THX1342: when you pwn
saintmthw: the ah ha moment?
the_EZPZ: of course John mcaffee is crazy
garydsmith1: @roreax6 can you gift me a sub?
covac123: oh yeah Kreygasm
zennydmt: the Eureka Moment?
wigglebeans: eureka!
zennydmt: the flow state?
MrStereoX: Happiness ? @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 That's kinda sad
smalldiickrick: jizzing
MrTriharder: PogChamp
ZemkeCWT: @garydsmith1 did he actually say that?
volere: dopamine
zennydmt: That's called the flow state
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you think different states will reach the apex of their infection curve at different times?
Hawklite: life is a complex never ending puzzle
zzorken: Matrix
koreanfoodyum: aww, he'd be the best programmer on rogan since carmack :O
C0deCane: it would probably be horrible honestly
guinness84: calm
gabo_sk: being god
allbrakesnogas: @georgehotz you should write a programming language
StrickenDown: Nope
ahh_me: Chasing the knowledge
blondephilia: 170 IQ PogChamp
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Wait, are you a girl? Eat some garlic mf
garydsmith1: @ZemkeCWT not sure. but that's what they use c++
Ayyyy420Lmao: deep
roreax6: I struggle with that every day, in that, I try to understand everything I can, but there's never enough time in the day.
slimpimp007: post nut clarity like
MrMcaustin1: The enlightenment georgehotz
roreax6: Profound answer though
jimmyadaro: lul
nremind: enlightenment?
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz do you like spicy food?
gabo_sk: dsdfsdgf
smalldiickrick: @georgehotz thoughts on terry davis?
MrStereoX: Whats your favorite work you ever done ? was it your own project or at a corporate ? @georgehotz
klarmacher: god
zennydmt: so enlightement or self actualization?
C0deCane: @georgehotz build us a bio firewall
64pillars: Dr Manhattan didn't seem to enjoy life
Santiago_LHC: Which movie you've seen captured technology in the most realistic way?
sidthescikid: Clap
mattdougherty22: Can you watch: watch lex and nick Bostrom and let us know about it
Ayyyy420Lmao: favourite pornstar?
THX1342: goddamit geo we need to meet and smoke weed someday LUL
realsirjoe: Nuclear Power Plants, yes or no?
vHyphy: How do you think we’d achieve that?
Drathimos: that was deep
waterpaste: Is he ever going to put away those groceries?
t00big2fl4il: What takes longer for mass adoption Bitcoin, SelfDriving/Assisted Driving, or Dow 40,000?
Penguino138: @georgehotz how many chicken tenders do you have left?
garydsmith1: are you really going to start a bio company?
pikomane2: ray kurzweil fan?
jimmyadaro: YOU'RE GREAT, WE LOVE YOU
imr_average: !uptime
pjayys77: uh oh are we living the Lost season, where you know we're already...
Ayyyy420Lmao: tits, ass or feet?
lanyxqt2: inspiring man
the_EZPZ: drop acid it's the closest you'll get
blondephilia: Thorium Pogchamp
C0deCane: Cleanest energy source we have
360Plato: gnite\
PiroFloydian: TRUE
smalldiickrick: true
mattdougherty22: Chamath Palihapitaya Yes or No?
koreanfoodyum: I LOVE PENGUINS!
localcanofdutchgold: do you think knowing everything would be satisfying afterwards? @georgehotz
garydsmith1: you really going to start a bio company?
MrMcaustin1: nuclear fusion or fission?
alfyfav: GO NUCLEAR!
octeezy: Tell that to the normies
THX1342: nuclear waste non issue?
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you think different states will reach the apex of their infection curve at different times?
blondephilia: Exactly. So why is the narrative surrounding nuclear so backwards?
Wireballz: @georgehotz how do you think virus spread so far ???
SHAVEYY_: what if the power plants melt down?
MrTriharder: Nuclear energy is the cleanest energy PogChamp
koreanfoodyum: :O
niiq: so what is the solution to nucear waste?
Ayyyy420Lmao: what are the reservers of uranium anyway?
alfyfav: nuclear fission is the easier right now
sidthescikid: @MrMcaustin1 fusion obv. tf?
AresRai: @MrMcaustin1 if we could do fusion it wouldnt even be a question
dr_set: How about the Fukushima factor?
Liz3DE: I think the issue with nuclear power is the waste @georgehotz
alfyfav: But nuclear fussion is awesome af
MrMcaustin1: yeah ik
niiq: @what do with the nuclear waste ?
tornpaperyoyos: Almost looks like the unemployment graph
C0deCane: @niiq inject it back into the earth in injection wells
wigglebeans: acidification of ocean seems pretty alarming
Ayyyy420Lmao: fusion isnt real
the_EZPZ: coal power LUL
martonlanga: Nuclear Fission will be here in 20 years:)
nremind: do you think cold fusion is possible?
MrTriharder: Finland has already done things to handle Nuclear waste PogChamp
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz https://www.edx.org/course/nuclear-energy-science-systems-and-society
ahh_me: Nuclear waste send taht shit to space!
THX1342: @georgehotz what to do with the nuclear waste?
sidthescikid: @Ayyyy420Lmao Yeah but it will be, fission is ass
alfyfav: Nuclear fission is already here bro
Ayyyy420Lmao: 20 years ago they said fusion would be here in 20 lmao
martonlanga: *Fusion
benchai18: @jimmyadaro You’re the only person I’ve ever met that’s talks more [shit] than me
SofiaLouise: why is it bad for thinking?
alfyfav: We don't have nuclear fussion yet
Ayyyy420Lmao: @alfyfav in your dreams
sidthescikid: @THX1342 bottle it and shove it in the ground
pjayys77: cheers to our eventual homes on space colonies
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Is that bad?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @alfyfav nvm missread fision as fusion
alfyfav: ;)
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Nah. Just a scary thought
waterpaste: @georgehotz Are you ever going to put away those groceries?
alfyfav: Don't worry
MrTriharder: @georgehotz comma.nuclear when ?
garydsmith1: are you really going to start a bio company?
dorkmo: chemtrails formula
THX1342: sidthescikid that' s literally brushing the dirt under the rug
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz do you like spicy food?
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Cowabunga it is
ahh_me: If you are taking a test in a stuffy non properly aired room you are statistically at a large disadvantage
alfyfav: I would work there
Santiago_LHC: Which movie (or work of fiction) you've seen represented technology in the most accurate way?
wigglebeans: what do you think about space babies? to be clear, space babies are babies in space
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you think different states will reach the apex of their infection curve at different times?
echotaco: Make a protein that does it backwards
Ayyyy420Lmao: favourite south park episode?
b2kemann: Good morning from once mighty europe
jimmyadaro: SMALL PHARMA
the_EZPZ: fake liberal chemistry more NASA lies
siriusblack189: hi
benchai18: @dorkmo Oooooo. I wonder how George feels abt chem trails
blondephilia: just plant trees :)
smalldiickrick: should i take a test on testosterone
martonlanga: "This is strong evidence that SARS-CoV-2 is not the product of purposeful manipulation" https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0820-9
mattdougherty22: Chamath Palihapitaya Yes or No?
jxmesito_: send some nut into space
Strictoaster: you talked about decentralized apps last stream, any particular project that you find particularly interesting?
iIyaRPV: is golang trash?
jimmyadaro: SPACE WHORES???
jxmesito_: let it grow
sidthescikid: @THX1342 thats what were doing rn, thorium reactors might be able to use nuclear waste and turn it into fuel
doctorgenus: if you didn't know how to code, where would you be now?
FusRoDead: hobbies outside of programming?
Penguino138: @georgehotz how many chicken tenders do you have left?
garydsmith1: are you going to buy lab equipment?
Ayyyy420Lmao: why is it dumb?
wigglebeans: do you supplemet with anything? is anything worthwhile taking daily or every once in a while?
benchai18: @dorkmo I mean obviously he thinks it’s bullshit, but has he looked into ut
alfyfav: :0
localcanofdutchgold: omegalul
SHAVEYY_: I am :)
roreax6: Haha
b2kemann: What are the bets on global warning?
MrTriharder: Sex in space Kreygasm
jimmyadaro: @b2kemann Death.
jimmyadaro: LUL
INTeaRs: python performance sux
timtee: What will be the name of the first porno in space?
jimmyadaro: @MrTriharder It'd be so hard LUL
alfyfav: I mean, there are some things better in golang than c++ isnt?
C0deCane: @martonlanga good link!
THX1342: sidthescikid using it to generate more energy is reasonable. burying it, I don't think so.
allbrakesnogas: there should be a school for dwarves, so they could save money on wall heights
Wireballz: @georgehotz how do you think virus spread so far ??
t00big2fl4il: Golang vs NAMD vs Rust vs ALGOL?
garydsmith1: are you going to buy lab equipment?
ahahahaitslit: have you tried ocaml
thoding: unsafe
smalldiickrick: LUL k im learning Golang now
Santiago_LHC: What are the odds of the people in the ISS getting coronavirus?
waterpaste: Pornhub is free rn
edu4594: lol c++ isn't not compared with coq
slimpimp007: how were your twenty's?
iIyaRPV: Gotcha, thanks man
zennydmt: are u a multitasker?
benchai18: @georgehotz is there a point to learning C still?
samuriia: why the fuck would you make your life harder when u can accomplish the same thing in python in 2 hours except 20
Chasewhip8_: thats how i write my epic java
mattdougherty22: Chamath Palihapitaya Yes or No?
volere: LEARN C
sidthescikid: @THX1342 for sure, def not sustainable, but its our only option rn besides emerging tech
PiroFloydian: @benchai18 embedded systems. and its really fast
smalldiickrick: creep-radiohead?
garydsmith1: @benchai18 yeah you learn about hard ware and memory management if that matters to you
dorkmo: why are airlines still flying almost empty planes.... chemtrails supply
jimmyadaro: Python > C > Java
Chasewhip8_: inside the court room and into the streets?
inatreecrown: your thoughts on swift language?
the_EZPZ: should everyone learn c++ at least a little bit
benchai18: @pirofloydian Yup that’s what I was thinking.
Ayyyy420Lmao: taylor swift Kappa
Liz3DE: I think the issue with nuclear power is the waste, what do you with it. i do not know if we have good sultions yet @georgehotz
eeXecute: LUL
blondephilia: @the_EZPZ LEARN C
Okayge_TeaTime: darude - sandstorm
MrTriharder: I’d choose any language before coding in Java FailFish it’s literally trash
happypuppppy: are you looking for taylor swift 22 song?
Chasewhip8_: Can we get a rap about the coronavirus
martonlanga: Rap incoming
jimmyadaro: @Liz3DE Throw that shit to the sun
localcanofdutchgold: java will kill your brain
THX1342: JAva is so terrible
SHAVEYY_: java be like
SHAVEYY_: try catch
Ayyyy420Lmao: consider a music career
11plus4thinking: AngelThump
jimmyadaro: Rap something @georgehotz
presidentkanyewest2024: BibleThump
Ayyyy420Lmao: comma.music
the_EZPZ: @blondephilia Why C > C++?
Vertwo: AngelThump
b2kemann: Haskell
pjayys77: mhmm go on
feverdreem_: pepeD
MrTriharder: Java is for lazy people who don’t know how write platform specific stuff so need a VM FailFish
porrosyhd123: Kreygasm
waterpaste: Comma.Voice Part 1
jagger_rsw: wow, I hear a plane over switzerland, ther shouldn't be any :)
Chasewhip8_: sars 2 rap would be next level to the point where its not even funny
dorkmo: twitch @ nite
SHAVEYY_: @the_EZPZ because if you learn C you know C++ Kappa
iIyaRPV: tomcr00se is back PogChamp
jimmyadaro: @MrTriharder lmao so true
benchai18: @garydsmith1 This is a dumb question. If I wanted to pop open some household electronics and jack into the UART... does knowing C help? Meaning, how many of those systems use C (if any)?
ICAntF331MyFAce: AngelThump
4FUN_PLAYER: comma.karaoke
Ayyyy420Lmao: @jagger_rsw chemtrailing doesnt stop
voxelfox0125: Do you think some people exist only serve as footstools for others with greater ambition?
saintmthw: beautiful
ahh_me: You this is lit
sidthescikid: AngelThump
MrStereoX: lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN lirikTEN
11plus4thinking: AngelThump voice of an angel
beldodogium: vcl
ahh_me: What do you like to do outside of programming a lot?
mattdougherty22: Watch https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk depicts it perfectly
FusRoDead: Any life advice?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Comma got talent when?
martonlanga: But shouldn't be the purpose of Rust to make it safer & easier to do lowish level coding?
waterpaste: RAP? lmao
MrStereoX: After the corona crap.. Where do you wanna travel ? @georgehotz
sidthescikid: Pog Clap
Krakken_TM: twitch sings stream when?
C0deCane: @jagger_rsw America sent 6 bb52 bombers over that way to fight the virus
PiroFloydian: @Liz3DE @THX1342 you can recycle waste and what you cant theres containment for. and the fuel is so energy dense that theres such a small amount of waste to store
the_EZPZ: AngelThump
thecoder15: Favorite GPGPU project you ever worked on
garydsmith1: are you really not smart enough to program in c++?
C0deCane: b52
t00big2fl4il: Did you ever get the microcorruption email?
BernardoFire: what is the name of the song???
mattdougherty22: WATCH THE PORTAL STORY ERIC WEINSTEIN (3 MIN): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
jimmyadaro: https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0820-9
brownyyyylocks: oh adele
b2kemann: Didnt expect this
jagger_rsw: next pwnie is waiting for ya
blondephilia: @the_EZPZ C teaches you how to program
ahahahaitslit: have you tried ocaml
THX1342: PiroFloydian I was just asking myself about how much waste is actually generated
Ayyyy420Lmao: have you tried TempleOS? thoughts on HolyC?
pjayys77: movei time
dorkmo: lol
waterpaste: omfg she looks scary asf
smalldiickrick: @Ayyyy420Lmao this is what i wanna know LUL
MrStereoX: Narnia ?
garydsmith1: @benchai18 no you learn about FPGA and stuff like that with c and your computer itself not random things in your house
jimmyadaro: OhMyDog
the_EZPZ: @blondephilia not if u want to do OOP... what does it teach that c++ doesn't
echotaco: 2x speed please
Ayyyy420Lmao: ^^
goldensoap_: whata is this
jimmyadaro: ^^^
blondephilia: @the_EZPZ OOP? Use Java
PiroFloydian: heros journey
Ayyyy420Lmao: holy shit dorothy is hot
ahahahaitslit: lmao
MrTriharder: @blondephilia Java is trash
presidentkanyewest2024: Kreygasm
goldensoap_: PedoBear
pjayys77: well nah, she was just high
THX1342: I can't see this and not hear Pink Floyd
SHAVEYY_: Java sucks. Use Python Kappa
guinness84: 2x plz
wigglebeans: cuz it's a convenient plot development device
jimmyadaro: Because movies need to SELL mf
niiq: oh shit i remember watching wizard of oz on acid
Ayyyy420Lmao: ellen paige ugh
smalldiickrick: its 3 mins you autists
jimmyadaro: @niiq Dope
blondephilia: @MrTriharder for OOP?
Santiago_LHC: A portal is an easy story telling mechanism to represent escapism
nvrUmbra: nvrUmbra subscribed at Tier 1.
sidthescikid: comma.philosophy
benchai18: Anyone have the Portal discord link???
MrTriharder: @blondephilia It’s only good for co operate projects
INTeaRs: LUL tru
THX1342: BibleThump
ICAntF331MyFAce: BibleThump
garydsmith1: anyone gifting subs?
Ayyyy420Lmao: putos guiris
the_EZPZ: BibleThump
nitrixen: Chart, URL ?
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao Wow calm down
Abnico: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
tornpaperyoyos: woah i wanna see this church now
THX1342: I want life++
Santiago_LHC: The music from this video is from the movie Moneyball
nitrixen: Chat, share URL?
Exclamation_mark_CODE: now we are thinking with portals GabeN
萊萊萊萊特密: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
AresRai: get your portal chat, do shrooms 🍄
niiq: PogChamp
mattdougherty22: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
thecoder15: been there its dope AF
sidthescikid: BibleThump
nitrixen: Thanks chat
jimmyadaro: He's smiling
MrTriharder: BibleThump
Abnico: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
THX1342: link
benchai18: Long 3 min wow
mattdougherty22: thank you for watching this @georgehotz you should do his show!
pjayys77: I knew it lol
sidthescikid: WeirdChamp Laughing
jimmyadaro: George smiling <3
t00big2fl4il: I think your email from microcorruption.com was stuck in the portal. your thoughts?
octeezy: BibleThump
MrStereoX: lirikTEN
ICAntF331MyFAce: Clap
martonlanga: "This is strong evidence that SARS-CoV-2 is not the product of purposeful manipulation" https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0820-9
C0deCane: LUL wish i could just open a portal when i was in jail
koreanfoodyum: CLAPFACE
garydsmith1: BibleThump
haircutjimmy: nice
ahahahaitslit: listen to his podcast
bokeee_: 😊
voxelfox0125: Do you think some people exist only serve as footstools for others with greater ambition?
FusRoDead: Any life advice?
sidthescikid: BibleThump Clap
martinstuessy: BibleThump
pjayys77: ya did it
ahh_me: @C0deCane LMAO
josalt: Link?
eaterenrgy: zentreCOMFY
MrStereoX: Can you link the video ?
wigglebeans: end it all
THX1342: do you like alan watts?
koreanfoodyum: link pls
chetta: thankyou for the stream
KerasAmateur: How do you feel about the state of the machine learning landscape right now?
goldensoap_: are u done with coronavirus
haircutjimmy: bye!
PiroFloydian: gnight george
pjayys77: can we have a community cry together
dorkmo: covid is a portal for the world
koreanfoodyum: I wanna bookmark
martinstuessy: <3 georgie I help you
jimmyadaro: BibleThump
Santiago_LHC: We all have a portal within
slimpimp007: retziSad
doctorgenus: noooo
11plus4thinking: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
ICAntF331MyFAce: BibleThump
tornpaperyoyos: nooooooooooooooo
MrMcaustin1: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
garydsmith1: saddddd
MrStereoX: NOOOOOOOOOOOOO
jimmyadaro: NO WAY
octeezy: I thought he just liked the game Poortal
C0deCane: LUL
Crime_Stein: noooo
doctorgenus: when's the next one?
gabo_sk: f
PiroFloydian: oh no BibleThump
braininavatt: BibleThump
Ayyyy420Lmao: where is the cure ??
jathemb: literally the first stream I've ever joined and its already ending
MrTriharder: BibleThump
okeeeeeee: good stream
eaterenrgy: Link the vid
braininavatt: :( :( :(
ahahahaitslit: Sheit.......
doctorgenus: this is my druggggggg
AresRai: FeelsBadMan corona noooooo
jimmyadaro: No man come on
senpagax: aw shit yo
eeXecute: BibleThump
goldensoap_: cya next month then
haircutjimmy: no
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
benchai18: Portal discord anyone???
boneitis: microcorruption next, ya?!!
pjayys77: o dayum, actually taking effect
josalt: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
sidthescikid: BibleThump Wait what?!
roreax6: Thanks for the stream - hope you continue the covid research at some point.
ChanceDies: can someone link vid
nizero: lol
MrTriharder: BibleThump 7 see you later
THX1342: you broke geo! BibleThump
dr_set: lul
jimmyadaro: Wow that video fucked his mind
prakyath_kantharaju: stream on Saturday ?
wigglebeans: u just broke him
sandmann00: Hack The Planet!!!!!!!!!
josalt: @ChanceDies https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pb_yvBNLjNk
b2kemann: Haskell next!!!
doctorgenus: don't leave george I'll change!!!!!!!
ChanceDies: tyty!
thecoder15: what we workin on next @georgehotz
doctorgenus: i promise
goldensoap_: ?????????????????
benchai18: Is he messing w us rn?
edu4594: what happened??
ahahahaitslit: bricked geohot
Ayyyy420Lmao: ▲ ▲▲ chat cant triforce
t00big2fl4il: why the end? we'll have to take a look at github.
senpagax: WHAT HAVE OYU DONE???
jimmyadaro: Jesus christ
ICAntF331MyFAce: BibleThump
benchai18: @ahahahaitslit LMFAO
edu4594: dayum bro
martonlanga: george overflow
MrTriharder: FeelsBadMan stop George
doctorgenus: george we neeed you
rndmsqnce: u watch westworld
jimmyadaro: BibleThump
braininavatt: we got chu george <3
culpritgene: the portal of rationality
Exclamation_mark_CODE: this is why we end it by asking what kboard he uses NotLikeThis
doctorgenus: you are our entertainment during this quarintine!!!!!
MrTriharder: BibleThump don’t
beldodogium: BibleThump
MrStereoX: We love these streams !!!!! @georgehotz
THX1342: LUL
Andremm2: this took a turn
ImJ4Gu4R: Lack of motivation?
feverdreem_: get some sleep george
goldensoap_: ??????????????
ImJ4Gu4R: this is hard
pikomane2: im on DMT 9/10 times
edu4594: yo dude don't kill yourself
extrovertintrovert: What patterns
MrTriharder: Who the fuck donated the video DansGame
potatpo567: What do you think about black holws
nizero: lol I'm ready for George to say psychhhhh
THX1342: Who broke Geo
Ayyyy420Lmao: bruh u need to redose that adderall
thecoder15: @georgehotz These days i think its best just stay focused on building cool stuff or exploring, everything else is noise
jimmyadaro: Who did it???
ICAntF331MyFAce: its about the journey, not the destination BibleThump
culpritgene: the portal is the process of portal-search apparantly
garydsmith1: @nizero yeah
MrMcaustin1: he froze
garydsmith1: or mabe he's serious
BernardoFire: THE HERO'S JOURNEY
Br4nnon: buffering...
chetta: when you find it, i feel like that's what life is
THX1342: ^^^
Br4nnon: the alchemist
garydsmith1: @BernardoFire yes!
THX1342: Hero's Journey
protectionfromblue: thats so true
blondephilia: hahah
THX1342: LUL
jimmyadaro: <3
Exclamation_mark_CODE: the power of friendship FeelsGoodMan
sandmann00: We live in the Matrix, Nothing your see or hear is real, its all a figure of your imagination!!!!! Hack The Planet!!!!
wigglebeans: :(
thecoder15: LOL HE TROLLING MAD
11plus4thinking: LUL
chetta: <3
THX1342: gn Geo, take care
happypuppppy: BibleThump
pjayys77: 99% aren't going to find it, and it sucks
Br4nnon: dont do it D:
alfyfav: :(
localcanofdutchgold: <3 FeelsStrongMan
BananStian: What's up?
niiq: CoolStoryBob
jimmyadaro: :(
octeezy: !uptime
waterpaste: Good night
eaterenrgy: gn !
MrStereoX: WE LOVE YOU DODOE
Ayyyy420Lmao: noooooo dont hurt yourself
CreeepingDeath: BibleThump BibleThump
feverdreem_: gn
braininavatt: GG everyone
josalt: <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3
0deinkymi0: best life advice :) thanks geohot
sidthescikid: <3
iIyaRPV: take care man
PiroFloydian: Thakns for the streams george!
pikomane2: run fast
ICAntF331MyFAce: <3
alfyfav: <3
psychedelictw9t: night, you're beautiful, Georgy.😽
tornpaperyoyos: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
b2kemann: GEO is in looove
jimmyadaro: <3
roreax6: Peace man
covac123: gn
goldensoap_: see you next month geothoot